I would love your reaction to
this.
I mean, this is something
that we've come across
in like a group that's
recruiting veterans.
So if you like, what an extreme.
You look at, like
questions 15, 16, and 17.
[dramatic music]
Jesus. [chuckling]
So I'm looking at an intake
questionnaire
for a violent extremist group,
and I'm gonna read you
three of the questions.
Question 15, are you in
the military or a veteran?
If so, which branch?
16, if it comes down to it,
would you go against the oath
you took
in the military and law
enforcement?
You could end up fighting
against
your military/law enforcement
brothers.
I,
I mean,
I think you gotta consider
where somebody has to be
in order to say yes to
those three questions.
And also some of the
capabilities and training
that some of these
individuals bring.
There are places in our military
where we are trained to
start and fuel insurgencies.
There are places in our
military where we are trained
to overthrow governments,
or work with armed militias
in order to do
that sort of thing.
I'm not saying
this to be alarmist,
and I don't think we need to
be afraid of our veterans.
What I do think is that we need
to have a solid understanding
of how badly this could
escalate.
We're not at the point
where violence
is the solution to our problems,
but there are a lot of people
trying to convince vets
and others that we are,
and that is a very
dangerous thing.
[Speaker 1] Today, domestic
terrorism
is the greatest terrorist
threat facing the United States.
[Speaker 2] The threat is
real, and we are all at risk.
For decades,
violent extremist groups
have sought to
infiltrate our military
to gain tactical training
and access to weapons and
explosives.
[Speaker 3] I do believe
the oath means something,
and I know that I'm going
directly against people
who think that they also
are honoring their oath.
[Speaker 4] I, I do
solemnly swear that I will
[Speaker 5] Support the
constitutional
of the United States.
[Speaker 6] Against all
enemies, foreign and domestic.
[Multiple Speakers] So help
me God,
so help me God, so help me, God.
[western music]
Go ahead and fill up
this magazine. [exhaling]
Asked a buddy of mine, I said,
hey man,
"can you uh..."
can you get me some
ammo, some decent ammo?
I can't find any.
He said, yeah, man,
I heard that there's a drug
dealer down on the corner.
He's actually slinging
ammunition now instead of drugs.
So bought some ammunition from
the drug dealer. [laughing]
When people look at these guns,
these rifles and these
handguns and so forth,
there's a lot of folks that see
something
that causes violence.
They see something that's
dangerous
and shouldn't be allowed
in society and so forth.
What they don't realize
is that this is what
gave us our freedom.
This is what won our
independence.
This is what protects
us from attack.
It's not just our God-given,
right,
to defend ourselves, it's
our constitutional right,
but it's also, it's just right,
when you think about it.
This rifle will never
hurt or harm anybody
unless something
comes up against it.
Baby's ready to rock and roll.
[western music]
Being a Texan,
we're supposed to be able
to protect ourselves.
The stuff that they
show you on the movies,
that's our real life,
that's who we are.
The cowboy way,
and the cowboy way is to
be able to defend yourself.
And, I'm proud to say that I
can do that,
you know, pretty effectively.
[gun firing]
I learned how to ride a
horse when I was about six.
The property that we lived
at was a lot like this.
Mesquite trees and so forth.
[gun firing]
My grandfather gave me my first
BB gun
and showed me how to aim,
how to breathe and shoot.
[gun firing]
I was taught how to hone into a
target
and be able to actually execute
with whatever tool I'm using.
[gun firing]
But what you learn in the
military and the army is,
your scopes will fail you,
your red dots will fail you,
the batteries will wear out,
but your irons never ever will.
So I've never had anything on
my rifles
other than my iron sites.
Not the best grouping, but
from 60 yards, 50 yards,
it'll work.
Up close, they'd all be in the
center.
good boy
Come on.
Hey puppy.
I spent my whole life
wanting to join the military.
I mean, there's a photo right
behind me
of me when I was probably
like five years old,
wearing camouflage head to
toe with a pair of dog tags.
I feel like most kids that
I grew up with
went through a phase
of wanting to be
a cop or a firefighter
or an army man, right?
I never grew out of that.
[Kristofer whistling]
[dog barking]
And when I was 16 years old,
September 11th happened,
and it kind of put a different
spin on that desire to serve.
And I went to go out and find
bad guys and find justice.
So this, when
I was 18 years old,
in basic training,
and it's the standard
photo that you take
before you know what anything
on the uniform means.
So you notice there's
no ribbon, no name tag,
anything like that, it's
a bare bones uniform.
I was wearing a shirt, jacket,
and tie that weren't mine.
I mean, this is ignorance
is bliss right here.
That's what this photo is.
The historical record
is absolutely clear
that the aftermath of warfare
is a danger point for
anti-democratic violence,
for racist violence,
for activity among Klan
and white power groups.
There's no question
that this is the case.
All of us, men, women, people
who have served or not,
old people, children,
everyone becomes more violent
in the aftermath of warfare.
I think that what
we don't know yet
is what happens to that
phenomenon
when we're talking
about a 20-year war.
[dark music]
My career started as a
enlisted soldier.
I was Private Crow,
and then almost a decade later
it ended as Captain Crow.
Over that period, there were
well over 100 combat missions
between Iraq and Afghanistan,
and of course felt like I left
that part of my life behind me.
[Speaker On Megaphone]
We will take that building.
[Speaker] We're gonna
storm the fucking capitol,
fuck you fuckers.
So on January 6th,
I had told all the
members of my staff
not to come in to the office.
I had heard reports of
Boogaloo Boys and Proud Boys
and others filling flights
to come into the Capitol.
[crowd shouting]
I think as a lot of us watched
things unfold on the sixth,
and then have looked at a
lot of the footage since,
we see things
we recognize as veterans.
That's affirmative,
Jesse is [indistinct].
[Narrator] On January 6th,
2021,
US military veterans who had
sworn an oath
to defend the country were at
the vanguard
of a violent attempt to stop
Congress
from certifying the 2020
presidential election.
They were determined to keep
Joe Biden
from becoming president.
You can actually see, if you
look at it,
the militia groups,
you know, the Oath Keepers,
the Three Percenters, the Proud
Boys.
They're organized, they're
behaving tactically.
They understand the dynamics of
a crowd,
and they're maneuvering to
exploit that mass of bodies,
so you see an organized
line of militia members
with shields ready to go,
ready to exploit a breach,
pushing the crowd in certain
directions.
The mob broke through into
the Capitol.
They evacuated leadership,
they evacuated the floor,
but they had forgotten
that there were about
two dozen members
up in the gallery.
[Member] Everybody stay down,
keep down.
The floor of the House was
evacuated,
but there was no safe
evacuation route,
evidently from the the gallery.
[Oath Keeper] There's no
safe place in the United States
for any of these motherfuckers.
Military principle 105,
cave means grave.
And that's when I
realized we were trapped,
there was no way out,
and we would likely have to
make a stand
or fight our way out.
This was one of the most
shocking moments of my life.
I made the decision
to call my wife
and let her know that I love her
and tell the kids
that I love them.
The only time that the US
Capitol had been breached before
was in the war of 1812,
and that was care of the
British King.
[Rioter] Here we are in the
Capitol.
No looking back now,
boys, no looking back.
[Oath Keeper] This is what
we fucking lived up for,
everything we fucking
trained for.
Wow.
This was the kind of
experience that I expected
as a US Marine in Iraq,
but could never even imagine
happening
as a United States
Congressman in Washington, DC.
You know, many people
have seen the pictures.
They had barred the
door to the gallery.
They were banging on that door
and breaking the
glass to that door.
And I've often asked myself,
how did I end up on one side of
that door
and my fellow veterans who
raised their same right hand
and took the same
oath that I took,
how did they end up on the
other side of that door?
[crowd shouting]
[Narrator] Nearly 150
law enforcement officers
were injured in the melee.
Five protestors died,
and another four police officers
later committed suicide.
[Officer] We've lost the line.
Donald Trump
tweeted out a video.
He said, we did
a good fucking job.
[Narrator] Among those charged
in connection with the attack,
a disproportionate number
are US military veterans.
[explosions]
[dark music]
For me now, the Capitol
is almost like walking
around Gettysburg,
or Antietam, or going
to Pearl Harbor.
And my son Michael was killed
in action in Afghanistan
on June 14th, 2008.
And when you join the military,
there's a lot of competing
ideals of why you show up.
And for most of it, there's
a large amount of patriotism.
But you never lose focus
and never lose sight that,
I'm here in this country maybe
to give them a better chance
to experience what
we have in America.
Where it's not perfect.
We are trying to form a more
perfect union every day,
and we want to give that
chance to other people.
My son died doing that in
Afghanistan,
only for us to lose
that sight here.
Veterans who swear that oath
to protect and defend the
Constitution of the
United States
against all enemies,
foreign and domestic,
of all Americans.
They should understand
how dangerous and unpatriotic
this insurrection was.
They were trying to overthrow
democratic election results.
They shouted for the hanging
of our own Vice President.
That's a coup attempt.
Watching the insurrection
happen,
and we're gonna call it that,
because that's what it was.
And watching veterans
participate,
being at the vanguard
of that insurrection,
it just, it's mind boggling.
But I don't have a really
good answer for why,
why veterans would do that.
[gun firing]
Though I was trained to blow
stuff up,
and run with the infantry,
I became this unofficial,
on the ground intelligence
reporter.
On May 15th, 2005,
we got called to
respond to a body
that was found in a trash
dump outside Sadr City.
When we got there, we realized
that it wasn't a body,
it was a bunch of bodies,
and I had never experienced
anything like it.
And now as I was taking photos,
close up photos of these faces
of victims of murder and
torture,
I was looking at their wounds
and looking at
the packaging tape
that was wrapped
around their eyes
and imagining
the terror that they felt.
And every time I snap a picture,
one of those faces freezes.
And the way that
it froze on the screen,
it froze in my head.
But that was just a day of
deployment.
And I had six and a half
months, seven months
left of Iraq to deal with that.
I went in as 11 Bravo to the
army.
I scored fairly high,
so I went to Airborne School,
which was gonna be my
next step of training
for special forces.
And during that time,
I ended up getting injured
really badly.
When I came home,
I had spent my entire adult
life up to that point,
either training for combat or
in combat.
It was hard for me to think of
anything positive in any way,
whether it's for myself or for
my country
or for democracy or for the
world.
I couldn't help but base my
beliefs
and my feelings on my
experiences,
all of which had been
horrifically fucking negative.
When most come out of the
military,
they're coming out to a world
that they no longer understand
anymore.
You really get lost in that life
when you're in the military.
And you know what happens is,
you have the camaraderie, the
friendship,
all the good things that
you have in the military.
And then when you come out,
you kind of have society that's
undisciplined, incapable,
and just downright ugly.
Good evening, I'm Jamie
Yuccas.
A massive police presence
in Portland, Oregon today,
in anticipation of a
violent confrontation.
[muffled speaking]
I'm a proud boy.
I'm president of the
Hellgate Bridge Crew chapter
in New York City.
I'm also an Air Force veteran.
What we're going
through right now
is a war on the US Constitution.
Biggest reason why I joined
the Air Force myself,
it's to give back to my
country, to serve my country.
I think a lot of that kind of
came from my up upbringing.
The family that I grew up in,
very proud to be an American,
very proud of what America
stood for,
what it represented around
the world, very patriotic.
And I think a lot of those
things are what's lost today.
Members of the Proud Boys and
Antifa
fought multiple times.
And Mayor Ted Wheeler just
sent out a statement late today
saying this past weekend quote,
put innocent lives at risk.
[guns firing]
[Narrator] The Proud Boys
were founded
in New York in 2016.
You wanna keep on bucking
a sleeping bear, guess what?
It's gonna rise up and it's
going be 1776
up into this bitch.
[Narrator] And are classified
as an international terrorist
organization by Canada.
We're western chauvinists.
What that essentially means is
that we're
the biggest cheerleaders
for western values,
western culture,
small government, maximum
freedom, maximum liberty,
pro-First Amendment, pro-Second
Amendment,
glorifying the entrepreneur,
venerating the housewife.
We're not militaristic in
any way, shape or form.
The fact of the matter is, you
have good guys in this world,
you have bad guys in this world,
and the only way to
stand up to the bad guys
is to fight them.
[Narrator] They came
to prominence in America
in September, 2020 during
a presidential debate
between Joe Biden and Donald
Trump.
[Moderator] White
supremacists.
And who would you like me to
condemn?
[talking at the same time]
Proud Boys, stand back and
stand by.
When I saw the President
of the United States
telling an extremist violent
organization, stand by,
that was a chilling moment.
That was a chilling
moment for me.
It wasn't any different
than a President of
the United States
telling Al-Qaeda or
telling ISIS, look,
I have a tough election,
stand by.
Let me tell you
what you need to do.
Did we get a lot of notoriety?
Absolutely, of course we did.
But at the very same time,
it's not because we're racists,
it's not because we're white
supremacists.
If we think about
what the militant right
and white power movement
looks like today,
there are many of these groups.
The specifics can change
from group to group,
but the overall
intent is the same.
The common ideology is simple.
We had power,
we should have power.
Power is being
taken away from us,
and by any means necessary,
we can get it back.
Fascist groups, you have
national socialist groups,
you have southern
nationalist groups,
you have all types of groups
with all types of creeds.
But ultimately
we're all being united
because we all believe
in the same thing,
which is ultimately that white
people have a right to exist.
[Simon] And whether
the we is a white, we.
Jews will not replace us.
Whether the we is an
anti-government we,
they're all intertwined.
The more laws they pass,
it's gonna end up the people
versus the government.
Right now, we're being peaceful.
In the future, nobody knows
when that breaking point's
gonna hit.
Should have hit a long
time ago personally for me.
A lot of people think
that, ah, you know,
these are knuckleheads and we
shouldn't worry about them.
Unfortunately, we said the
same thing about the Jihadis,
prior to the events of 9-11.
They live in caves in
Afghanistan.
They don't pose any
threat to the homeland.
But by the time we decided
to go after them, after 9-11,
it was a little bit too late.
[rioters cheering]
I would like to think that
we would draw the attention
of people that are from the
military
with the military background.
And I think it would be true
of like the Three Percenters,
or the Oath Keepers.
The one thread that kind of
combines all of our groups
is the US Constitution,
our respect for it.
[muffled speaking]
And I signed up to defend
this country.
I was essentially joining
the Three Percenters already.
The oath of enlistment
is the exact oath
of a Three Percenter.
I do solemnly swear.
[All] I do solemnly swear.
That I will support and
defend the Constitution.
[All] That I will support
and defend the Constitution.
Of the United States.
[All] Of United States
Against all enemies
[All] Against all enemies.
Foreign and domestic.
[All] Foreign and domestic.
In Atlanta,
I met up with 3% SF,
and some of the
other brothers out there.
And everybody was upset
about the election.
I mean basically we're
looking at a criminal
that has become our
President, illegitimately.
Joe Biden has already harmed
this country.
His son has already
harmed this country.
We know for a fact that that
family is a criminal family.
The situation we're in is
a situation of treason.
The punishment for
treason is death.
In America, you have the
right to be an asshole.
You have the right to have
the most pathetic
views in the world.
I don't have to agree with you,
you don't have to agree with me.
That is a right protected
by the First Amendment.
I think when we talk about
violent extremist groups,
we're talking about
individuals that go beyond
the narrative to violence.
People who are planning to
attack the US government,
because it's an evil empire.
People who are trying to
kill Jews or kill immigrants
or kill black people,
just based on their race
or on their religion.
When you move away
from the narrative,
as ugly as that narrative is,
to carry out violence
based on that narrative,
to recruit individuals
to carry out violence
based on that narrative,
then you are a violent
extremist.
Then you're frankly a terrorist.
[explosion]
[soldier yelling]
We used to talk about IEDs,
improvised explosive devices in
Iraq,
and they were incredibly lethal.
And what we learned as
we tried to stop this,
was that the problem
was not the bomb itself,
the problem, you had
to go left of the boom.
You had to go upstream
to the problem
and look at where the
problem is coming from.
Where's the energy?
January 6th now.
A militia group had stashes
of guns on the outskirts of DC
ready to go on that fateful
day during the insurrection.
That's just one of the
alarming allegations
from the Justice Department
today,
after the feds charged the
leader, Stewart Rhodes,
and several members of
the right wing group,
the Oath Keepers, with
seditious conspiracy.
[Narrator] Stewart Rhodes
is a former army paratrooper
with a law degree from Yale.
In 2009, he founded the Oath
Keepers,
a shadowy organization that
recruited
law enforcement officers,
active duty military and
veterans.
Their mission was to supposedly
defend the US Constitution,
but it quickly devolved
into an armed militia
dedicated to overthrowing
the US government.
The founders told us with
their wisdom
that we must be the militia.
You will not be secure,
you'll not be free without it.
It's time we resurrect that
and become
the militia once again.
[Narrator] There are
thought to be 35,000 members
in the organization,
most of them heavily armed.
And January 6th was not
the first time Rhodes
assembled his forces and
an arsenal of weapons.
[News Reporter] A state of
emergency
in Louisville, Kentucky,
after a grand jury decided not
to indict
three police officers
in the shooting death of
Breonna Taylor.
[muffled Protestor]
[News Reporter]
Late this afternoon,
protestors clashed with police.
Guys, bring it in.
Pay attention, can't talk
and listen at the same time.
You're in a military
operation, behave like it.
Overdrive,
it's gonna be Bravo team.
And the pawn shop's
gonna be Charlie Team.
[Narrator] Following the
killing of Breonna Taylor,
the Oath Keepers
went to Kentucky
alongside local militia groups.
We're here in Louisville to
protect this Shell station,
and also the pawn shop
across the street,
and also a private residence.
We can't predict unpredictable,
you can't predict chaos,
you can't predict stupid.
[ominous music]
[Speaker] Is there gonna be
enough room?
My main message
is you gotta get ready
and prepare yourselves
and your communities
for what we see coming, where
I think it's unavoidable now.
You got too many
brainwashed Americans
who have been brainwashed
by communist professors
and teachers
to hate their own country.
[protestors chanting]
Whose streets? Our streets.
What do we want? Justice!
[protestors chanting]
When do we want it? Now!
What do you do with someone
that hates their own country,
that hates you,
by close extension if you
believe in your country still?
Three, two, one, go.
[ominous music]
[Speaker] Right behind
you, right behind you.
It's almost like you're
in a foreign country
doing a stability operation
against an insurgency.
One of our guys up there
is SF - Special Forces vet,
and we got another one that's
a retired Staff Sergeant, SF.
I'm not surprised that
extremist organizations
try to recruit veterans for
the credibility that we bring,
but also for our commitment.
And that commitment
takes a lot of forms.
Veterans are people
in our society
who in many ways have said,
I will do whatever is necessary
to preserve what I believe in,
to preserve the baseline values
and the baseline existence of
my society
up to and including violence.
Put a scope on them,
take a peek at 'em,
see what they got.
That's same kinda of shit
that they've been doing
their whole career.
Now they're doing it here
inside the United States.
It's kind of a weird feeling.
I have two purple hearts
already and a bronze star.
They said David, the only
way we'll call you back in
is if the shit's
gonna hit the fan.
I came home to visit my
mom in Crestwood, Kentucky.
I was taking a shower,
she come pounding on the
door early in the morning.
She pointed at the
TV about the time
the second airplane hits, 9-11.
Well, three weeks later
I was getting my shots.
Our group was the second
group to enter Afghanistan.
Hell yeah, man.
It's, it's so enticing.
I mean,
God you get to fight again.
You're trained
in certain things.
You can see the battlefield
better.
If you believe the country's
under attack,
you have a certain set of skills
that maybe you were
trained with, that you can,
help the group around you, right?
You're a force multiplier.
The quintessential examples
of a force multiplier
are Special Forces,
Army Green Berets,
these 12 man A teams that
actually go behind enemy lines
and train up to a battalion,
up to 6 or 700 local indigenous
forces on combat skills.
Certainly, I think
that's one of the reasons
why some of these
extremist groups
are recruiting these individuals
very deliberately
into their movements.
They're fucking coming.
We need to get locked and
loaded and ready to go.
Hey guys, everybody
spread out, get eyes open,
get a good perimeter.
When I was 21
and severely damaged
from a war that
I had been lied into
and that my friends
were dying for.
When a guy like Stewart Rhodes
comes along
with a Yale law degree and
they see the eye patch.
They don't know that he
shot himself at a range,
but they assume he's a combat
wounded vet,
and says like, hey,
you can support and
defend the Constitution
in the United States
standing with us.
And just repeats the words
of the the Second Amendment.
That that's all it took for
me to be like, okay, you know,
you've got the pedigree,
you've got the background.
So why should I challenge that?
You know, I have no basis
in experience or
education to challenge it.
[sirens blaring]
The challenge with having
veterans
directly involved is twofold.
The first is that they
bring a certain expertise.
They might bring in
organizational
skills or military skills
that can make a movement more
dangerous.
All right,
form up and let's go.
The second thing that's
disturbing however,
is particularly in our society,
veterans have legitimacy.
They have a particular
place of respect.
And when we see veterans
involved in something,
it gives some component of
legitimacy to that cause.
Our command's been trying
to tell us to inform you that
you are breaking
curfew right now.
Yes sir.
So if you could just
go back to your post
not not by us, just by we
will have to enforce curfew.
- Ten-four.
- Appreciate it.
Copy that.
Thank you so much.
Veterans have a kind of
social cachet
that provides cover for a
lot of the extremist activity
that these groups
are trying to do.
So if you turn out to a protest
with a bunch of people in
uniform,
much like if you turn out
with a bunch of women,
you have a different
kind of reception
than if you turn
out wearing say,
swastikas and hoods and robes.
So when we think about this,
this is along the lines of
something like
choosing to come out in
polo shirts and khakis,
or choosing to come out
in funny Hawaiian shirts
as part of Boogaloo.
Those are deliberate
decisions that are made
to create the opportunity
for public reception.
And the use of veterans
is one way to do this,
among several.
I've not been a part of
any militia beforehand,
but once they opened up and said
that they were
doing all this BLM,
and I've seen my city on fire,
I was just like,
I've had enough.
And so I reached out to
my local militia
and I've been
with them ever since.
Yeah, straight back.
When you're vulnerable and
you're looking for family,
'cause that's what the
people you serve with are,
they look like they could be
family.
They look like they can provide
you that sense of purpose,
that mission, that camaraderie,
that you had in the military,
that you became dependent on,
that became the center of your
identity.
They could give that back to
you.
And when he tells you to
fight,
you have no reason to question
that,
because he's giving you purpose
and he's giving you mission.
Yeah, yeah.
We got our people across
the country making plans,
but there's too many of us.
There's too many veterans,
first of all,
too many freaking military
veterans.
That's one thing.
I'm not a big fan of the War on
Terror
what it did to a lot of our
rights.
But one thing it did give
us is a massive pool,
huge pool of combat veterans,
and about 95% of them are
on the conservative side
or are on the side of the
constitution.
So it's not gonna play out very
well.
[crowd shouting]
And so when I look at January
6th,
of course there were
people who did violence
and climbed gates and caused
trouble.
But in my view, they were
likely the foot soldiers.
They were the result of the
efforts of other people.
There's the man behind the
curtain pushing everybody out.
You know these are the
half-cocked plans,
the guys who go early.
The people you really have to
worry about
are the people you don't even
know exist
until you're two years into the
conflict,
'cause they're
tactically patient and
they're watching you.
[Rioter] Oh my god.
And I still am
absolutely stunned
that people don't see how
awful January 6th was,
and what an indicator that
is and how it's escalating.
And anybody who says that this
can't happen in a worse way,
either they're ignorant or
they're part of the problem.
Overran the capitol.
We're in the fucking capitol, bro.
People shouldn't look
at the insurrection
at the capitol as an anomaly.
We should pay attention to
the pattern that got us there.
[muffled speaking]
[Klansman] In the name of
Jesus Christ,
we light this cross, and
as light dispels darkness,
so may his word and his example
dispel the heathen
from our midst.
Amen.
[All] Amen. Amen.
[Klansman] By this
sign, you will conquer.
White victory.
[All] White victory.
[Klansman] White power.
[All] White power.
[Klansman] We will fight.
[All] We will fight.
There is one American example
of an extraordinarily
successful terrorist movement,
and that is of course
the Ku Klux Klan.
Many people in the Klan
talked about their experience
as a continuation of warfare.
The first wave came
after the Civil War,
and here we saw
prominent veterans
like Nathan Bedford Forrest,
who rose to leadership
of that Klan.
And although it started as a
veteran's social organization,
it very quickly pivoted
to extralegal violence
targeted at African Americans,
which included night writings,
lynchings,
serial rape, serial murder.
All of these things were
designed to create terror
in African American communities
to control labor pools,
to control local politics
and to keep African
Americans from the polls.
One of the main parts
of the Jim Crow era
was something that we would
think of today
as election subversion.
And we would see in states like
Georgia,
where they refused to
seat 33 state legislators.
We saw in states like Louisiana
where they refused to seat
a duly elected
United States Senator,
in North Carolina
where they held a coup
to overthrow black
leadership in Wilmington.
[Narrator] And in Mississippi
when winning elections
by fraud and violence became
increasingly difficult,
white politicians turned
to the state constitution.
In 1890, Solomon Calhoon,
the conventions president
gave delegates
their marching orders.
"We came here
to exclude the Negro.
Nothing short of
this will answer."
The poll tax and literacy tests
that were written into
Mississippi law
were so effective at
keeping blacks from voting,
that Calhoon's strategy became
a model
for the rest of the South,
staying in place for
almost another century.
The Klan managed to keep
African Americans from voting
for 100 years.
That is an astonishing
political success.
And it happened because the
Klan was politically powerful,
really well connected, largely
in the Democratic party,
not just in the South.
And was able to establish
itself as a counter power
that would stop the
emergence of new voters,
whether those voters were
blacks or indeed Catholics,
who they didn't see as
genuinely American.
[Narrator] The next and most
politically effective wave
of KKK activity came after
World War I.
[trumpet music]
The second Klan that emerges
after Birth of a Nation,
a movie that really changes
the perception of the Klan,
that Woodrow Wilson as President
screens in the White House,
allows a new media savvy
extremist movement to emerge.
And this is when you really
saw the group take off,
not just in the South but
nationwide.
This is the clan that reached a
membership
of some 4 million people and
10% of the state of Indiana.
They were parading in public
on the National Mall in
Washington, DC.
And the founder of that
organization
had been a veteran of
the Spanish-American War.
It comes to a head in 1924.
The Democratic Party has a
convention
at Madison Square Garden,
and the Ku Klux Klan decides
that it's going to stop
the Democratic Party from
condemning Klan violence.
And they pretty much take over
the party,
and make sure that it is
running on their agenda.
Now, if you want
the optimistic story,
four years later the
Democratic party changes.
If you want the pessimistic
story,
a major political party
gets co-opted and taken over
by a violent insurrectionist
terrorist movement.
[Narrator] The KKK's grip
on the Democratic Party
soon ended, but nearly 100
years later
attempts to subvert free
and fair elections have not.
[Caller] You rigged my
fucking election,
you fucking piece of shit.
We're gonna try you and
we're gonna hang you.
We're talking about 50
and 60 year old ladies
that are just,
that've just been working
elections their whole life,
or respected leaders on both
sides that are being inundated
with some of
the worst types of threats
that you can imagine.
[News Reporter] You and your
family
will be killed very slowly.
The death threats came by
text to Tricia Rothenberger,
wife of Georgia
Secretary of State,
as Trump attacked him
incessantly
for standing by the
election results in Georgia.
He's an enemy of the people.
Intimidation is a form
of voter suppression,
and goes hand in hand
with election subversion,
both in our history and today.
They're trying to rig an
election
and we can't let that happen.
I hope you're all gonna be poll
watchers.
Morning, here to vote?
The entire poll watching
program
for the Trump campaign,
was called Army for Trump.
We need every able-bodied
man, woman,
to join Army for Trump's
election security operation.
The underlying narrative,
the messages that were pushed
were one of,
we need to go protect
and stop fraud
from coming into our elections.
It was a very militaristic
campaign.
[Narrator] To increase its
operational effectiveness,
Trump's army enlisted
groups like True the Vote,
which had many veterans within
its ranks.
As a veteran,
we're sworn to support and
defend the constitution.
My brothers and I were
willing to shed our blood
on the battlefield
to protect the beliefs of the
Iraqi people
so they can vote.
So I'm asking you as Americans
to take involvement
in this vote.
The idea that military
service entitles you
to talk about protecting the
constitution is a real problem,
because it gives a level of
justification
these groups do not deserve
and have not earned.
If you have any information
about
ballot harvesting in your
state, go to True the Vote.
It's called truethevote.org.
And I'm sure a lot of people
in this audience saw plenty.
If there's always this
underlying belief
that people are trying to game
this system in an unfair way,
then regardless of the
intent of the people
that are brought into that
system,
that default will always be
there, to police that vote.
And we know that that's going
to have
a disproportionate impact
on communities of color.
[Texas GOP Official] We're
trying to build an army here
that will have the
confidence and courage
to come down in here
in these areas
where we really
need poll workers.
'Cause this is where
the fraud is occurring.
You know, those areas
that he was pointing out.
There are no allegations
of any sort of voter fraud
or shenanigans taking
place there in 2020 at all.
The only thing that's known
is that black and brown people
vote heavily in those areas.
[Narrator] Harris County,
like the rest of
the United States,
has seen its percentage of
white residents
decrease dramatically.
50 years ago, white Americans
made up
more than 80% of the US
population.
By 2044 they will be in the
minority.
The demographic change
of the United States
away from being a white
majority country
towards a multiracial nation
and a multicultural nation
is what moves it from simply,
aha, my community is becoming
multiracial
and our politics will
change because of this,
to we have to stop this
because if people can vote
and exercise their rights,
the white majority will be
imperiled.
And everywhere I turn,
I have been hearing from my
constituents,
they are deeply worried.
They know their history.
They are witnessing what is
happening
to our democracy in real time.
[Narrator] In the aftermath
of the 2020 election,
Republican legislatures in
Georgia and 18 other states
passed a slew of laws
that limited access to the
ballot box.
But what is even more
disconcerting
is that these politicians
in the state legislature
have already laid the tracks
to take over local
boards of elections.
Control the count.
We can get to the same place
through bureaucratic
violence, as some would say,
as we can get to through actual
violence and intimidation.
And when you marry those two,
then you are in a unique
era of suppression
and anti-democratic efforts.
[muffled speaking]
Heavenly Father, we thank you
for this wonderful
gathering of people
that's come this
afternoon, Lord,
to celebrate this
grassroot campaign
of keeping America great.
We know that
there's groups today
that have brought havoc to our
great cities across America.
This militant Marxist groups,
Lord,
that would destroy us
from being a greatness.
I pray against them.
Holy Spirit in Jesus name.
And everybody said
a big old Amen.
[All] Amen.
You joyful warriors
and patriots have watched
as your tyrannical
governments have separated you
from your churches,
from your schools,
from your prosperity, right,
from your families,
from your businesses.
But now you can fight back,
'cause that's what we do.
We fight back.
[audience applauding]
[person yelling]
How many veterans
I got in here?
Let me hear you shout.
[audience shouting]
They're trying to make
us a socialist country.
Maybe they're trying to
make us a communist country.
I am deadly serious.
The next three years
is gonna determine
whether we remain
a free country.
That's why, all over America,
we need people like Eric,
particularly in the Senate.
[audience cheering]
Mayor Giuliani's never
stopped fighting.
He's still on the front lines.
And the day after the election,
he said, you know what?
We got some serious
irregularities here.
We need to look into this fraud.
And what did you hear
from the mainstream media
over and over again?
They said,
oh, that's just crazy.
You can't do that.
You can't say that there's
any fraud in the election.
Well, I'm proud to tell you
I'm the only person in this race
from Missouri who went
down to the front lines
in Arizona myself,
to look at the election audit,
and they need to audit the
whole election.
They need to audit the whole
election.
[Narrator] Eric Greitens
is a highly decorated
former Navy Seal
and a Rhodes Scholar.
He grew up as a Democrat and
after leaving the service,
wrote several bestselling
books about humanitarianism.
"Strength and Compassion" is
a book
of photographs and essays from
eight different countries,
where I did international
humanitarian work
and documentary photography.
[Narrator] He also co-founded
the influential veteran
nonprofit,
The Mission Continues.
While everybody's home
sleeping,
we're out here working.
The mission continues, baby.
Our belief that The Mission
Continues
was that every single
veteran who was coming home
was an asset and that
they could all live lives
of purpose and dignity
and meaning here at home.
[Narrator] In 2015, he became
the Republican governor of
Missouri,
but resigned less
than two years later
in the wake of a sex
and fundraising scandal.
In 2021, he began his
campaign for the US Senate.
When I took the oath to serve
in the United States military,
I took an oath to
defend the constitution
against all enemies,
foreign and domestic.
And domestic.
[audience applauding]
And folks, let's be clear,
we have a fight on our
hands for this country.
And we are here to let
the mainstream media know,
and let the left know, and
the establishment know,
and let the RINOs know,
that we are going to win, and
we're taking back our country.
[audience applauding and
cheering]
This is our country and
we're taking it back.
[audience applauding and
cheering]
There's a cadre of Iraq
and Afghanistan era veterans
who were trained in elite
military units,
who went to elite schools.
A Plus, we're with you all
the way.
Who know better.
And over the last few years
have seen Trump's rise to power,
and rather than
be disgusted by it,
because it goes against
all of our values,
they don't live by those values.
[Charlie] And you went from
high school to the Marines?
Yeah, the great thing
about the Marine Corps
is that they really
force you to shape up.
I like to describe it as a
four-year character education,
because they teach you not
just how to iron a uniform,
but they teach you about
financial management.
They teach you
how to make your bed.
a lot of the skillsets
that you need to be a
successful adult.
[Narrator] JD Vance is a
former Marine.
Like Stewart Rhodes, he
graduated from Yale Law School.
And like Eric Greitens,
he's a best-selling author
who was once a darling
of the New York Times.
[Interviewer]
Are there commonalities
between poor whites,
poor blacks, poor Latinos?
Absolutely, there are
things that are shared
across different groups.
And I think that we should
take some inspiration from it,
some recognition that we are
sort of in this together.
[Narrator] In 2016, he
called Donald Trump an idiot.
I'm a never Trump guy.
I never liked him.
[Narrator] And suggested
that he could be
an American Hitler.
But four years later,
he changed his tune when
he launched his campaign
for Ohio's senate seat.
I wasn't always nice,
but the simple fact is
he's the best president
of my lifetime.
And he revealed the
corruption in this country
like nobody else.
JD Vance a few years ago,
I think a lot of people
across the political spectrum
had a lot of respect for him.
But now we see him
pretending to be an idiot.
Are you a racist?
Do you hate Mexicans?
I think it's ridiculous that
we're focused
on this border in Ukraine.
I gotta be honest with you,
I don't really care what happens
to Ukraine one way or another.
A guy like Eric Greitens
or a guy like JD Vance,
they didn't internalize any of
the morals
that are supposed
to be instilled in us
during our training.
Things like valor and
honor and respect.
[guns firing]
They understand
when they're lying.
They understand when
they're fueling hatred.
I say it all the time, right?
I think the election
was stolen from Trump.
And technology
companies would not let us
talk about the fact
that Joe Biden
is the leader of the world's
biggest crime family.
And they recognize
that they need to do it
in order to achieve power.
Part of the problem for
the young veteran too,
is that some of these
manipulative voices
are former high ranking
military leaders.
General Michael Flynn.
[crowd cheering]
So when you hear somebody
who held sway over you
when you were in uniform,
and now they're out
and they're still
commanding that respect,
that has just such a strong
purpose.
Trump won.
He won.
[crowd cheering]
He won the popular vote,
he won the popular vote,
and he won the electoral
college vote.
Ah, you know,
Flynn's a character.
He's something special.
It comes a little bit
from the comradery
of being a military person.
I can look at Flynn and I can
see that
he's got some really, really
deep love for this country
and respect for it.
And he does respect his oath.
I am not a
conspiracy theorist.
I base my life on facts and
judgment,
and what I believe is
right for this country,
for this country, period.
Flynn has been exposing
truth left and right,
and that's what makes
him one of the most
dangerous men in America.
[Narrator]
Michael Flynn is a retired
US Army three star general.
His specialty was
military intelligence.
Is it trusted?
The intelligence
community wants to
validate the sources of
information that we have
in order to ensure that it's
believable, reliable, relevant.
[Narrator] And the teams he
led were notoriously effective
in rooting out insurgencies
in Iraq and Afghanistan
for over a decade.
In 2012, he was nominated
by Barack Obama
to be the Director of the
Defense Intelligence Agency.
Mike Flynn brings
to this position
decades of experience in
military intelligence.
His knowledge of the
21st century battlefield
is unsurpassed.
[audience applauding]
[Narrator]
But three years later,
the one-time
Democrat had become
an avid supporter
of candidate Trump.
Lock her up, that's right.
Yeah, that's right,
lock her up.
[Narrator]
And would soon become
President Trump's
National Security Advisor.
But just 22 days into his term,
Trump fired him for lying
about his interactions
with Russia.
The evolving and eroding
level of trust
as a result of this situation,
is what led the President
to ask for General Flynn's
resignation.
[Narrator] And General Flynn
would soon
enter a plea deal with the FBI.
His prison sentence was under
review when Trump pardoned him
in December, 2020, less than
a month before leaving office.
Mike Flynn and I served
together for many years,
and were very close friends.
I disagree with him politically.
I am disappointed
by the nature of the
comments that he makes,
the calls to action.
This is one of our top
quality guns.
[all laughing]
Disgraced former General
Michael Flynn, convicted felon.
He uses General like
it's his first name.
I'm his Facebook friend.
His Facebook name is Gen Flynn.
On Telegram, he's General Flynn.
He's using his rank as
part of his identity.
And he has adopted the
radical fascist politics
of MAGA and of QAnon.
Where we go one, we go all.
God bless America.
To build himself up as
a leader for an insurgency
against the people of the
United States.
This country is awake.
This is soil that we have
fought over
and we will fight for in the
future.
He could take military
capabilities
and he could place 'em
in those states,
and basically rerun an election
in each of those states.
Clearly his military
experience
influences some people
to give him legitimacy that
he might not otherwise have.
No reason,
I mean it should happen,
No reason, that's right.
[Narrator]
Flynn's apparent endorsement
of a military coup
is not the only time
the former military
intelligence officer
has planted ideas about the
illegitimacy
of the federal government
and its partners in crime.
Well he doesn't need any
introduction
on this Friday,
January 28th broadcast.
He's General Flynn and of
course a embattled individual
in the fight for this republic.
All these global
organizations,
they see themselves as,
this is how we can control
societies.
This is how we can control
humanity.
So let's introduce something
called COVID.
And they did it and they did
it for a couple of reasons.
One of the big reasons was
was to steal an election.
They have an intent to
have a new world order.
They have an intent to track
every single one of us.
And they use it under the skin.
They use a means by which
it's under the skin.
Dr. Fauci would be right
in there in the same room
with people like Dr. Mengele
and Dr. Zell,
who worked for the
Nazis at the time of
all of Hitler's experimentation
on human beings.
The reality is, as you
learn the ability to lead,
whether it's military or not,
you learn the ability to
get people to do stuff.
And that's just
what he's doing.
We are in a crucible
moment in the history
of the United States of America.
We're fighting with faith,
we're fighting with courage,
and nothing can resist
the power of prayer.
He perverts this military
experience,
this religious experience
to evoke this kind of
feeling of a higher purpose.
The oppression that they
have used with this virus
is an abomination to freedom.
There is no righteousness
on their side.
The Lord is not on their
side, he is on ours.
[Audience Member] That's
right.
We will not go silently
in to the night.
We will fight.
We are making our lists and
we are checking them twice.
And we are finding out
who is the enemy of America.
People that are creating the
oppression in this country,
the people that are involved
with tearing down our freedoms,
our liberties and the value
of what we hold dear in this
country
need to be placed on lists.
People like Dr. Fauci that have
constantly
in his life caused death,
destruction, illness, and
horrible things.
They have to be put on these
lists.
They have to be put out of
our society all together
and never be trusted again.
Now, if someone ends up
attacking these people
that have been found to be
an enemy of the United States
and they're criminals, I'm not
gonna shed a tear about it.
Come here.
Good boy.
When I left the military,
I was a hardcore Republican.
I was libertarian like a lot
of people in the military.
I was looking at like, I can't
even call 'em documentaries.
But these YouTube videos
like this movie, "Zeitgeist."
You had better wake up and
understand
that there are people
who are guiding your life
and you don't even know it.
Now that I study extremism,
I recognize it's filled
with anti-Semitic tropes.
The theme of the movie
without explicitly saying it,
is that Jewish people are out
there controlling the banks
and the banks are the
reasons why we go into wars.
So therefore the Jews
are responsible for
my friends dying.
That's the connection
that it's trying to make.
[Rockefeller] The ultimate
goal is to get everybody
in this world chipped with an
RFID chip.
And have all money
be on those chips
and everything
on those chips.
And if anybody wants
to protest what we do,
or violate what we want,
we just turn off their chip.
I just absorbed this
propaganda and fell for it,
fell into it.
And I was watching Alex Jones
before anyone knew what his
name was.
I mean now they're openly
bragging
it's world government and they
run it.
[Kristofer]
Tucker Carlson when
he was back on MSNBC
and Glenn Beck.
It's all connected.
These people down
here are radicals.
And all of these concepts
started to fit together
and feed this narrative,
this idea that I had felt
but couldn't put
words to for so long,
that I was the victim,
not just of circumstance,
but of some sort of nefarious
group of powerful individuals
who were manipulating all
of us and that everyone
was just acting as puppets.
You know what people
now call the deep state,
but we were awake.
And it was our job to
wake everybody else up.
Who's a patriot?
Video.
[rock music]
[Speaker] Ladies and
gentlemen,
prepare for the storm
[indistinct].
Yep that's.
[Speaker] Come on, come on.
There was a lot there.
They flashed photos of the
pyramid on our dollar bills.
They showed a picture of George
Soros.
They talked about the World
Bank.
Everything's incorporated.
These are all things
that I didn't understand
when I was watching
my propaganda videos
back in 2007, 2008.
But man, I mean,
it's like they just took
notes off of the shit
that had me all confused
and crazy back then.
And the second
thing was my family.
These groups have always
operated on a playbook
of using the prevailing social
context to mobilize people,
recruit and radicalize.
The 20s Klan was
anti-Black and anti-Jewish,
but it was also anti-Mexican
near the border,
anti-labor in the Pacific
northwest,
anti-immigrant in the northeast
where there were a lot of
immigrants.
What it did was figure out
what the prevailing social
tensions were
in a given community,
and use those to recruit
people for its own purposes.
[explosion]
[Narrator]
The prevailing feeling
among a host of veterans
returning from Vietnam,
was that they had been
stabbed in the back
by an ungrateful society,
their own feckless government,
and the media elite.
Well it seems now
more certain than ever,
that the bloody experience of
Vietnam
is to end in a stalemate.
[Narrator] It made them ripe
recruits
for a new, conspiracy-fueled
wave of violent extremism
aimed at rooting
out the enemy within.
The Cubans are coming
in by the thousands.
The Mexicans are coming
in by the millions.
The the Haitians are
coming in from Haiti
or wherever that little
nigger country is,
coming in by the hundreds of
thousands.
White people have had enough.
They can no longer
even afford to buy
proper housing for themselves,
yet our government would have
us spend
thousands and thousands
of millions of dollars
on non-whites.
They've had enough.
One of the key figures
in the white power movement
after the Vietnam War,
and one of the architects of
its move
to cell style terrorism,
to using the early internet
and to a number of
other major changes
that fueled its rise is a
veteran named, Louis Beam.
The only thing that's
important tonight,
is will America be white
100 years from tonight?
And if so,
will you commit yourself to
the battle to make it so?
[Narrator] Louis Beam
served two tours in Vietnam
as a helicopter gunner,
and came home in 1968 with
multiple medals
for bravery in combat.
Says that I used great
professional skill and courage
in the face of great personal
danger.
That hasn't changed at all in
my opinion.
Presently, I'm having to use
utmost skill,
and I think it does take courage
to do what I'm doing,
and I'm doing it in the face of
the enemy.
This time the enemy goes
under a different name.
[Narrator] Beam took the
skills he honed in the military
and brought them to the KKK,
where he rose to Grand
Dragon of the Texas Knights.
I have been paid by the
government
$300 a month to fight and kill
commies,
or execute 'em, whatever term
you want to use, in Vietnam.
And what is the difference
between Vietnam
and Houston, Texas, but
a few thousand miles?
One of the reasons that Beam
rose so quickly in these
organizations,
is that he told a story
about warfare and trauma
that a lot of other
people were mobilized by,
including people
who didn't serve.
I saw a young man
about 19 years old,
entrapped in a armored
personnel carrier
about 22 miles
northeast of Saigon,
with his legs pinned beneath
the seat
as a result of a rocket
propelled grenade.
And he stayed on the radio,
kept asking for help,
asking us to
come get him.
So his argument was
about the wrongness of war,
the horror of seeing
casualties in the field,
the horror of losing your
fellow soldiers.
But his pivot was,
this is why we should come
back to the United States
and bring that violence home
to everybody who left us there.
Our mission is a
reconnaissance patrol.
We have information that the
enemy
is in the area.
Halt.
The Jews have assumed leadership
of the federal government.
They totally control it, and
they're controlling us thusly.
The government that's
in Washington DC today
does not represent the
interest of the white people.
Therefore, we will
replace them with people
who will represent the ideals
of white western Christian
civilization.
How are we gonna replace
them? By any means necessary.
We want the heads of the
enemies in our to toe sacks.
In Vietnam, they took ears.
We're gonna take heads.
[Narrator] Beam's rhetoric
and military exercises
eventually got the attention of
the FBI.
And in 1983, he left Texas
for Hayden Lake, Idaho,
a haven for white supremacists.
He joined forces with Aryan
nations
and began to command a cell
style terrorist movement
of white power activists.
The idea was that one or a
few white power activists
could work together
towards a commonly held
set of goals and targets,
but without prosecutable
ties between them,
and without direct ties
to movement leadership.
[Narrator] But there was a
problem.
The cells, which were
spread across the country
and into Canada,
still needed to communicate
with each other.
And even when the FBI wasn't
listening on their phones,
Beam wanted to
do more than talk.
He wanted to share ideas
and create networks.
[phone dialing]
So they created a social
network called Liberty Net.
And one of the first postings
was titled,
"On-Line for God and Country."
And then Louis Beam
traveled around the country,
teaching people
how to go online.
These message boards
included assassination lists,
and ideological content and
who you should hate and why.
But they also included
social network content
like personal ads.
And this was in 1984-85,
way before most
people think about
far right online activism.
Decades before Facebook.
[Narrator] Using this
early form of the internet,
Klansman, skinheads, Neo Nazis,
and other extremist groups
banded together to commit a
series of heinous robberies,
bombings, and murders
across the country.
And since we're all racist,
since we're all
the radical right,
and that's a crime in America.
When you have to do the
time, don't regret the crime.
We'll be at the forefront of
the fight.
[Interviewer] Doing what?
Hopefully smashing
the skulls of communists
or executing race traitors
or shooting on sight anybody
we don't think is white.
We have to get our government
back.
That's what it's all about.
All these so-called
subversive groups
are nothing but patriotic
citizens trying to do just that.
[Narrator] By 1985,
the Department of Justice
came to believe that the
network of white power cells
behind these crimes
represented a serious
threat to national security.
Louis Beam has been charged
with Seditious Conspiracy,
along with 13 other individuals.
What else is a country boy
gonna do on Saturday night
when the only drugstore in
town's closed?
[Narrator] But the trial
was a disaster for the
government.
A stunning verdict this
afternoon,
the trial of 13 white
supremacists.
Among charges they faced,
conspiracy to overthrow the
government of the United States.
The verdicts from the all
white jury
came on the fourth day of
deliberations.
Beam and his co-defendants
were acquitted on all charges.
The humiliating
outcome led the DOJ
to focus their attention
on individual criminals
and abandon investigations
of the white power movement
as a domestic terrorist threat.
The catastrophic legacy
of leaderless resistance
has been that we as a public
have lost sight of this
movement.
We don't have any domestic
terrorism legislation.
We don't have domestic
terrorism laws.
For example, the number one tool
FBI agents and prosecutors use
to disrupt terrorist
attacks in the United States
is material support.
Material support is
basically a charge to levy
on individuals who are helping
a terrorist organization
or a violent organization.
Unfortunately,
we don't have that
when it comes to domestic
terrorist organizations.
The problem with this situation
is,
when you don't have
domestic terrorism laws,
you need an act to happen.
You need a hot body in order
to start an investigation,
and usually you can
charge that individual
with hate crime or
with other charges,
but you cannot charge
them with terrorism.
You cannot go after
the whole network.
[News Reporter] Holy cow,
about a third of the building
has been blown away,
it's just devastating.
[crowd shouting]
A massive car bomb exploded
outside of a large federal
building
in downtown Oklahoma City,
shattering that building,
killing children,
killing federal employees,
military men and civilians.
Even Timothy McVeigh,
he blew up a
whole federal building,
and prosecutors could not charge
him or his associates with
terrorism.
The bombing of Oklahoma City
in 1995
was the largest deliberate
mass casualty event
on American soil between
Pearl Harbor and 9-11,
but most people
still don't understand
what that event was
and what it meant.
[News Reporter] The
indictment charges
that Timothy McVeigh
and Terry Nichols,
former army buddies with a
grudge against the government,
planned the bombing,
selected the [indistinct].
McVeigh and Nichols met each
other through their service.
They trained together
at Fort Riley, Kansas,
before McVeigh
deployed to the Gulf
as part of Big Red One
Infantry Unit in Iraq.
There he seems to have
experienced some amount
of traumatic combat
before their return home.
After washing out of Special
Forces, he was really angry,
and we see at that moment
his deepening involvement
in radical white power activity.
[guns firing]
Ranging from McVeigh's
connection
to the Michigan militia.
The federal government itself
is the child of the armed
citizen.
We, the people are the parent
of the child we call government.
In short, the federal
government needs a good spanking
to make it behave.
His contact and attempted
contact with groups
like the Arizona Patriots
and the National Alliance,
and his written belief
in white power principles
that were published in
his hometown newspaper.
[Narrator] McVeigh used
his military training
to help carry out the
Oklahoma City bombing.
And in a letter to a friend,
he invoked his military
oath to justify it.
I have sworn to uphold and
defend the constitution
against all enemies, foreign
and domestic, and I will.
Blood will flow in the streets.
Good versus evil.
Free men versus socialist
wannabe slaves.
Pray it's not your blood,
my friend.
The other key component here
was his use of
"The Turner Diaries".
[Narrator] At gun shows,
Timothy McVeigh
would hand out copies
of "The Turner Diaries",
a dystopian novel that details
how to topple the US government.
The fictional
revolutionaries start
by blowing up a federal
building,
and then proceed to exterminate
their political enemies,
including all
Jews, Blacks, and Latinos.
"The Turner Diaries"
became enormously important
to this movement, not
because it's a good book,
but because it provides
the imaginative answer
to a really important question,
which is how can a tiny group
of people,
a small fringe movement,
do what they're setting
out to do in this period,
which is to overthrow the
most militarized superstate
in world history.
[Narrator] In 1997,
McVeigh was convicted
of murdering 168 people,
using a weapon of mass
destruction,
and blowing up a federal
building.
No domestic terrorism charges
were brought, however,
because he and Nichols were
thought to have acted alone.
Just imagine if Timothy
McVeigh's name was Mohamed.
We will look at
that terrorism threat
in a very different lens.
First of all,
we will look at it as a
terrorist threat.
We will go after McVeigh.
We will go after all the
people who are helping him
and who are assisting him.
We will keep
the investigation going
in order to get
the whole network.
When you are very limited
with the tools you are using,
these groups will
take benefits from it.
These are not lone wolves.
These are people who
are united by ideology,
by social ties,
by selection of targets.
These are all part
of the same movement,
and this is really
what we're seeing
continuing into
our present day moment.
[dark music]
Tonight, the plot to kidnap
a governor foiled by the FBI.
[Narrator] In October, 2020,
less than a month before
the presidential election,
14 men were arrested in a plot
to kidnap
Michigan Governor Gretchen
Whitmer,
their plans included
storming the state capitol,
using zip ties to take hostages,
and conducting a trial
that would result
in a public hanging
of the governor.
The suspects were all members
of the Wolverine Watchmen,
a paramilitary group
commanded by a former Marine
that had ties to the Michigan
militia.
Prosecutors contend that
they wanted to kidnap her
to try to ignite another
American Civil War
before the 2020 election,
in hopes of disrupting it
and perhaps keeping Joe Biden
from becoming president.
[Narrator] But federal
prosecutors could not charge
any of the conspirators
with material support.
And despite having a mountain
of evidence
laid out against them at trial.
[News Reporter] The
group's leader, Adam Fox,
telling the informant he was
inspired
by Oklahoma City bombing
terrorist, Timothy McVeigh,
telling the informant, if
we can't have our world,
they can't have theirs.
Burning it down.
[Narrator] Like Louis Beam
before them.
If we can't have this
country, nobody gets it.
Is that clear?
There's gonna be total ashes
everywhere.
[Narrator] None of the
defendants
were convicted
on federal charges.
The goals of this insurgency
in Michigan
were to take over
the State House,
and then to kidnap and
execute the governor.
The goal of the insurgency
on January 6th
was to overturn the results
of a democratic election.
So if we see this
as part of a movement,
it's to stop the American people
being able to choose
their own leaders.
An insurgency is all about
seizing control of a government,
not through winning an election,
not through democratic
processes,
not through persuasion,
but through violence.
It's a form of war.
[Crowd] USA, USA, USA.
Fuckin coward traitor bitch!
If you look at January 6th,
what we're looking at
is really the collision
of three different streams of
activity.
One is the organized white
power movement
that is coming off of
decades, if not generations,
of organizing, armament,
training, and ideological
content.
They want to know what
the orange hats stand for.
Fucking Proud Boys.
Another is QAnon, which
is newer, more radical,
works very fast.
Where we go one, we go all.
And the final one, the
biggest one,
is simply the Trump base.
[Crowd] We want Trump, we
want Trump, we want Trump.
We want Trump.
[Stanley] It's clear
to me that what you had
was a concerted effort by a
number of different organizers.
Do you want your house back?
[crowd] Yes.
Take it.
To take these various
groups together
and focus their energies
and to create a critical mass.
And that's not new.
[gun firing]
Allahu Akbar.
[speaking in foreign language]
In Iraq, when Al Qaeda in
Iraq emerged,
it really came led by a guy
named Abu Musab al-Zarqawi.
He traveled around the
country, had a charisma to him,
and he portrayed this,
hey, I'm not your normal
political leader,
and we are going to show
the kind of commitment
that real men would do.
And Al Qaeda in Iraq, which
was very extreme ideologically,
started to be joined by people
who weren't natural bedfellows.
People go, finally,
someone who's not gonna
put up with the crap,
someone who's going to take
the law into their own hands,
and is gonna get
us what we deserve,
because we have been exploited
by the elites of the region.
I think Abu Musab
al-Zarqawi and Donald Trump
both understand that you
can inflame those passions.
It is where the leader
takes those frustrations
that becomes potentially
disastrous.
Grievance narratives
are made up.
They're constructed narratives,
but they are used by
demagogues because they work.
And if you have a political
party
that is organized around
grievance,
around a sense of loss
and a sense of threat,
you have the basis for the
ideology
that will promote violence.
We're gathered together in the
heart of our nation's capital
for one very, very
basic and simple reason,
to save our democracy.
We're gonna walk down to the
capitol.
[crowd cheering]
And we're gonna cheer
on our brave senators
and congressmen and women.
And we're probably not
gonna be cheering so much
for some of them,
because you'll never take back
our country with weakness.
You have to show strength,
and you have to be strong.
[crowd shouting]
DC is a motherfucking war
zone.
Let's go.
This is what we came for, yeah.
[Narrator] The siege of
the capitol on January 6th
did not overturn the results
of the 2020 election,
but that's not the only measure
by which the actions of
that day are being judged.
There's footage of Proud
Boys directing journalists
to read "The Turner Diaries."
Read "The Turner Diaries."
On January 6th,
"The Turner Diaries"
was structuring
a lot of the imaginative,
performative action of that day.
The noose hung outside the
Capitol,
refers to events in "The Turner
Diaries"
called The Day of the Rope,
which is the hanging of race
traitors,
which include politicians.
And significantly,
there is a strike on the capitol
that is not supposed to be
a mass casualty attack.
In "The Turner Diaries",
it's a mortar attack.
It's meant to be simply
the selected killing
of a few corrupt legislators
in order to show other white
people
that extremists can strike at
the heart of American power.
[rioter yelling]
- We did it.
We fucking did it.
Yo, take laptops,
paperwork, take everything.
All that shit.
And by that measure,
I think that they succeeded.
Donald Trump tweeted out a
video.
He said, we did a good fucking
job.
January 6th was a huge
success for them.
January 6th inspired
so many people,
not only here in the United
States, but even in Europe,
that violence is the way
to change the government,
is a way to change the
establishments
in the western world that
they consider corrupt,
they consider evil.
They consider that these
governments are nothing
but tools to the Jews
or to whatever conspiracy they
believe in.
[Speaker] You believe the
rich people in the world
are using this disease and
exaggerating it
to create some sort of
apocalyptic nightmare, right?
You think it's common sense
that we all have to stay inside
and be afraid of the air?
[audience applauding]
[crowd hooting]
You look at January 6th,
I think the people that were
there that participated in it,
number one, they wanted it
to serve as a wake up call
to those people who are in
power.
And the fact of the matter is,
every single person
that was there that day
is a patriot of this nation.
[Speaker] Yo Randy, maybe you
wanna put
the beers inside the fridge.
Maybe you want to get off
your ass and do something.
Being a patriot, being a person
that loves their country,
especially, you know,
being a military veteran,
you take an oath to the
Constitution.
And for a lot of those people
that were there that day,
they felt that their
constitution
was being shredded up.
Our democracy was being shredded
right in front of our eyes.
I think it's absolutely
heartbreaking
to see veterans involved in
these things,
and I know for a lot of
them that their hearts
are in some ways in the right
place,
that we just don't live in the
same world of truth anymore.
The people in DC they
were Americans, yeah,
and they were patriots.
They only broke laws
because the DC police
didn't do their job.
[Interviewer] Okay, okay.
That's it, people died because
they didn't do their job.
So they broke into the capitol
because DC police
didn't do their job.
The DC police.
They didn't break into
anything.
They let 'em in.
Not only did they let them in,
it's paid for by tax dollars.
It's their fucking property.
Sorry.
This is the lethal danger of
the big election lie, right?
This is a conspiracy theory
that says,
the very heart of American
political life,
the very heart of our democracy,
has been destroyed
and taken from us,
which leaves us what recourse?
Do I believe the
election was stolen?
Absolutely, without a doubt.
There's no way in hell
Joe Biden was elected.
81 Million votes for Joe
Biden, I don't think so.
We're in a situation right now
where,
we can't trust our elections
anymore, we know that.
So what really is scary is, is
that what will the people do?
What will the average American
do when they finally wake up
to the reality of all this?
And the answer to that is, we
don't know.
We have no idea what the
American people will do.
This no longer is a
constitutional republic,
and we are going to fight
to bring our constitutional
republic back again.
We've had violent domestic
extremist organizations
for a long time,
but I think what makes this
moment particularly dangerous,
there are a couple of things.
The first one is the fact that
it's able to ride on a wave
of conspiracy thinking,
and general distrust
that's happening because of
social media technologies.
It's happening because of the
way
we've structured our
society on the internet,
that gives them the
sheer numbers of people
that they could never dream
of bringing to bear on their
own.
Everybody's gotta put
their shoulder to the wheel.
We need participation 24/7.
We need you to be a force
multiplier.
As a soldier and as a general,
as a retired general, we have
an army of digital soldiers.
If you can do command and
control over social media,
and you're fighting
against evil,
and you're on the side of God,
and you're on the side of the
United States and your oath,
it's a very attractive
proposition.
The sad part is,
is you're using all those
skills and that goodness
and that purity of heart
that you think is actually
absolute unadulterated bullshit.
The second major difference
is you have political
cover from the very top.
The only way we're
gonna lose this election
is if the election is
rigged, remember that.
January 6th was the
culmination of two months
of a propagation of a big lie,
and of conspiracy theories,
by the president
of the United States.
Two-thirds of house
Republicans go along with Trump
and vote to overturn
the electors
on the evening of January 6th.
We a United States Senator
and members of the
House of Representatives
object to the counting
of the electoral votes
of the state of Pennsylvania.
Madam Speaker, I rise
to support the objection.
Madam Chair, I vigorously
support this objection.
And I ask you.
In a vote that has
always been thought to be
ceremonial and ministerial,
where you accept the
electoral college results,
which were in no serious
way contested.
I mean, that's almost as
astounding
as what happened in terms
of the insurrection.
How can so many people
believe that it was unfair?
It was because their
president said it was unfair.
Their senator said it was
unfair.
Their member of Congress
said it was unfair.
A full audit is absolutely
necessary.
We should get injunctions if
And normally those are people
that the electorate
can have faith in.
I rise for myself and 60
of my colleagues to object
to the counting of the
electoral ballots from Arizona.
Is the objection in writing,
and signed by a senator?
Yes, it is.
It is.
[Narrator] But it is
not just the big lie
that appears to have captured
much of the Republican party.
Congressman Denver Riggleman
lost his party's nomination
over the weekend.
The first term congressman
was ousted
by former Liberty University
employee, Bob Good.
Getting run outta the
Republican party
was really interesting.
I believe I was the first
one that was affected
by Q conspiracy theories
when I didn't even know it.
I had conducted a same sex
wedding in summer of 2019.
Two guys who had worked
for me, or volunteered.
And then I started hearing
these weird things.
I'm funded by George
Soros, I'm a secret Jew,
I'm a secret Dem.
I'm trying to change the
sexual orientation of children.
I'm a tool of the antichrist.
And I'm hearing all this,
I'm like, this sounds like
new world order, crazy stuff.
You know,
the old anti-Semitic tropes.
[Speaker] You had better
wake up and understand that.
Then I started doing my own
research
and I'm pretty good at it.
And I saw some
of the same patterns
that you saw with foreign
terrorists, you know,
and when you chased ISIS
or Al-Qaeda or IED resupply
from Iraq into Iran,
I've seen some things.
And what I saw was that
people were using language
in the open that I thought we
would never see as Americans.
My two decades of intelligence,
war fighting and
counter-terrorism experience,
coupled with serving
in the 116th Congress,
is why I will not allow
conspiracy peddlers
to hijack our ability to conduct
reasonable policy discussions
for the betterment of all
Americans.
I was pretty much
drummed out and censured,
for following the law and
trying to save this country.
And I'm not, I don't think
I'm overstating that.
[Crowd] Stop the steal, stop
the steal, stop the steal.
One of our two parties is
committed to
an Orwellian whitewashing of
history.
If you didn't know the TV
footage
was a video from January the
sixth,
you would actually think it
was a normal tourist visit.
Is committed to propagating
or at least not quarreling
with a big lie.
The big lie, the big
lie is a lot of bullshit,
that's what it is.
[crowd cheering]
Is committed to not
quarreling much
with conspiracy theories,
is committed to purging those
Republicans
at the state and local level
and at the national level
who want to fight back
against the lies
and the conspiracy theories.
That's a big deal.
War is literally the
continuation of politics
by other violent means.
Our military forces are
the part of our society
that carries out that piece.
Then we come home, and the
question is,
do we have a political
system that functions?
Or are we at a point
where our own politics,
the politics inside our own
communities,
country,
can only be continued through
other means?
And we gotta be very careful,
because if you think you have
support
from the highest levels of
government,
why aren't you fighting for
your country?
Aren't you already sort
of sworn in to do this?
The issue is, is that the people
that we are identifying as
extremists,
they're identifying as
patriots or freedom fighters.
And that is,
it almost sounds like I'm
talking
about terrorism right now.
[dark music]
[keyboard clicking]
One of the organizations
that I'm particularly
interested in,
is the Patriot Front.
They're producing what
they refer to as propaganda.
They're studying books on
fascism,
because they believe democracy
has failed,
and their vision for the
future is a dominant white race
that has captured the
Republican party
and has defeated their
political opponents
by violence or by exclusion.
These guys showed up in
Philadelphia
on the 4th of July, 2021 and
assaulted a bunch of people.
Nothing came of it,
'cause
the local cops didn't know
what the hell they
were dealing with.
So this is a fascist gang
who's operating
all around the country.
Police in Idaho say they
prevented
a possible domestic terror
attack over the weekend.
31 men were arrested, all
dressed alike,
allegedly on their way to
wreak havoc at a Pride event
in the city of Coeur d'Alene.
[Narrator] Coeur d'Alene
is just a few miles
north of Hayden Lake,
and the Patriot Front,
following in the footsteps of
Louis Beam
had made it the base of
operations.
And in the same way Denver
Riggleman
had been targeted by QAnon
for officiating a gay wedding,
Q's rhetoric casting the LGBTQ
community
as groomers and pedophiles
helped put them squarely in the
sights
of the white nationalist
Patriot Front.
While the Proud Boys, the
Oath Keepers,
the Three Percenters are a
threat.
The ones that I'm really
afraid of, are the Gen Z ones,
the service members who have
served
during a time of relative peace.
These young people who joined
to fight,
never got a chance to fight,
and who, starting in
conservative
echo chambers online,
have been brought into the
Proud Boy to fascist pipeline.
So Gab is an alternative
social media platform
that was created to be a
safe space for neo-Nazis.
One of the groups on here is
the National Justice Party.
This is a neo-Nazi party
within the United States,
whose goal is to use protests
to radicalize Trump supporters
into explicit white supremacy.
They're developing new
and original propaganda
that paint them in a light of
achieving
the power and the ability
to shape politics,
and engage in violence in a way
that they thought they were
gonna get from the military.
They understand how to recruit
people into that lifestyle.
So right here, this is
in Italian, "mene frego".
"I don't care".
That was the slogan of the
Fascist Party under Mussolini.
So what they're trying to
do is make white nationalism
look like it's a
testosterone-filled way to be a
man.
I believe that these young
veterans who are getting out
and joining things like Patriot
Front
and Nationalist Socialist Club,
and the word Nazi is
nationalist-socialist.
I think that the Republican
Party is
more than capable of
adopting that ideology
in a way that that's
unfathomable even to me.
You know, I never saw
us where we are today.
I think another four years,
things could be far worse.
[dark music]
I think the worst case
scenario
is probably worse than
most of us want to imagine.
I could see a civil war.
Because this is the same
movement
we've been dealing with this
whole time,
it's reasonable to assume
that what we can see
is only about half of the
activity,
that there is an underground
that is mounting violent action,
training in camps,
trying to accumulate weapons
and preparing for violence.
When you talk about civil war
or specific sectors of the
country that could go kinetic,
just go to these areas where
you see
the first big far left protests.
When Republicans take
back the house, boom.
If there's anybody out there
from Antifa or Black Lives
Matters,
spend your first fucking
bullet at my chest, okay?
Or if Republicans think
that one of the state
elections were stolen, boom.
Forget writing your
legislators.
You gotta do something.
It's us, it's we the people.
You're gonna have to take my
life.
There's no way, I'll die on
this hill.
There's no way, no way.
All of this can happen.
Who's to say that if
legislation came down
where we lost our second
amendment tomorrow,
that that wouldn't start a
civil war?
To be honest with you,
I don't know of any veteran
that wants war in this country.
But at the very same time,
when you look back to
what our founding fathers
wanted for this country,
we are so far away
from that today.
It's just something
they're ready for,
and their gun safe is full.
If you're prepared,
you're prepared,
and if you're not, you're not.
If you're armed, then
you're somewhat prepared
to defend your family and
yourself.
If you're not armed,
you're dog meat.
There's imminent civil war.
If we don't fix our elections
and actually make
them bonafide again,
we don't have 2024.
There is no 2024.
[Narrator] But it is
the election of 2024
that opens up a different front,
one that is potentially as
dangerous as a violent civil
war.
There are people in
this movement who believe
that the nation cannot
be saved as it is,
and must be overthrown
in order to make way
for a white ethno-state.
And then there are probably
people in this movement
who think, aha,
there's an opening here to run
for office,
and mount a sort
of coup from inside
in order to change the
very nature of the nation.
Now, I worry about scenarios
in which,
in 2024, one party controls
Congress.
The other party wins a
presidential election.
Congress refuses to certify the
election.
The Republican party has
a pretty systematic plan
to have state legislatures
impose themselves
much more directly into the
certification of electors,
to perhaps also suppress
some democratic votes
along the way.
So I do think the
chances of a real attempt
to overturn a legitimate
election result are not nothing,
and they're not tiny.
And then somebody as president
or people that are elected
that aren't there in a legal
way.
And then that's when the
dissent happens,
and that's the end of our
country and our legal norms.
And that scares
the hell outta me.
This country,
you as individuals
with the individual liberties
and the individual rights that
you have,
you need to start assuming risk
for your neighborhoods and your
communities and your towns.
You have to get involved.
General Flynn's ultimate
plan is to undermine democracy,
is to get his digital soldiers
to radicalize the rest
of the Republican base.
Go run for dog catcher.
If you don't like this, who's
running your school board?
Go run for the school board.
If you don't like who's
running your little town
or your little parish,
go get involved.
If Flynn can convince his
followers
to push enough good
people out of government,
they'll beat us into submission.
I don't want guys like
disgraced former General
Michael Flynn
to be deciding who's an
American and who's not.
General Flynn, do you believe
the violence on January 6th was
justified?
Because their movement
is about excluding others.
It's not about
the will of the people.
It's about suppressing
opposition.
It's about power.
General Flynn, do you believe
in the peaceful transition
of power in the United States
of America?
This is how countries fall
apart.
Part of my experience as a
veteran,
and as somebody who's worked
with refugees
and done human rights work,
I know what happens when
the center cannot hold
and a society falls apart.
I know what happens when
your ethnic identity
or your in-group out-group
membership
becomes a life and death issue,
and when neighbors start killing
each other, I've seen it.
And whatever your Twitter
bravado
about the next civil war is,
nobody wants to see that.
That is the road to hell.
The very worst case scenario
is that we slide to
authoritarianism,
that we are not able
to climb out of this.
We have seen this happen
over and over and over again
in other countries.
We have seen them fight
back against the first wave,
and not be ready for the second,
and not be ready for the third.
This is gonna take a long time,
and it's going to take
everything we have
to make sure that our democracy
is still standing at the end of
it.
I hope that people are
fucking scared,
because being scared motivates
people.
And I want you to be
scared by what's true.
And I want you to look at
evidence.
I want you to think critically,
and do everything within your
power
and within the confines of the
law
to make sure that we don't live
in that dystopian future,
that could just be a few years
away.
I went to my son's grave site,
and I just felt so helpless.
It made me angry that
my son's sacrifice
almost felt like it was in vain.
Now I've refocused and I
had to take a look at it,
and I had to do a lot of soul
searching
to understand that that's not
the case.
And this fight is not over.
It's far from over and
it may never be over.
But his sacrifice is not in
vain.
My service, the service of
everyone
else, of all Americans,
regardless if you wore a uniform
as long as you got up in the
morning,
you just tried to do the right
thing.
It's not in vain.
What if every young American
did national service for a year,
maybe in uniform, but not
necessarily?
What if they did it in
healthcare,
conservation, education,
how would they feel about
each other at the end of that?
By experience we know you
almost always feel different,
more tightly, you break down
many of your preconceived
prejudices against other groups.
Trust starts to build.
In 2013, I first applied to
my local community college.
Having had my military
experience turn out so negative,
I'll be honest, my
confidence was destroyed,
and I was like terrified
of registering for classes,
because I was terrified of
failure.
And I went over the course
of my first semester
at Nassau Community College,
fulfilling a lot of bad
stereotypes about veterans.
You know, coming in,
having my headphones on,
having my hoodie over my head,
and just like sitting down,
not talking to anybody, not
engaging.
And a group of student veterans
at my community college
identified that,
recognized that it was a
problem,
and helped to break me of my
shell.
I went from being that guy
who doesn't talk to anybody
and sits in the corner to
being elected to represent
all of the student veterans at
my school.
Student Veterans of Nassau is a
chapter
of Student Veterans of America.
It's a national organization
focused on basically
easing people into the
transition
from combat to college to
careers.
One of the things that
the Veterans Center does,
is it allows for us to get
back into an environment
that we we're familiar with.
It gives us a sense of
camaraderie
that we really miss from the
military.
It's not something that
happened overnight,
but it set me on the
path towards recovery.
And rather than feel like
the future was predetermined
by these powerful groups,
and that there was nothing that
I could do
to fight against them.
I started to accept the idea of
maybe the truth is
somewhere in the middle.
And because most of my
interactions with the outside
world
were in person, person to
person,
I wasn't as easily able to
seek out an echo chamber
that didn't challenge my
opinions,
that only reinforced my beliefs.
That diversity of opinion
is what kept me from
joining the Oath Keepers
when it first sprang up,
it helped to break me out of it.
A lot of veterans getting out,
they don't have that
opportunity.
We're in a different world.
In this new world,
our troops have to be trained
to not only defend themselves
against a Chinese sniper
or a Russian tank,
but against enemy disinformation
campaigns on the internet.
It's also true that
disinformation
is not just coming from China
and Russia.
We know how to combat
malicious misinformation.
We did a pretty good job
teaching soldiers and citizens
how to not fall for Nazi
propaganda.
We did a pretty good job
teaching soldiers and citizens
how to not fall for communist
propaganda
all through the Cold War.
The problem with that, of
course, is that,
opposition to the Nazis
was a goal shared
by both political parties in
America.
Opposition to the Soviet
Union was a goal shared
by most across the political
spectrum in America.
Right now, this conflict,
it's far too partisan,
it's far too divisive and
it's far too politicized.
We know how to do this,
but it takes unity.
And this is a layer cake of
problems.
This is something that does not
just exist
at say DOD policy level.
This is about how journalists
talk about the movement,
how our laws prosecute the
movement,
how our national leaders direct
their time and attention.
We know that there is
a lack of political will
to establish or to create
a domestic terrorism law.
Yet I think there is a big
possibility
that we can designate these
groups
as international terrorist
organizations.
So what that means, we
can take all the rules,
the laws, the authorities,
that the FBI and other law
enforcement
and intelligence agencies
have to go after them,
the same way we go after
international terrorist
organizations.
Who's paid a price?
Who's paid a price for being
a conspiratorial irresponsible
demagogic extremist?
With the exception of a few
true believers
who were just duped and taken in
and foolishly believed all this
stuff,
most of them are going about
going along, doing fine.
Voters need to decide
whether they are comfortable
with those who incite
violence representing them,
and movements like this end,
when the entire
population decides
that they are unacceptable.
We haven't seen that yet.
[dark music]
So the ideal solution
is de-radicalization,
but that's not something
I'm interested in.
I'm interested in justice,
and I'm interested
in imposing costs
on people who are trying to
hurt America and Americans.
All I think about all
day is finding bad guys
and hoping that
they end up in jail,
documenting any potentially
criminal behavior,
documenting things that
if they're not illegal,
society would frown upon.
And ultimately it's to put a
cost behind
being an insurgent
within the United States.
I'm a Nazi hunter.
But it doesn't mean we're
gonna win,
and that's what I want to tell
people.
Good doesn't always triumph,
but I do believe the oath means
something.
And I know that I'm going
directly against people
who think that they also
are honoring their oath
in the same way.
And that's why I think
this makes this dangerous.
But what's enabling
that schism to happen,
is the lie.
Which world of truth do you
live in?
It's not about commitment
to country, that's shared.
So the only way to get back
together,
the only possibility of
reconciliation
is a conversation that can occur
in an environment of truth.
We can either reconcile with
with each other as a country,
or we can have a conflict.
Where do I want America to go?
Not here, not where we're at.
This path we're on will kill us.
It'll kill this country.
It'll kill freedom,
it'll kill our comradery,
it'll kill our compassion
and our human decency for each
other.
What I'd like to see is for
the people on both sides,
all come together and agree
on going by the truth only.
If we can do that, then
this nation can be salvaged.
Do I see that happening?
No, I don't.
I can hope though.
[dramatic music]
[soft music]