[heart beating]
[woman's muffled screaming]
[rumbling]
[woman panting]
[rumbling continues]
[muffled screams continue]
[muffled indistinct chatter]
[man] ...push.
[high-pitched ringing]
- [woman] He hit his head.
- [man] He did not.
- [woman] Did he hit his head?
- [man] I caught him in time.
[woman] But he hit the floor. I saw him.
- Dropped him.
- [man] I promise you, he's fine.
- [woman] Why isn't he crying?
- [snipping]
- He should be crying, right?
- [man] He will be crying in no time.
[woman] Where are you taking him?
Where are you taking him?
What is...? What is wrong?
Why isn't he breathing?
- Did you kill him?! Did you kill my baby?!
- [man] No!
- [woman] Did you drop him?
- [woman] You made me have him.
- [man] Nurse, are you getting him?
[nurse] Yes, we are. We vacuumed him.
[woman screaming indistinctly]
[woman] Why are you flinging him?
[repeated slapping]
[baby screaming and crying]
[door closes]
[inhales, then exhales]
I accidentally drank mouthwash
Friday night.
You can't get stomach cancer that way.
Not from one time.
I drank a mouthful a couple weeks ago too.
I'm sure it's fine.
[cell phone ringing and buzzing]
[ringing and buzzing continues]
I'm visiting my mother tomorrow.
I know you are. Your father's anniversary.
The day he died.
How you feeling about that?
You know. I never met him.
I meant, how you feeling about going home?
[cell phone chimes]
I had the dream again.
[Friel] Let's stay on track.
How are you feeling about the trip?
It's good I'm going back.
It's been a long time.
Has it?
Several months.
Are you feeling guilty about that?
And, um...
when you're out there,
are you going with any sense of a plan?
Hoping for a certain outcome?
Like what?
Do you feel like you're going
with realistic expectations?
If the last time you were thirsty,
you went to a well
and the water made you sick,
are you gonna go back
to that specific well,
expecting it to be safe?
Mm.
Do you ever wish that she was dead?
What? Of course not.
But it wouldn't be so crazy if you did.
We can sort of want these things
and also not want them at all.
Those feelings can coexist.
We're here so we can air
those kinds of thoughts.
Okay.
How's the Hydrotipnol?
Still making the eyes itchy?
Only if I don't keep blinking.
Is it helping the anxiety?
Um...
Tell you what.
I'm gonna write you a scrip
for a very cool new drug,
which, I think,
should be smoother on all fronts.
Always with water.
Always. And if your breathing changes
or you feel warm, call me immediately.
That's serious.
Break a leg.
- [ethereal music playing]
- [on recording] Hi, Carrot, it's Mom.
I'm just calling to say that I'm so, so,
so excited to see you tomorrow.
- Joseph?
- You're my angel and I love you.
Okay. I love you. Okay, bye, sweetie.
I love you.
Listen to your mother
when I tell you to not leave my sight!
[pop music playing over radio]
Hello. Could I please see this one?
- That one?
- [man yells] You think I won't?
Do you fucking want me to do it?
Oh, yeah?
[crowd clamoring]
Excuse me!
[Beau] Excuse me. What is that man doing?
We're trying to get him to jump. [laughs]
[ethereal music continues]
[Latin music playing over speakers]
[people yelling
and chattering indistinctly]
[man 1] Dumb bitch! Fuck you!
[gunshots]
[man 2] Get away from me.
Get away from me!
You get away from me!
Get away!
You look like a minestrone man.
[man 2] Stay away!
- It's hot!
- [woman] We're running low on crackers.
[intense, ominous rumbling]
[Beau yells]
[lock beeps, then clicks]
[Beau gasping]
[people yelling indistinctly on street]
- [elevator chimes]
- [ethereal music continues]
- [grating metal sound]
- [fluorescent lights buzzing]
[man screaming indistinctly on street]
[beeps]
Hey, Dad.
...search continues for the man known
as "Birthday Boy Stab Man,"
who in the last week
has claimed three more lives.
He is known for prowling
the streets without clothes
and stabbing random pedestrians
in the neck and guts.
Witnesses have identified him
as a circumcised white male...
[indistinct yelling on street]
[music turns pensive, then fades]
- [seagulls squawking]
- [waves susurrating]
- [car horns honking]
- [sirens wailing]
[man yelling indistinctly on street]
[man and woman
yelling indistinctly on street]
[dog barking in distance]
[soft thump]
[ominous music playing]
[footsteps approaching]
Hello?
[pounding on door]
[man] Turn it down! I need to sleep!
[man yelling indistinctly]
[footsteps approaching]
[man] How about this?
[electronic music blaring over speakers]
- [rock music blaring over speakers]
- [alarm beeping]
- [rock music stops]
- [alarm continues beeping]
- [yells]
- [dramatic sting plays]
[tense music playing]
[groans]
[door slams]
Excuse me, sir?
My bag and my key were just here.
You're fucked, pal. [chuckles]
[Beau] Hey, wait a minute.
Why would you say that?
[woman] Hello?
Oh, hi, Mrs. Wolski.
This is Beau Wassermann
from Apartment 303.
- I'm calling because my keys were...
- No solicitors!
No, I'm sorry. I'm not a solicitor,
I'm one of your tenants.
I need a locksmith.
I'm late for the airport.
- Thank you.
- Hello?
Hello.
- [indistinct chatter on street]
- [thudding and clattering]
[men yelling indistinctly]
[siren wails]
[line ringing]
- [Martha] Hello?
- Hi, Martha. I'm sorry, is Mom there?
Beau! Sweetie! Yes, she's right here.
[woman] Beau?
Hi, Mom.
Hi, Carrot. Are you at the airport?
No, not yet.
Are you on your way?
- In the cab? How long is the cab ride?
- No, Mom.
Mom, I don't want to worry you.
I was on my way.
But something... I don't know.
I was up all night
because my neighbor kept leaving notes
underneath my door about noise,
even though I didn't make any noise.
And I overslept and when I went to leave,
I forgot something, I went back in.
And then I came back out
and my key was stolen out of my door.
Oh, my God.
So, where are you calling me from now?
My apartment.
Wait. What time is it? Isn't it 4:30?
Yeah, I know.
Baby, your flight is in an hour!
I know, but, Mom,
my key got stolen out of my door.
Mom?
[sighs]
Okay, sweetheart. I understand.
Wait, what's okay? No, it's not.
What do you understand?
No, of course it isn't.
Your keys are stolen. That's terrible.
They were stolen.
Then we'll just do
another visit another time.
I can even come to you
so it's not such a pain.
It's not a pain.
It's never a pain.
You know what,
I can still just come to you.
I'm still coming, I'm on my way. I just...
What do you think I should do?
I'm sure you'll do the right thing,
sweetheart.
What is the right thing?
What would be the right thing for you?
Do I call the police?
Or maybe there's a way for me
to just still come home now.
But is that safe?
If my apartment's open to the public
and somebody has my keys,
I don't know what's going on.
That doesn't sound safe.
It's not safe, is it?
- Beau...
- What?
Beau.
Yeah?
I'm sorry about your keys. I have to go.
No, you don't have to go.
- I hope you find them.
- Mom.
Wait, wait. Come on, let's fix this.
Let's fix this.
[call disconnects]
Hello?
[engine rumbles and tires screech]
- [man] Yo, you gonna die, bitch!
- [gunshots]
- [woman screams]
- [tires screech]
[people screaming]
[ominous music playing]
- [screaming continues]
- [sirens wailing]
[intense pulsing]
[woman] Who turned the water off?
Turn the fucking water on!
- [retches]
- [tense music playing]
[coughing and retching]
[Latin music playing over speakers]
[tense music continues]
[screaming]
[Friel] Always with water.
Always...
[keyboard clacking]
- [elevator chimes]
- [ominous music playing]
- [man screaming]
- [people yelling indistinctly]
[music intensifying]
- [music intensifying]
- [screaming continues]
[music crescendos]
- [Beau yelps]
- Help me. Help me.
- [gunshot]
Help me. Help me. Help me.
[gasping]
- [screaming continues]
- [pop music playing over radio]
Declined.
What? No, it's not.
Can you try again, please?
[ominous music playing]
Oh, no.
[cashier] No good.
Oh, God. How much?
You drank already. You owe $1.79.
$1.79.
[Beau] Oh, no.
Oh! Oh! Oh!
- I call the police.
- No, no, look, I'm paying! I'm paying!
- [cashier] Thirty cents more.
- [Beau] Oh!
Oh, God.
[cashier] Twenty now.
- [Beau] Oh, my God.
- [cashier] Twenty.
- I know!
- Don't curse me, my friend.
I'm not the one.
- [Beau] Oh, my God.
- [cashier] Five more now.
There!
I call the police!
[tense music playing]
[panting]
Mrs. Wolski?
[man] Stay away from me!
Stay away! You stay away!
- [Beau] Oh, no.
- [man] Get away from me!
- [Beau] Oh!
- [man] Get away!
Get back. Stay away.
Get back!
[tense music playing]
[man yelling indistinctly]
[music turns dramatic]
[lights buzzing]
[sirens wailing]
[men yelling indistinctly]
- [yelling continues]
- [Latin music playing over speakers]
[man] Fuck you! Fuck you!
[dramatic music continues]
[man] Fuck, it's hot.
[ethereal, haunting music playing]
[drill whirring]
[unsettling music playing]
[unsettling music continues]
Hello?
Sir?
[unsettling music continues]
[on recording] Hi, you've reached Mona.
Leave me a message
if you ever wanna speak to me again.
[voicemail beeps]
Hi, Mom.
So, I'm trying
to book a flight for tonight,
but the credit card got declined.
[automated voice] We're sorry.
Your message did not go through.
Please hang up and try again.
[line ringing]
[man] Hello?
Hello?
I'm sorry. Who is this?
Uh... Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm trying to call my Mom.
This is your mom's number?
Oh...
Mm. Yeah, it is.
Who's this?
I'm with UPS.
Um, I don't know whose phone this is.
I just called the police.
They're already on their way.
Oh.
Okay.
Why?
Hello?
Can you maybe describe your mother to me?
Uh...
Brown eyes. Red-brown hair.
Okay.
Can you maybe describe her physique?
Wait, what's going on?
Why are you calling the police?
Listen, I don't know what this is.
I have a package and I only came in
because of the smell and the dogs
on the block were all going crazy,
and the door was open,
so I just barely came inside, but, um...
there's a lady on the floor.
Well, the body of a lady,
and there's no face or head.
What?
[haunting music playing]
I don't think I should've answered this.
The police are coming.
This isn't my phone.
I'm truly just finding this.
I'm sorry, you don't... Makes any sense.
What do you mean,
there's no face or head? For who?
I mean, I'm sure there is.
I'm sure it's here.
I'm sure it's everywhere.
A chandelier...
fell on top of it.
And it looks like it dropped
off the ceiling and it fell on a woman.
And it smashed her head.
Like, it evaporated.
But who is it?
What?
Who is it?
I don't know, I'm trying to be tactful.
You're saying this could be your mom?
What? I didn't say that.
Why are you saying that?
No, you said that to me.
Look, you asked if your mother was here.
That's what I'm saying.
I don't know who this is!
I just picked up the phone
and that's what you said.
I didn't do this!
I didn't do this! You know?
[dog barking over phone]
I swear.
Maybe you called the wrong number.
Did you dial this number?
It's saved in my phone.
It's saved on your phone?
Okay, maybe you misdialed.
Oh, my God.
Right? Maybe you misdialed.
Maybe this is all a big misunderstanding.
- So, we should hang up...
- Okay.
- ...then maybe your mom will pick up.
Okay. Hang up. Call back.
[Beau breathing heavily]
[line ringing]
[man] I'm so sorry.
[haunting music playing]
I'm so sorry.
Do I have your permission
to check her purse for some ID?
Since it's more likely now
that this is your mom?
Hello?
Is her name...
[man clears throat]
Mona Wassermann?
That your mother?
Hello?
- Mona Wassermann, is that your mom?
- [wheezing]
Hey.
Is somebody there?
- [car alarm beeping]
- [woman screaming indistinctly]
[ominous music playing]
[line ringing]
[on recording]
Hi, you've reached Dr. Jeremy Friel.
Please leave a message
and I'll return your call
as soon as I'm able.
I'm so sorry.
[voicemail beeps]
[rubber squeaks]
[man whimpering]
[sobbing]
[man] Please.
Please.
[suspenseful music in crescendo]
[gasps]
[man yelps]
- [man screams]
- [Beau yells]
[intense, unsettling music playing]
[Beau] Help!
[man screaming]
Help! Help!
[yells]
- [Latin music playing over speakers]
- Fuck you! Fuck you! Fuck you!
[yells]
Police! Oh, my God!
Police!
- Police, please help, will you?
- Freeze!
There's a man in my bath
and a man with a knife!
- [officer] Freeze!
- What?
Freeze. Drop the weapon. Drop it!
Drop the weapon! Drop the weapon!
Drop the weapon! Drop it!
Fuck it. What? Do not move.
I fucking said, do not move!
- Freeze!
- I'm freezing. I'm freezing.
- I said, fucking freeze!
- I'm not moving!
- I'm not gonna say it again.
- I'm frozen!
Oh, my God, don't make me do this.
Do not make me do this, please.
Oh, please, please,
please don't make me do this.
No! No! No!
- Don't make me do this!
- [screaming]
[gunshots]
- [intense music playing]
- [Birthday Boy Stab Man cackling]
[yelps]
[yelling]
[water splashing softly]
[screeching indistinctly]
[birds twittering]
[wind chimes tinkling]
[alert chimes]
[woman] I'm coming!
Roger, he's awake!
Did you hit the button?
Are you awake?
How are you feeling?
- [thermometer beeps]
- [mumbling] Strange.
I bet. You've been sleeping for two days.
What?
Did I get hit with a car?
There was an accident, yes.
Oh, goodness. Uh, I hit you with my car.
[Beau groans]
Is that this?
There was a stabbing.
You were assaulted.
What?
- [screaming]
- [intense music playing]
Oh, God! Oh, God! Oh, God!
Why? Why?
- What?
- I know.
- Am I dead?
- No.
No. You've been healing so quickly.
And no organs were hit,
and your bleeding was really mild.
What...? This is a room, this?
This is a room in our house.
But it's your home
for as long as you need.
- My name's Grace.
- [knocking on door]
Oh, this is Roger.
This is my husband.
Hey, guy. Welcome back.
Thought you'd sleep in, huh?
[Grace] Roger's a very respected surgeon.
He's the one who dressed
and treated your wounds.
You're a lucky man.
[monitor beeps]
What is...? What is this?
That's my little assistant health monitor.
Keeps track of your condition.
Was that a dream before?
- What is...?
- Was that a dream?
- The stabbing?
- No, my mom.
- Your...?
- My mommy.
Your mommy?
Is my mommy dead?
What was your dream, sweetie?
[sobs] Her head, it was just gone.
- Her what?
- Her head.
Oh, no, no.
That's a dream. That was a dream.
- No, her head is gone.
- Oh. Shh.
No, no, no. That's a bad dream.
It's okay. Shh. That's a bad dream.
- There you go. Oh, no.
- My mommy.
Just a dream. It's just a dream.
[birds singing]
[poignant music playing]
Amen?
Amen.
That's Nate. Our boy.
Nathan.
He's Army?
Eighty-second Airborne Division. Caracas.
Killed in action.
Where's that?
[Roger]
Oh, is it time for dessert already?
Here you go.
And, uh...
two for the big man.
By the way, Beau. Uh...
Not for the dinner table, but, uh,
I noticed when you first came in...
your testicles
are significantly distended.
- Mm.
- Looks like a bad case of epididymitis.
Let him eat, Roger.
But we should get an ultrasound,
just to be safe.
[Grace] Oh, Toni!
Ton... Come here.
- Come here.
- [Roger] Oh, she's not dead. That's nice.
[Grace] Come in here.
I want you to meet our new friend.
Beau, this is Toni.
Toni, this is Beau.
Oh, hello.
You enjoying my bed and all my stuff?
- What? That's your bedroom?
- [Roger] Oh, God. Here we go.
I didn't realize that. I'm...
Beau, take it easy.
Toni's happy to give you her room.
Yeah, no. It's not like we have
a totally empty room available,
completely unused.
That's right.
It's not like that. You know that.
I'm going to school.
Honey, it's Saturday.
- Don't mix those, Toni!
- [door slams]
Little asshole.
Okay, so you wanna dial nine
and then you're good.
Do you have the number you need?
My mom made me memorize it.
Hi, Jeeves.
Uh, Jeeves, um, he...
Jeeves and my son served together
in Caracas.
He was with him when he died.
[Jeeves yells]
Oh, that's gonna be blood.
- Did you give him his meds?
- I thought you did!
All right.
If you need anything, just shout.
Stay right there, Jeeves.
Sweetie, don't touch anything.
[keypad beeping]
[line ringing]
[man] Hello?
Dr. Cohen?
I'm not a doctor, Beau. I'm an attorney.
I'm calling about Mom.
Is it true?
Is what true?
That she was discovered
with a collapsed head in her living room?
That you were the first person notified
and it's taken three days
for anyone to hear from you?
[sobbing]
Yes, Beau.
It's true.
But how? I was just speaking with her.
I was coming to see her.
- I was coming to see her. What...?
- Shh!
[unsettling music playing]
What...? What happened?
Am I the first person you're asking?
A chandelier crushed her head!
Hello?
Oh, my God.
What do I do?
What...?
Do...?
Do...? Do I call the funeral people?
About what?
Do I need to...?
Everyone was contacted
on the day that she was found.
The burial has been
outrageously postponed.
So...
when...?
When is it now?
A body is to be buried immediately, Beau.
"It shall not remain all night,"
does that ring a bell?
Do you understand anything?
I just woke up.
- I got hit by a car and I got stabbed.
- [Jeeves yells]
[tense music playing]
It was your mother's unfortunate wish
that she not be buried
without you present.
So, we are waiting, Beau.
And every minute more that we wait
only deepens the humiliation.
Okay.
Your mother's body
is being watched at all hours.
There is no rest for her.
There has been no rest
for the people that love her.
You need to be here, Beau,
dressed in a suit, with a eulogy.
You need to stop the humiliation.
It's all that's being asked of you.
We'll keep an eye out
for Your Highness's royal carriage.
[call disconnects]
Was that okay?
[groans]
No, I...
I... I need to get home.
I have to get back. [whimpers]
[Grace] Oh.
Baby.
- [Beau] I have to get back.
- [Roger] Paging Dr. Roge.
Dr. Roge incoming.
- All right, bub. A little medley here.
- [Beau] I just need to go.
- Now, will you take me?
- Under the tongue.
- Come on. Attaboy.
- [Beau] Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God.
How's our patient?
- He needs to get back.
- Oh, I need to go now.
Is there a flight tonight
or this afternoon?
Oh, sweetheart, this is the afternoon.
Okay, well, can we order one or...?
Whoa, partner! Partner, hold your horses.
- He can't fly in his condition.
- Yeah, I was gonna say.
- What's the problem, old buddy?
- She needs to be buried.
They're waiting for me.
[sobbing] She's humiliated.
She's humiliated. Oh, so much.
Beau, listen.
There's nothing worse
than losing a parent.
I lost my mother when I was 11.
I don't think I ever got over it.
But I promise you,
we will get you there, easy.
Wasserton's only like
a six-hour drive from here.
Can you take me now?
But you also need
to get some serious rest, my brother.
- No! I feel fine.
- And some support.
When can you take me?
[ominous music playing]
- Couple of days. Then...
- What?
Then, after the show,
we can all swing back here together.
- Roger, Roger, please.
- As a family.
Please, I need to get back now.
[Grace]
Beau, if you need to get home ASAP,
we're just gonna have to find a way
to take you tomorrow.
[Beau] What?
Tomorrow? Not...? Not...? No.
But today? Why not today?
You're right, honey. Tomorrow.
- [Beau sobs]
- Oh, babers.
Why not today?
[Roger] Not in this condition.
["A Thousand Miles" playing over speakers]
♪ Just making my way ♪
[Grace] One more red and blue.
♪ Through the crowd ♪
Here. I found it.
♪ And I need you
And I miss you... ♪
[Roger] All right.
It's beddy-byes for the Roge-man.
Where's my blushing bride?
Whoo-hoo? Babe?
[ethereal music playing]
Oh, I'm sorry.
I was just going to the bathroom.
Would you like to trade?
I really don't mind.
Shut my door and get in my bed.
I really, really, really don't mind,
really. I like couches.
And I'm leaving tomorrow anyway.
Well, if you do change your mind,
I'm ready to switch whenever.
I'll be happy to.
I'm sorry. Thank you. Sorry.
[couch springs squeak]
[footsteps thumping]
[music turns ominous]
[door slides open]
[inaudible dialogue]
[Toni] Now, where the fuck is it?
He touched it.
Why would you touch someone else's shit?
He moved my toothbrush. He used...
- Did he fucking use my toothbrush?
- Today's the day, Beau. How's it feel?
Is he okay like me?
Eh, probably.
[Grace] It's just his nerves, Beau.
He's been through a lot. Just like you.
Man's a hero.
Okay, pally-o, it's you and me.
Grace, unfortunately, can't join.
She's got her big shareholder meeting.
[chuckles]
You feeling sad about going home, Beau?
[water running]
Must feel totally unreal.
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't know.
Right. So, not sad, exactly.
I mean, yes. Of course, I just...
I think I need to get there to even...
[pop music ringtone playing on cell phone]
Hey, that makes sense.
That makes all the sense in the world.
Hello?
Speaking.
Uh-huh.
When did it happen?
Water skiing?
[groans] Well, yes, no, of course.
Tell them to rush him over.
Oh, my God.
Emergency surgery.
Carl Oberst split his head open.
- [Grace gasps]
- One of my oldest patients.
[Grace] Well, I can't miss work today,
it's all hands on deck.
- [Roger sighs]
- [Grace] Oh, my gosh, Carl.
[Roger] I know. Good old Carl.
Okay. Okay.
Mm.
Mm!
Oh!
[sighs]
Beau...
this is gonna take a while.
I don't know if today's gonna happen.
Okay.
What do you mean?
I wanna say tonight,
but I already pushed
this morning's surgeries to tomorrow.
But if I pull them all back
to this afternoon,
we could blast off tomorrow morning.
No, but I have to go today.
I have to leave today. My mother...
[yells, then groans]
- See?
- [Beau gasps]
- [Roger] Uh-uh.
- [Grace gasps] Oh, Beau.
[Roger] You aren't healed, my dude.
Not to mention...
Maybe there's a way.
Since you're busy, maybe I can...
I can fly.
I fly and I can pay you back
when I get my credit card.
It isn't about the money, Beau.
You can't fly with your wounds.
The air pressure will rip you wide open.
Maybe I can take a bus.
I can take a bus. Can I take a bus?
I could take a train. Or a cab?
Beau, we're responsible for you.
Driving you home
is the absolute least we can do.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
I'm sorry, but I have to go today.
I have to go today.
I don't wanna impose.
Going tomorrow won't be an imposition.
It'll be my pleasure.
Okay?
Okay.
Is it, Beau?
Don't just say that.
This is your decision.
[pensive music drones]
Thanks, pal. You're a trouper.
Sorry for the curveball, Beau.
Wait, don't you need to stitch me up?
Ah, it's fine.
Just cut back on the jumping jacks,
you know what I mean?
In the meantime, my man,
this is your home.
I need to run too, sweetie.
- There's...
- [Roger] Oh!
And I'm giving Jeeves his medicine,
so if you hear him screaming,
he's just asleep.
- Don't forget to hydrate.
- What?
[Grace] Drink lots of water.
[Roger] We're taking you back tomorrow!
[Grace] Goodbye, sweetie.
[Roger] Tomorrow.
What?
What does this mean?
Wait! What does that mean?
[Roger] Shake a leg.
- [ominous music playing]
- [telephone keypad beeping]
[on recording]
You've reached the office of Harold Cohen.
Leave a detailed message.
I'll get back to you as soon as possible.
[voicemail beeps]
Hey, Dr. Cohen. It's Beau.
I'm on my way.
[automated voice] The mailbox is full
and cannot accept any messages...
[keyboard clacking]
[man on video] Our senior correspondent
Brian Galloway joins us now.
Brian, what have we learned?
All we know at the moment
is that Mona Wassermann was found dead
in the living room of her magnificent home
with a chandelier
where one's head should be.
Due to extenuating circumstances,
she has not yet been buried.
But she must. She was 70 years old.
[man]
Excuse me, sir, you discovered the body?
I never would've gone inside
if, uh, the dogs hadn't been going nuts
and I hadn't smelled that smell
and the door hadn't been open.
That's the only reason I went inside.
Admired by her friends
and feared by her competitors,
Mona Wassermann was a local industry titan
and a force to be reckoned with.
I just can't believe it.
[Brian] Mona Wassermann has been...
Wait.
What the fuck?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I was on your computer. I threw up.
I'll clean it up. I'll clean up.
I'll clean it up better than before.
[Toni] We're leaving.
What?
I'm taking you home.
What about Roger taking me?
Who the fuck
do you think told me to take you?
[car alarm chirps]
Meet my new brother.
I'm just Grace and Roger's friend. Hi.
Look at this.
I don't even care.
He just threw up on my fucking computer.
Thank you. Thank you for taking me.
Taking him where?
Aren't you a little old
to be getting adopted?
I'm not adopted.
[Toni] Yeah, you are.
To him.
No, thank you.
[Toni] Dad told me you need to smoke it.
[Beau] What?
[Toni] It's for your healing.
He says you need to relax.
That's okay. Really. Thank you.
I already took some pills.
[Toni] Um, no.
Actually, it's not okay, really,
thank you.
Your new dad says
that your pills aren't enough
and you need to smoke this
with your little sister.
Please. I really can't do this.
I just saw something very confusing
and I just need to get home.
[tires screech]
Look, you smoke it and we take you home.
You don't and we don't. That's it.
Okay.
Then I'll just wait for Roger to take me.
Can you please open the door?
If you don't do it right now,
I'm gonna make her pull my hair so hard
that it detaches my scalp,
and she'll say that you did it.
[Liz] I will.
I remember that you did. I saw it.
You taking advantage of us.
[ominous music playing]
What's in it?
[Toni] It's three things.
Okay, thank you.
[Toni] Do it actually.
Please. That was enough.
[Toni] Harder.
Keep going.
- Don't stop.
- [grunts]
Don't cough. Don't...
[Toni and Liz laughing]
[Toni] Dude.
Oh, my God.
[Toni] I'll take this.
Wait, what...?
- What is that? What...?
- [Toni] What is that?
- All right, can you please open...?
- [Liz] Your brother is fucked.
Can you open the window, please?
[whimpers]
[joint burns]
[Liz] Yeah, bitch. Hit that.
- [Toni exhales]
- [Liz laughs]
[Beau groans]
Oh, my God.
Wait, what is in that?
[Toni] You saw what Sarah posted?
[Liz] Oh, my God.
What a lying, little bitch.
[Toni] Bet she never even met that guy.
[Liz]
You need to raise your price for this.
Can you die from this?
- What? I don't know. Wait. Wait. [whines]
- [unsettling music playing]
- I don't want to...
- [Liz] Dude, I'm still so fucking pissed.
[Toni] Yeah, whatever.
[Liz] This is like the fifth time.
[Toni] It is not the fifth.
It's like the second.
[Liz] I don't care.
Not even a D, a D-plus.
Just give me a fucking C-minus.
- [Toni] It's 'cause he wants you.
- [Liz] He should be fired for wanting me.
[Toni] Oh, my God,
he would totally not survive it.
He's like a thousand years old.
[Toni and Liz laugh]
[Liz] Oh, my God. What if we killed him
by getting him fired?
[Toni and Liz laughing]
[distorted laughter]
[Beau] The car is getting smaller.
Wait, that's the house again.
We just passed your house.
- Hey!
- What?!
What?
[ship horn blows]
- [waves susurrating]
- [seagulls cawing]
[woman] Do you miss Martha, Beau?
Of course. I love Martha.
You love Martha?
She's my friend.
I like her.
Ah, see, Beau?
You're not the only kid here.
[inaudible dialogue]
You know what I've been through.
- You tell me what to do.
- You can't even pay for it.
[shower running]
[girl] There's a dead man in the pool!
There's a dead man in the pool!
[pounding on door]
So, you're just here with your mom?
[Young Beau] Only sometimes.
Right now I'm by myself.
I'm Elaine.
I'm Beau.
[Young Beau]
Are you here with your mother?
[Elaine] Yeah.
She got me, and my dad
got our rich whore neighbor,
who he's probably fucking right now
on a pile of her slut money in Aruba.
Here, take a picture of me and Gene.
[camera clicks, then whirs]
[Mona] Is that the type of girl
you're attracted to?
[Young Beau] No.
[Mona] Because I've noticed you
noticing certain types.
It's okay if you are.
You don't have to feel embarrassed.
I'm not.
[Mona] She's very pretty.
Very natural.
You could ask my advice, you know.
Only women know women.
That's the truth.
Men are blind.
That's not a criticism.
That's their charm.
Don't be defensive.
I'm proud of the man you are.
Hey.
A girl like that...
Confident, self-possessed.
A man would have to match her.
But you could.
She should be so lucky.
Any woman would be so lucky.
You just have to commit completely.
Nothing in life is more important
than choosing the right companion.
Hey, my dude. Long time no see.
- How was your day?
- [Grace] How are you feeling?
Oh, good, you're already in your PJs.
Well, we're hot on your tail. [chuckles]
[Mona] I think I might go to bed early.
[Young Beau] Okay.
[Mona] I haven't decided yet.
Unless you'd rather I stay up.
We could stroll around the deck.
Go stargazing.
I'll go to bed.
What about éclairs?
People hide razors in them.
What about rainbow cake?
The colors make cancer.
What about liquid shit?
[tense music playing]
Do you think your mom's a cunt?
What do you mean?
Well, it's okay. My mom's a complete cunt.
Are you a virgin?
Well, it doesn't matter.
I am too. I mean, who gives a shit?
I have to.
It's very dangerous for me. It's genetic.
My father died.
Here.
- Suck this off.
- What?
What?
We're allowed to kiss.
Who is?
- But only for the next ten seconds.
- What do you mean?
Ten. Nine.
- Eight. Seven.
- What? Wait.
- Six. Five.
- We're allowed to...?
- Four. Three.
- Can you just explain?
Two. One. One and a half.
One and three-quarters.
I'm sorry.
Elaine!
Shit. Fuck. I gotta go.
Okay. I'm sorry.
- Tomorrow?
- Now!
- [gasps]
- [Toni] You should be in my bed!
He's breaking your rules! Hypocrite!
[Roger yells]
You wanna test me, young lady?
Jeeves!
He's inside!
Beau's inside!
[pounding on door]
- Beau, Beau, Beau. They're taking me away.
- [screaming]
Beau, wake up. She's taking me away.
She's taking me off the ship.
- [Mona] What's happening?
- She's taking me away.
- Will you wait for me?
- [Mona] What is going on?
- [Young Beau] What's happening?
I love you.
[Mona] Oh, my God.
Why are you doing this?
What is this?
- Will you wait for me?
- Yes.
Promise? Do you promise? Promise me!
- Okay?
- I promise.
- Enough!
- Who is this bitch?
- [woman] I'm sorry.
- What is this?
No! No! No!
Beau, I love you, okay?
- Come here right now!
- Wait for me. Wait for me, okay?
- Shut up!
- Oh, my God!
- [Elaine] Wait for me!
- [Mona] My heart.
- My heart. My heart.
- [woman] What's wrong with you?
[Mona] What did you promise her, Beau?
[Mona gasping]
Beau!
Where is she going, Beau? Was she the one?
[Roger] No, no! Put that down!
- He's on the couch!
- [Jeeves] He's inside!
[lamp shatters]
[Grace] Okay, okay, okay.
That's him! That's him!
- [Jeeves yells]
- [Grace] Oh!
- That's enough!
- [Roger] No need to get up, Beau!
- Stay in bed! Stay in bed!
- [Grace] All right.
[tense music playing]
He's laughing! He's laughing!
- He's laughing!
- Don't worry, Beau. False alarm.
[Grace] It's okay, Beau.
He doesn't know what he's doing.
It's all under control.
- Okay.
- [Jeeves] He's laughing!
[Grace]
When they rescued him in the jungle,
they found him running around,
shooting at the bodies.
And not at...
Not the enemy, his own squad too.
[Roger] His own squad, Beau.
[Grace]
He was defending himself. He still is.
He's a hero and he came back to nothing.
We're the only ones who would take him in.
[Roger] He's gonna be so ashamed
in the morning, Beau.
Mark my words.
He loves you.
[fading] He told me he loves you.
He told me yesterday.
[unsettling music playing]
[Grace]
That's not part of the original contract.
I'm a mother myself, you know.
In that case, I might have to...
Look alive, pal! It's grill time.
I thought we'd have
a little goodbye barbecue
before we hit the road.
What?
You got the tri-tip.
Good morning, sweetheart.
How are you feeling?
- [Roger] You coming, Gracey?
- Right there.
Let's get you up.
- [groans]
- Oh! Oh, oh, oh. Shh. Shh. Shh.
Baby.
There you go. There we go.
As someone who sees you and loves you
and knows what you're going through,
even though I know I can never know,
I have to tell you...
[Roger] Babers?
You mind coming out here for a sec?
I need a hand.
Of course.
Why don't you find something to watch?
I'll be right back.
Channel 78.
[Toni screams] Now!
What? What is...?
What?
What? What?
We're gonna finally put some color
on these walls.
What?
Here. Take that wall.
That wall!
Okay.
Yeah, how about this?
Please. What...?
What are you doing?
Why are you doing this?
- Hey, Grace is so careful about this room.
- It's my brother!
I know. So, why?
Okay.
- Yeah...
- What?
[Toni] Yeah, you know what?
You'll just get fucked up with me.
- I'm supposed to be leaving.
- So, you'll leave fucked up.
No, I feel really bad right now, please!
So, what, you can come into my life
and sleep in my bed
and steal my fucking parents,
but you can't get fucked up with me?
No! I'm not trying
to steal anything, I swear!
No, you've already blown it!
You failed your stupid test!
What?
Everyone pretending
you're some sad, old orphan.
- It makes me puke!
- Wait. Wait. What do you mean?
I'm sorry. Please...
I'll leave. I'll do whatever you want.
But what does that mean?
- What do you mean, a test?
- No one is asking you to leave.
I'm asking you to fucking drink
this fucking paint with me.
- Toni, please.
- Don't call me Toni!
I'm sorry, but it's your name.
It is my name. It's my name.
What did you mean
when you said that about the test?
- What does that mean?
- I don't care! You first.
Don't. Toni, please.
You listen to me.
I have videos of you. I'll post them.
I'll say what you did.
What? What did I do? What did I do?
- Fine, you fucking pussy, faggot.
- No, please, Toni, don't!
Stop, please! You're gonna be sick!
Stop! Stop!
Fuck you!
[Beau] Help! Help! Doctor!
Help! [sobbing]
[Grace screams]
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
She drank. She drank it.
- No. What did you do to her?!
- She drank it.
No. I didn't. I tried to get her to stop.
I begged her, "Please stop doing it."
Come on, Toni. No, no, no, Toni.
No. No. Come on, baby.
I didn't. I didn't. I told her not to.
I begged her.
[Grace] Come on. No!
Come on, baby. Come on.
I see you now!
What?
Replacing my son...
- with a demon.
- No, no. No, Grace.
With a demon! [screaming]
- I'll kill you!
- No! Please, no!
- No. Oh, my God.
[Beau yells]
This ends up bad.
It's bad. It's bad. Totally bad.
[Grace] Jeeves!
Rip him apart!
[panting]
[metal screeches]
[birds singing and chirping]
[unsettling, pensive music playing]
[crickets chirping]
[music fades]
[woman singing] ♪ In my heart
Pull me out ♪
♪ Into your arms ♪
♪ Into your mouth ♪
♪ Into your eyes
I fall ♪
♪ I felt all my breath ♪
♪ You breathe me in ♪
♪ Oh, my heart
You start... ♪
[Beau] Hello? I'm...
I'm sorry, I'm lost.
I was in an accident. And I don't...
I don't know where I am.
I'm sorry, but can you please help me?
Are you hurt?
That's a very big piece of glass
in your head.
Glass?
Oh, it was a door.
Uh...
I think we should take it out.
Can I take it out?
- Oh, God. Oh.
- Okay. Okay. Okay.
- It's bleeding a lot?
- It's okay.
The head ones, they bleed like crazy
and then they just stop.
- Is it? Is it stopped?
- Mm-hm.
It is?
- See?
- Is it?
Trust me. My father bled to death.
We should clean it up.
It could still get infected.
You wanna come with me?
Okay.
Thank you.
We're nearly there.
[unsettling music playing]
[men speaking indistinctly]
[pregnant woman] Hi, Lloyd.
- This is Beau.
- [Beau] Hello.
[pregnant woman] He was in an accident.
His mother just died
and his father died before he was born.
When sorrows come,
they come not single spies,
but in battalions.
[Beau] Thank you.
[pregnant woman]
This is me. Just a sec, Beau.
[man 1]
...sweeping changes day before the show,
and then wonders why it's not right.
Everything was right.
It was right for months.
You aren't set?
I have an extra sleeping bag
if you need one.
This way, Beau.
[Lloyd] Some Cupid kills with arrows,
some with traps.
[man 2 singing] ♪ Fly, ladybug, fly ♪
♪ Up in the sky so high ♪
♪ I have no parents left ♪
♪ That's why I'm so bereft ♪
[man 3] Damn these crossroads!
How can one stake one's life
on a choice between two unmarked paths?
[man 4] If one leads forward,
must the other go backwards?
- [woman] If it were a trap?
- [man 4] Or this an opportunity?
Or might they both lead home,
where I can take my rightful seat
and be lord of my own possessions?
They're rehearsing for the preview.
[man 3] Damn these crossroads!
There, let's not spoil it.
[horns sounding]
[man 4] As great trumpets speak,
our poor hero realizes too late:
But these are funeral horns!
[pregnant woman] Everyone?
This is Beau.
- [man 4] Hi, Beau.
- [man 3] Hi, Beau.
- [woman] Hi, Beau.
- [man 3] Hello.
He was in an accident,
and both his parents are dead.
- [man 3] No!
- [man 4] Are you okay?
[man 3] That's terrible.
What is this place?
We call ourselves
the Orphans of the Forest.
[Ladybug Man] That's right.
Although many of our parents
simply abandoned us
without even bothering to die.
We're a traveling theater company.
We go from forest to forest, off the grid,
making up homes from whatever we find.
[Ladybug Man]
And then at the end, we put on a big show!
I'm so sorry.
See him?
That's Yesekov.
He's the man who started all of this.
[boy] Papa...
[tri-tone chimes,
then dramatic music plays]
It's time for the show.
Hi there. Are you joining us?
- What do you mean?
- Do you want a costume?
We like to blur the line
between the audience and the players.
Either of these?
I like this color with your eyes.
Or this one's fun.
[Beau] Um...
- That one.
- That's my favorite too.
Let's get changed.
[pregnant woman]
I'm happy you're joining, Beau.
Hey there, brother, I'm Duncan.
What brought you here?
[ominous music playing]
[Grace] Jeeves! Rip him apart!
[Jeeves yelling]
[beeping]
["Shine" playing]
♪ You can give your life
You can lose your soul ♪
♪ You can bang your head
Or you can drown in a hole ♪
♪ Nothing lasts forever
But you can try ♪
What am I doing here?
♪ Look around you ♪
♪ Everyone you see
Everyone you know is gonna ♪
Tell me, what am I doing here?
♪ Shine... ♪
[ominous music playing]
[bell rings]
[man] No!
Oh, God...
Fate has burned my house to cinders
and launched me into exile.
I once thought I knew despair,
and that I could master it...
but now that I know this pain,
I can't fathom relief.
When I reach out for answers,
I grasp cold air.
[sobs] O, with my mother and father gone,
I have lost my whole self!
[sobbing]
[mechanical whirring]
[wind howling]
[birds chirping]
You grieve well.
Your parents are honored
and now may rest forever in peace.
Rise.
Now go forth.
Erect your own glittering home...
and make it permanent.
Do I venture forth...
or stay here?
With what I know.
[deep thrumming]
If I stay, I die.
No. I must go.
[gasps]
What? Chains?
- [grunts]
- Now you see.
They have always been there.
[thrumming continues]
[pensive music playing]
[angel] Yes. Push forward.
Pray that you learn valor
and be given luck.
You will walk many miles.
Dozens will become hundreds.
Hundreds will become thousands.
You will pass through countless villages.
But, finally,
one village will speak to you,
some deep, essential part of you
will recognize it,
and you will say, "This village is mine."
You will learn a trade...
and eventually earn a living.
You will know
the pleasure of tasting fruit
and bread and wine that is yours,
because you have earned it.
You will find a plot of land
and build a house with your own hands.
You will cultivate the land.
You will live off it.
You will come to make new friends.
[camera clicks]
One day, you will meet a woman.
The story of your meeting will change
according to who tells it:
That you were lost
and she helped you find your way,
or that she was off-course
and you guided her home.
She will see your fears and your pain
and your dreams and your potential...
and you will see hers.
In finding your other half,
the gifts of your life will multiply.
Sometimes she will look like a man to you.
She will become pregnant
because you have sex with her.
You will have children. Three sons.
You will teach them what you know,
and you will tell them
you love them every day.
They will grow into handsome boys,
blessed with courage
and kindness and ambition.
You will share your feelings of pride
with your therapist.
He will archive them.
One day, an historic storm will sweep
through your village
and destroy your home.
[dramatic music playing]
You will be carried away by a great flood.
[boys yelling]
You and your family will be separated...
and you will be deposited
in a strange country.
[insects chittering]
[wolf howling]
You will look for your family for days...
then weeks...
then months.
So many months
that you will come to lose count,
but you will not find them.
You will try to find work
to support your continuing search,
but no one will speak your language.
You will be treated like a criminal.
Eventually, you will come upon a village
wracked by an inexplicable plague.
As you pass through,
a man deranged by tragedy
will identify you as the beast
who burned down his home
and replaced his children's feet
with their hands.
You will try to argue your innocence,
but this will only
make you sound more guilty.
You will wonder yourself
whether you are guilty.
You will flee.
Mad with vengeance,
they will send an attack dog
to pursue you.
It will tear through the world
to find you.
You won't know this,
but you will sense it.
And you will keep a detailed record
of these impressions in a log.
And over time,
this log will become many logs.
Your adventures will continue
for years and years.
You will learn
to distinguish birds by their call,
and you will know every tree
and plant by its name.
Abandoning all comforts,
you will condition your mind
to new ways of seeing.
You will experience great highs
and profound lows,
and you will look for your family
until your life shrinks
and fades into the dream of a ghost.
You will come to wonder
if they ever existed.
Finally, when you are old and frail,
you will collapse in exhaustion.
[Beau sobbing]
Oh, sweetheart.
Why are you crying?
Because I have searched
for my family all my life...
to the end of my life,
and I'm still alone.
[angel] You should not be crying
for your misfortunes, for your own sins.
You also have been searched for,
but you're so lost in your own selfishness
that no one could ever find you.
Confess.
Before your peers.
But what did I do?
[angel] You know.
Confess.
I've been a coward my whole life.
You will confess everything.
After which you will find
the earth replaced by good water.
Sleep will come untroubled.
- [birds singing]
- [trumpets sounding]
To the sound of distant trumpets,
you will awake,
as if by a miracle...
at the foot of your glittering village.
No one will recognize you,
but the smell of the air
and the sounds of the insects
and the way the evening light
slashes itself across the chimney
of a neighbor's old house
will unloose in you
a torrent of vivid memories.
You will be invited to a special play
being put on in an outdoor theater
just for that night.
Despite your hunger,
you will decide to spend
your last dollar on this.
Over the last 40 years,
his memory had faltered to the extent
that he couldn't remember
his own mother's face,
but just by breathing in the air,
he was seized by the absolute certainty
that this was his village.
Nobody remembered him.
And even though all of his neighbors
had been replaced by younger generations,
he recognized everything,
and somehow he too felt recognized.
His home had waited for him
just as loyally as he had searched for it.
Even the sight of the evening sun
casting slashes of amber light
across a familiar chimney
sent him reeling into a flood of memories.
- What did our father do next?
- Where was the village?
We only saw it as boys
and have no memories.
- Please, tell us where to find it.
- No, wait. What did he do next?
He was delirious with hunger
and only had enough money
for one bowl of soup,
but before he could spend it,
he was invited to a special play.
It was already in progress,
but he felt compelled to go in,
and so he spent his last dollar.
Not long after sitting in,
he saw that the details of the plot
were impossibly similar
to those of his own life.
And there were three young men
on the stage
who looked remarkably like himself.
This is me!
And he rose up, at once exhilarated
and terrified that it might not be true,
- and he announced...
- This is my story!
And the three young men immediately
recognized the man as their father.
- Dad?
- No. It can't be.
[Beau] My sons.
[boy 1] Dad?
Dad. Dad...
- [Beau] Oh...
- [boy 1 sobbing]
Oh, my God.
- [boy 2] Oh, my God.
- You're my boys.
Oh, my beautiful, sweet boys.
Don't be afraid. Come here. Come here.
Come here. Oh, my... Oh, my God. Oh!
Where have you been?
You were ripped from me.
I've looked for you for so long.
[sobbing] So long...
- [boy 1] Where did you go?
- I know you.
I made you. Oh, my loves.
- Oh, my loves. Oh, my darlings.
- [boys sobbing]
- Oh, my darlings.
- [boy 2] I missed you so much.
Oh. Oh...
That's okay. It's okay.
I'm here. I'm here.
Oh, my loves.
It's okay.
What about our mother? Is she...?
- What?
- Is she...?
She's not with you?
- Oh, God.
- [boy 3] We were raised as orphans.
Oh, no.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
- [boy 1] Where's Mom?
- [Beau] It's okay, my love. It's okay.
[boy 1] Mom...
[boy 2] Is there...?
Is there any other family?
Besides us?
You had a grandmother.
[boy 2] Where is she?
Her head...
And our grandfather?
[boy 2] How did he die?
[Mona] He died on our wedding night.
The same night you were conceived.
He died the very instant
you were conceived.
How?
By finishing.
Into me.
He had a heart murmur, just like you.
Did it hurt?
I'm sure it was excruciating.
It was the first time we made love.
The first time either of us made love,
with anyone.
Your grandpa and your great-grandpa
died the same way.
But he thought he might be different.
I'm just as guilty.
I urged him on.
I wanted a normal life.
I wanted a child.
He died on top of me.
Inside.
I think about it,
and I wanna rip my ears off.
But then...
But then, that same trauma...
which changed me so utterly...
also resulted
in the greatest gift of my life.
I am so sorry for what your daddy
passed down to you.
I can't tell you how sorry I am.
[boy 1] Is that a lie?
No.
[boy 2] Can that really happen?
Yes.
It's why I never...
with anyone.
[boy 1] Dad...
you've never been with anyone?
[boy 2] Then...? Then how did you have us?
What should I do?
Which limb shall I strike off?
You might act yesterday,
and it would be decades tardy.
[Hero] Have I not given all I have?
- All you have?
- You have given trifles.
[God] You have sacrificed nothing real.
[Hero] I have been pinned down
by my promises.
I am not the master of my life.
Are you okay?
- [Hero] I am a mouse in a maze!
- [God] A maze.
I feel sick.
I know.
[actors speaking indistinctly]
Try this.
It helps me.
- Thank you.
[pensive music playing]
Hello.
Can I help you?
Do you recognize me?
I don't know.
When you were little...
[Beau] What?
How did you come here?
I was chased.
Your father is alive.
What?
I knew him. After you were born.
I worked for your mom...
Not before I was born. He died before...
...serving your dad food,
cleaning up after him.
My parents were in debt to your mom.
What's that?
What?
- Who are you?
- It doesn't matter, I...
- It does. It does.
- No. It's just... Kidding. I...
I'm so happy to see you.
Are you him?
Wait.
[pregnant woman] You okay, sweetheart?
[Hero] Do my eyes deceive me?
What is this phantom I see?
[tracker beeping]
Hello, fair stranger!
[beeping intensifies]
Ah, now you see, out of the shadows...
[grunts]
[actors screaming]
[man 1] Everybody hide now!
Get me down from here!
- Somebody help me!
- [man 2] Somebody!
[tense music playing]
- [woman] Oh, my God!
- [man 3] Somebody help me!
[man 1] Get me down from here!
Get me down! I can't, I'm tied up. Hurry!
Get me down! Help!
[Strange Man] Beau!
- Dad?
- Run! Now...
- [people screaming]
- [intense music playing]
[machine gun firing]
[Beau yelling]
[electricity crackling]
[Elaine] Am I hurting you?
Okay, let's go. Clothes off.
[Mona] Come on. Enough, now.
What did I say?
Didn't I say I wasn't gonna do this again
with you tonight?
I'm about to feel hurt.
You're about to really hurt me.
Where's Daddy?
Excuse me?
You know where Daddy is.
Daddy's dead.
Are you trying to hurt me?
I don't care! I want Daddy!
Do you want Daddy too?
Come on. You want it your way, let's go!
Up you go.
- I can't.
- Oh, but of course you can.
You're big enough to hurt Mommy,
you're big enough for this.
- Nobody's allowed up there.
- Up!
- Do you wanna go up too?
- [Young Beau] No.
What is that? Are you nodding?
This is it.
We don't talk about you anymore!
Get back in!
[bird singing]
[ominous music playing]
[music turns ethereal]
[music turns dramatic]
[Beau] Excuse me, sir.
Is the funeral already happening?
Already over. There's a video inside.
[man on recording] Mona.
Mona Wassermann.
We're gathered here today as a community,
bound together by our love for Mona
and by a feeling of duty.
The duty to mourn Mona's passing,
but also to celebrate Mona's life.
Mona, who was petrified of squirrels.
Mona, who single-handedly built
a super-business
beyond her wildest dreams.
Mona, who was an endlessly dedicated wife
to her adoring husband,
who passed away tragically just
as their life together was blossoming.
And Mona, who was a devoted mother
to her sole surviving son, Beau,
whom she loved so deeply
and who has elected
not to be present with us today.
Mona loved Beau with a love
that could move mountains.
In fact, I suggest when we leave,
we check on the mountains
to make sure they're okay.
[somber music playing]
[woman on recording] What can you say?
I hope she knows that.
I wish I could tell her that.
That I did, I loved her.
[man] And it's in accordance
with her last wishes
that we now play this song.
Her favorite song.
["Everything I Own" playing over speakers]
♪ You sheltered me from harm ♪
♪ Kept me warm, kept me warm ♪
♪ You gave my life to me ♪
♪ Set me free, set me free ♪
♪ The finest years I ever knew ♪
♪ Were all the years I had with you ♪
♪ And I would give anything I own ♪
♪ I'd give up my life, my heart, my home ♪
♪ I would give everything I own ♪
♪ Just to have you back again ♪
♪ You taught me how to love ♪
♪ What it's of, what it's of ♪
♪ You never said too much
But still you showed the way ♪
♪ And I knew from watching you ♪
♪ Nobody else could ever know ♪
♪ The part of me that can't let go ♪
♪ And I would give anything I own ♪
♪ I'd give up my life, my heart, my home ♪
♪ I would give everything I own ♪
♪ Just to have you back again ♪
♪ Is there someone you know ♪
♪ You're loving them so ♪
♪ But taking them all for granted? ♪
♪ You may lose them one day ♪
♪ Someone takes them away ♪
♪ And they don't hear the words
You long to say ♪
♪ I would give anything I own ♪
♪ I'd give up my life, my heart, my home ♪
♪ I would give everything I own ♪
♪ Just to have you back again ♪
♪ Just to touch you once again ♪
["The Waiting Song" playing over speakers]
♪ Goodbye, my Johnny, my darling... ♪
["Isn't it a Pity" playing over speakers]
[door opens]
[woman] Hello?
Hello?
♪ You don't know... ♪
Yoo-hoo?
♪ But I'm gon' tell you soon ♪
Hello?
♪ Isn't it a shame? ♪
♪ Yes, how we break each other's hearts ♪
Hi.
♪ And cause each other pain ♪
I'm sorry.
I thought it started at 8 p.m.
♪ How we take each other's love... ♪
Okay. Um...
I brought flowers.
I'll just leave them here, I guess.
She also owes me money.
This certainly isn't the time
and you're probably not the person.
♪ Isn't it a pity? ♪
Okay. Um...
♪ Some things take so long... ♪
I'll be leaving, then.
I just need to call another Uber.
I can wait for it. I'm sorry again.
♪ When not too many people can see ♪
♪ That we are all just the same ♪
♪ We're all guilty ♪
♪ Because of all the tears ♪
♪ Our eyes just can't hope to see... ♪
[crickets chirping]
Elaine?
It's me.
It's Beau.
Oh, my God.
Beau?
No.
Uh, it can't be.
I can't believe it's you.
Oh, my God.
I mean, of course it's you.
This is your mom.
I'm so sorry.
For your loss.
What are you doing here?
I'm just trying to, you know,
uh, pay my respects, and...
I guess, give you my condolences,
since you're actually here.
I'm...
so sorry.
I can't believe it's you.
Do I look different?
You recognized me. I'm old now.
You're the same.
No, I'm not.
You are.
Well, you're the same too.
Except for your body and your face.
You worked for her?
What do you mean?
I did, until last week.
I was actually just drowning my sorrows
before I came.
My breath's like pure wine.
"Until last week"?
I'm sorry for your loss.
I waited for you.
What do you mean?
Why?
You told me to.
I even have it in writing.
I wanted you to.
Baby.
Baby, baby...
Do you want to go inside?
Do you want me to leave?
Let's go inside.
Bedroom. Where?
♪ And we're capable
Of taking each other's souls... ♪
The dragon's lair.
Got any candles in here?
Why don't you go to the bathroom?
When you come back, I'll be ready.
- You didn't get undressed.
- Yep.
Hi. Sorry. Hi.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Are you?
- You're so tense.
- Oh.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- Relax.
Okay. It's just because, you know,
it's been... Well, kind of a while.
Yeah, me too.
["Always Be My Baby"
playing over speakers]
I like that you're not all macho.
Thank you.
Take these off.
Okay, what I meant was that
it's been really kind of a while.
- Well, it hasn't affected your virility.
- What?
- You're crazy hard.
- Really?
♪ Doo-doo-doo, oh
Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo, da... ♪
[Beau moans]
Oh, my God.
- Is it...? Is it on?
- Yeah.
You sure the condom's on all the way?
Yeah? Oh, my God.
- Am I really in?
- You feel so good.
Oh, no.
[Beau gasping]
Isn't it nice?
Yeah. But wait...
- I... What?
- Let's start it over.
["Always Be My Baby" starts again]
- Isn't it nice?
- Yeah.
You... Wait a second.
I can't...
I think it's gonna happen.
Wait! You gotta wait a second.
Stop.
Oh! Stop. Stop. Stop.
Oh, no! [yelling]
[moaning] Oh!
Oh! Oh!
♪ Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo, da... ♪
[Beau] Oh! [gasps]
Oh, my... My God.
God.
[Elaine] Oh!
I really felt that.
- I...
- Oh, God that was a lot.
You just blasted through that bag.
[moans]
- Oh, my God.
- I love you.
- [Beau gasps]
- [moans]
♪ That you would always be mine... ♪
I wanna come too.
- I...
- Hold on.
Hold on.
On.
Getting it. Don't move.
Yeah. Don't move.
Don't move. Okay? [moaning]
♪ You'll always be a part of me
I'm part of you indefinitely ♪
♪ Boy, don't you know
You can't escape me? ♪
♪ Ooh, darling,
'Cause you'll always be my baby ♪
♪ And we'll linger on
Time can't erase a feeling this strong ♪
♪ No way you're never gonna shake me ♪
♪ Ooh, darling... ♪
Oh, my God. [laughs]
♪ Yeah, doo-doo-doo, oh
Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo, da... ♪
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my God.
♪ I ain't gonna cry, no... ♪
I really thought I was gonna die.
My whole life.
♪ But inevitably... ♪
Oh, thank you.
Oh, thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
♪ Our love will never end, no ♪
♪ You'll always be a part of me
I'm part of you indefinitely... ♪
[screams]
[body thuds]
♪ 'Cause you'll always be my baby ♪
[muffled screams]
[sobbing]
♪ Boy, don't you know
You can't escape me? ♪
♪ Ooh, darling
'Cause you'll always be my baby ♪
♪ I know that you'll be back, boy ♪
♪ When your days and your nights
Get a little bit colder, oh ♪
♪ I know that you'll be right back, baby ♪
♪ Oh, baby, believe me,
It's only a matter of time, time ♪
♪ Time ♪
♪ You'll always be a part of me
I'm part of you indefinitely ♪
♪ Boy, don't you know
You can't escape me? ♪
♪ Ooh, darling,
'Cause you'll always be my baby ♪
- ♪ And we'll linger on ♪
- ♪ And we will linger on and on ♪
♪ Time can't erase
A feeling this strong... ♪
[phone clicks, then song ends]
[Mona]
No, please. Continue as if I wasn't here.
What would be next?
No?
You don't look especially
overjoyed to see me, honey.
I was dead just a minute ago.
This is a miracle.
Get rid of this. Feed Harry.
She worked for you?
I sincerely doubt that, sweetheart,
but if you're right,
you can let her know she's fired.
For how long?
How many years from the beginning?
- From...?
- How is your head feeling?
It looks like
you really banged up your face.
You could have a concussion.
You don't feel disoriented?
You know where you are?
I'm in my house.
Actually, you're in my house, sweetheart.
And my house is your house,
which it always will be.
But if you know where you are,
then you must also know
where you just were
and where you just did what you just did,
which I saw every second of.
You didn't just wake up suddenly
and you were there.
You didn't just get dropped in,
out of the blue, to your surprise.
Your deceased mother's room.
Only days
after what you believed was her death.
I didn't.
- You didn't get deposited by accident.
- I didn't mean it.
- I know you didn't.
- No, I knew you weren't dead.
I saw with my own eyes exactly
what you knew
and what you didn't know.
You saw my body.
I saw the birthmark, Mom.
I know those were Martha's hands.
That's right.
- Good night, baby.
- Good night, Martha.
And if I hear any noise,
I'll break back in
and tickle you to death!
[both laughing]
It's...
What...? How...?
How do you even...?
How can you do that to her?
"Do that to her"?
Baby, I would never do anything
to the loyal and devoted housekeeper
who gave me 37 years
of unconditional service.
She volunteered.
- No, she didn't.
- Yes.
- She did.
No, she didn't.
I couldn't restrain her from volunteering.
For how much?
[poignant, pensive music playing]
[Mona] Enough that every member
of her extended family...
quit their job on the same day...
and won't ever need to work again.
And you know something else?
It was worth every penny.
Because now I know.
- What do you know?
- Everything.
You don't know anything.
Oh, do you think so, Beau?
Do you really think so?
Do you also think
I didn't know when you called
to give me the big, bad news
about your fictitious keys being stolen
from your imaginary door?
- My key... They were stolen.
- You think a mother can even help
but see through her son's blatant lies
and falsehoods and endless schemes?
You think this is any different
from the time you gave me
the exact same CD for my birthday
that you gave me the year before,
and which you also gave
your fucking high school counselor?
Or when you bought me that kitchen set
the very week
after I publicly swore off cooking?
Even when you were a baby,
you rejected me and refused to breastfeed,
while every other smug cunt on the street
had happy, docile babies
sucking their tits dry.
You think I hear the absurd story
of you missing your flight
and that I don't absolutely know,
that I have any hint of a doubt,
that you never, from the very start,
intended to make that flight?!
The true surprise, the shock,
would have been you actually coming!
Now, that would have spun
my head like a top.
I wouldn't have known what to do.
I'd have thrown myself,
flopping on the floor,
begging God's forgiveness
for ever having doubted you,
but still, I would have been struck stupid
with disbelief!
[ominous music playing]
What, you walking away?
Where you going?
What's behind the door, Beau?
Where on earth are you gonna go?
You've always acted
like some dutiful, doting little boy,
as if it's throwing me off some scent.
None of it's ever been real.
You spent your whole life going around,
asking every half-wit you could find:
"If I do this, can I avoid this,
or will that happen?"
As if you were born
without the mechanism to choose.
You let it all resolve itself
in the absence of you.
You make everyone do it for you.
You think that makes you innocent?
My own mother wouldn't even touch me.
Not if it was simply
to stamp me out if I was on fire.
I wasn't worthy of her love.
I hadn't earned it. And I never earned it.
No matter what I did.
No matter how much
of my deepest, real self
I denied and buried and smothered
until it was dead.
None of it mattered.
She blamed me
for everything her mother did to her.
When I had you, I promised,
"I will never do that to him.
I will give him all the love I have."
You know what I tell people
when they ask me how my son is doing?
I say, "Your guess is as good as mine."
How I wish that were true.
[Friel on recording]
Tell me more about that period.
[Beau] Well...
when I was just starting
to like my own stuff
and do my own things,
she'd take all those changes
very personally
and get very mad or sad,
and make me feel bad about it
until I stopped.
[toilet flushes]
[Friel] So, through the weaning process,
she took your displays of autonomy
as a betrayal.
[Beau] Exactly.
What do you mean?
[Friel] Can you give me an example?
[Beau] Well, like,
she would give me lots of love...
Oh, I gave you lots of love. I'm sorry.
...but if I didn't give it back to her
in the exact same way,
she saw it as me being not thankful
and, like, trying to hurt her.
[Friel] So, the love was conditional?
[Beau] Yes.
[Friel] This is very good for you, Beau.
Over 300 sessions, and that was about
as flattering to me as they get.
Which one was my favorite, Jeremy?
October 3, 2018.
[Beau] How could you...?
How could you...?
How could you do this to me?
[Beau on recording]
I've been having it since I was little,
where I'm a little boy,
probably the same age
as when I started having the dream,
and there's another me, who's identical...
but he's braver,
and he asks her about my father
because I'm too scared.
And then...
she sends him away and locks him up.
Upstairs.
And she never talks about him again.
[Friel] What is it you want to know
about your father?
If you weren't afraid,
if there were no consequences...
- I want to know the truth.
- ...what would you ask your mom?
[Beau] I'd ask her...
- To tell me the truth.
- I don't know.
[Friel]
Do you feel she didn't tell you the truth?
- Yes.
- [Beau] I...
- I don't know.
- Yes.
- I know now.
- But I think I'm too afraid to believe it.
I know the truth. I...
I met my father.
I met the man in the woods, and I know.
Why did you lie to me?
Do you want the truth now?
Yes!
[Mona] Follow me.
- Up there?
- That's right.
Nobody's allowed up there.
Some things are for your protection, Beau,
and I want you to remember
that I kept this from you.
- I don't wanna go up there now.
- No.
You want the truth,
and I think you deserve it.
Don't worry, sweetheart.
- I'll be right behind you.
- I don't want... Mom.
I'll be right behind you. Don't worry.
Up you go.
Don't worry, I'll be right behind you.
Don't worry, sweetheart. Up you go.
- This is just like my dream.
- I'm right behind you.
I'm right behind you.
Oh, God.
[unsettling music playing]
Oh, this is exactly like my dream.
[Mona] Don't you get it, you stupid idiot?
That wasn't a dream.
- That was a memory.
- Wait, wait, wait!
Mommy, wait!
No. No. Come on.
- Come on.
- [metallic clang]
[metallic clang repeats]
[metallic clang speeds up]
[man] Beau?
Beau?
My beautiful, sweet boy.
Oh, boy, let me see.
- [alarm blaring]
- [roaring]
[intense music playing]
[Beau screaming]
[Mona] Oh, Beau. Oh, baby.
Baby, sweetheart.
Oh, sweetheart.
I didn't want you to know.
Do you see now why I lied?
Beau.
Beau!
That was your father.
Oh, no!
[groans and sobs]
I'm so sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I know I've been a bad son.
I'll be a good son. Please. I'm sorry.
I'll do anything to make it up to you.
I'll make it up to you.
Please, please, please.
- Please. I'm sorry.
- You selfish little boy!
What are you crying about?
Do you have any idea
what I had to go through
to bring you into this world?
Stand up.
You cry now?
You need a mother now?
Ever since you clawed your way out of me,
I've had to dig down deep
to my very bottom
and squeeze the love out of myself,
but still I gave it to you.
I've given you my whole fucking life.
Which you took, and you took,
and you took, and I squeezed myself empty.
I gave you everything.
And what do I get back? What do I have?
Insults. And empty promises.
You promised to never hurt me.
Do you even remember that one?
You promised it a hundred fucking times.
You swore on your own life.
But your promises are nothing but shit.
I've been ground down to nothing
by love and panic and worry.
Is my baby hungry? Is he healthy?
Is he scared enough of the world?
And the fruit of all this anguish
is grief.
And hatred.
Yes. Yes. Hatred.
I do. I do.
I hate...
[ominous music playing]
Mommy?
Are you okay? You...
You can breathe. Can you breathe?
Can you breathe?
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Are you okay? Are you okay?
[gasps]
[Beau yells]
[crickets chirping]
[rumbling]
[haunting music playing]
[motor sputters and fails]
[man] Beau Isaac Wassermann.
Born May 10th, 1975.
Proceed.
We are gathered now
to assess the extent...
of the subject's guilt.
To begin with,
a seemingly innocuous tradition.
Every Monday,
before his weekly appointment
to scapegoat his mother,
the subject would visit his local pond
to feed the ducks.
Just as he never missed an opportunity
to feed his therapist's fish.
Very nice.
But what happens...
when he meets a human beggar
that very night?
Now, one can see...
that the subject will go out of his way
to feed a bird or a fish,
but not to support a suffering member
of his own species.
[defense] Objection! Violent street crimes
were everywhere on the news
and everyone was advised
to avoid strangers!
This is nothing new!
The subject had thoughts every day
around relieving the suffering
of those less fortunate.
By all indications,
he has a healthy, functioning conscience.
He just chose to ignore it.
Consider the following episode.
Day 49 of his 9th year.
He goes shopping with his mother.
At one point, she lost him.
Or so she thought.
Fearing the worst, she panics.
She searches the building.
She cries out for the boy,
who was, in fact,
hiding behind a corner,
watching the whole thing.
[defense] My client was genuinely lost.
It was upon finding his mother,
seeing her frantic state,
that he hesitated, for fear of punishment.
[Cohen] It was in this frantic state
of mind that his mother tripped and fell,
tearing ligaments in her knee
and badly harming her ankle.
And still...
the subject did not intervene.
[defense] He was afraid!
[Cohen] Consider now the subject
at age 15, day 210,
finding himself in the rare company
of other boys.
The subject,
hoping to impress
his horrendous new friends,
invites them into his home
while his mother is out
buying him gifts for his birthday.
He lets them into her private bathroom,
and allows them
to rifle through her dirty laundry,
and inspect, and ultimately steal,
her undergarments.
[Beau] Oh, God.
Oh, God. They pressured me.
- They pressured me!
- [defense] They pressured him!
What are you doing?
No! No!
No!
Oh, God!
Oh, God! Oh, my God.
Oh, God.
Even his supposed acts of thoughtfulness
are emblematic of a greater hypocrisy.
Take this very week.
The subject asked Grace and Roger
to drive him home,
so that he might bury his mother
and commence proper mourning.
Roger offered the option...
of driving home tonight
if the offer of driving tomorrow
wasn't soon enough.
And Beau chose to drive home tomorrow,
further postponing a trip
that had already been
outrageously delayed.
And if one examines
the expression on his face
when Roger made this challenge...
one can only conclude
that the subject was panicked
at the idea of returning home.
I didn't wanna put him out.
I... He had surgeries.
[intense music playing]
I cried when I was beside the coffin.
When I was told the news,
I cried for hours!
Continuing to bear this in mind,
I ask you to consider yesterday.
Not three hours
after meeting a knocked-up dimwit
who made clumsy eyes at him,
did he gift her with a tributary gift
intended for no one less
than his recently deceased mother.
Now, when the pregnant slut offered
to return this special gift,
did he insist
that this total stranger keep...?
[trumpets sounding]
[yells]
No. No. Wait!
Wait! Mom!
Wait.
My legs! My legs are stuck.
What? Wait.
Wait, Mom. My legs. I can't move.
What?
Mommy, please.
Please help me! Please!
Please help me out! Please!
Please!
Please don't fault me!
Help! Help me!
Somebody help me, please!
Help!
Help me, please!
Help! Please!
Please. I don't want to...
I don't want to...
[dramatic music playing]
[Mona sobbing] My baby! No!
My baby. No.
My baby.
No.