♪♪
[projector whirring]
There's a park...
Playgrounds.
Nice, right?
It is,
it's all just spacious.
Isn't this a beautiful
neighborhood?
It is.
Why is he waving?
We're in the South, baby.
People are just...
extra friendly down here.
Oh... okay.
We're here.
[chuckling]
Okay!
- Oh my God.
- Yeah, wow.
Babe, the house is
so beautiful.
Man, them pictures
didn't even do it justice.
- I know, right?
- Right.
Don't you start getting
emotional now.
Babe,
you did a great job
picking out this house.
I'm glad you like it, baby.
Look, I already got
some stuff set up inside.
Look, why don't you go in,
take a look around,
and I'm gonna grab
the luggage.
Okay.
[laughing]
[soft music]
[soft music continues]
Well, don't you look
comfortable?
Babe, I absolutely
love this house.
Do you now?
More than me?
I don't love anything
in this world
- as much as I love you.
- Aww, that's sweet.
That's what
I like to hear, Boo-Boo.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
[doorbell rings]
- You expecting somebody?
- Uh, no?
Whoa-whoa, no-no-no-no-no,
that don't mean you have
to go and answer it.
Look, there'll be
plenty of time for that later.
That's no time like the present.
We here now.
Southern hospitality.
What about my
Southern hospitality?
- Ever thought about that?
- Move.
- Come on now, baby-- all right.
- You said it, baby.
Okay, I know I said it,
but that doesn't mean
- you have to--
- Just following your lead.
[groaning]
[sighing]
- Hi.
Hello. I'm George.
This is my wife, Wilma.
We're your new neighbors,
and we thought
we'd drop by to say hello.
Well, I'm Keisha,
and this is my husband, Brandon.
Hello, welcome
to the neighborhood.
Thanks so much. I'm Joy,
and this is my husband, Greg.
Howdy.
- So, where y'all from?
- Keisha.
- What?
- Already with the questions.
I can't ask 'em
where they from?
It's cool.
We're from Los Angeles.
West Side.
[clearing throat]
We thought we'd bring you
a little housewarming gift.
Oh, neat. Cool.
Thank you.
We appreciate it.
I hope you all like wine.
We most certainly do.
- The bubbly.
- Thank you.
Guys, we're not
fully unpacked,
but did you guys want
to come inside?
No, no-no,
you guys settle in.
There'd be plenty of time
to hang out later.
- You sure?
- Yes, yes.
There'd be plenty of time
to hang out later.
Okay, well, it was
a pleasure meeting you all.
You, too.
- Thank you.
- ...bye.
[soft chatter]
We have such great neighbors.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Southern hospitality, baby.
We don't have to go
on no wine run now.
- Right?
- Mm-hm.
What they got
going on here too--
- I mean, the good stuff.
- [scoffs]
- They wasn't cheap.
- [doorbell rings]
Oh, we are just popular today.
What is this?
- Hey.
- Hello, I'm Rebecca.
I'm one of your new neighbors.
Everyone just calls me Becky.
Sorry I don't
have anything for you.
I just wanted to drop by,
say hi, and introduce myself.
Oh, no, that's no worries.
No worries at all.
I'm Greg.
Nice to meet you.
We appreciate you
stopping by, anyway.
- Oh, you're not alone?
- No, no, my wife's here.
Hello.
I'm Joy.
- Nice to meet you.
- Becky. [clears throat]
Well, you must come over
for dinner sometime.
I-- since I didn't
get you guys anything.
Oh, no, no, you don't have
to worry about that.
No, I will not take no
for an answer.
Besides, I make a mean
spaghetti and meatballs.
Sure.
Just let us know when.
- It's a date.
Well, I'll let you all
get back to moving in.
Okay.
Enjoy the new home.
- We will.
- Thanks for coming by again.
She was sweet.
- "It's a date."
- She was talking to both of us.
She was looking at you.
Baby, don't start.
Don't do that now.
You need to stop.
That's crazy.
You know,
it's Southern hospitality.
Come on, now.
You excited about
your first day of work tomorrow?
More anxious
than anything, it...
feels like the first day
of high school all over again.
Well, let me guess,
what, you're gonna have
clothes all across the floor,
matching shoes and everything.
That's what
you telling me now?
Sir, I've graduated.
I hang my clothes up,
and I put the shoes underneath.
We got some growth happening.
Yes, we got growth.
Thank you.
Hello!
All right.
Look...
I've only been
in marketing ten years.
Why am I nervous?
It's a new position, babe.
Executive.
Nervous is normal.
I just want things to go right.
And they will.
You've earned this.
Thanks, babe.
Just telling you how it is.
You through eating?
Yeah...
yeah, I'm done eating.
[soft music]
Yes, sir.
Oh, you gotta be
kidding me, man.
- [hollow clunking]
- Shit.
Oh, hey! Hey.
- Hey.
- You a runner, too?
Um, no, no, really I just
do it to keep in shape.
Take this physical agility test
for the police academy.
Okay, oh,
neighborhood protector.
- [chuckling]
- No, not yet, but,
after a few of their tests
and a background check,
maybe so.
I'm sure you'll do fine.
Um, so you're a runner?
It helps me focus.
My therapist
suggested it, so.
- No-- don't worry.
- Okay.
- I'm not crazy or anything.
- Oh, no, no, of course.
I wasn't thinking of it
like that.
[laughter] Well, no,
I mean, seriously,
everybody needs a little bit
of help and, you know,
someone to talk to
every now and then.
- It's true.
- Yeah.
Yeah, you know,
not all of us are blessed
with a significant other,
you know?
We got to do the best
with what we got.
Touché, touché.
Anyway, you ready to run back?
- What, me and you, like, race?
- Yeah, let's do it.
That's what you want?
You sure you want--
- You scared?
- Come-- let's do it then.
- No stopping. No stopping.
- No stopping?
- No stopping.
- Child, please.
- Let's do this. You ready?
- All right. Ready?
- On you. On you.
- Set.
- Oh!
- [laughing]
[soft music]
- Well, hey, beautiful.
- Hey, babe.
Hey.
Mm. Thank you.
- How was your run?
- It was good. It was good.
I just went
to the park and back.
Getting my win in.
Okay, okay, my baby gonna ace
that conditioning test.
- You know I will, come on.
- Okay, shoot.
- Let's go.
- Since he found himself
a new running partner.
Baby, she was
already at the park
- by the time I got there.
- Just messing with you.
I know my baby loves him
some chocolate.
You know I do.
Don't you forget that.
- Never.
- Mm-hm.
Okay, I gotta go.
- You all set?
- Yes, I love you.
I love you, too.
You do good
on your first day.
- I will.
- Knock them dead.
- Thank you.
- All right.
♪ She feeds on superstitions ♪
♪ I am the truth
that haunts her mind ♪
♪ I'll have no need
for vengeance ♪
♪ Just tell that girl
that she's not mine ♪
♪ My heart is cold
and missing ♪
♪ She hates the fact
I don't rewind ♪
♪ I'm gone,
you should have listened ♪
♪ And I'm not
coming back this time ♪
♪ I wear my sunglasses
at night ♪
♪ Because my eyes deceive me ♪
♪ I've been moving like
a thief while in the night ♪
♪ I hope no one can see me ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been moving
like a raging madman ♪
♪ I've been moving like someone
who's lost his mind ♪
♪ When it comes to the girls,
I'm the bad man ♪
♪ And my love is
forever lost in time ♪
♪ Someone please come quick ♪
♪ She broke
her heart again ♪
♪ And I didn't mean to go
this far with her ♪
♪ Because she was
just a friend ♪
♪ No, I'm not going back,
not this time ♪
♪ I'm a whisper in the wind ♪
♪ So you can stay with him,
waste his time ♪
♪ This is
where my love ends ♪
♪ I beat a superstition... ♪♪
♪♪
Hey, baby.
- How was your day?
- Hi.
- Long.
- It was long?
[groaning]
Let me get this stuff.
Why don't you tell me
all about it?
I need all the details.
How was it?
Well, everyone was super nice.
I have a young
and hungry staff
right out of college
who is willing to learn.
- Good.
- They think they're ready
- to take my job.
- Ahh. [laughing]
Well, is that a good thing?
Extremely.
- This looks great.
- Yes, yes, yes, ooh.
What you think?
- Mm, mm-hm.
- This is delicious.
I love it when you cook.
You're so much better
at it than me.
Thank you, baby.
That's sweet.
But you can cut out
the reverse psychology
because you're
cooking tomorrow.
Baby, I only use
my powers for good,
but yes, I can take care
of you tomorrow
since I'll be gone
till Saturday.
Wow, where are you going?
They're flying me
out to Atlanta
to speak
to potential clients.
So, I have to get
myself and the team
up to speed tomorrow.
Oh, wow, sounds like a lot.
It is.
Well... I have news, too.
Yeah, what's that?
So I'll be taking
the agility test on Friday.
And if I pass--
- Mm-mm.
- --then I'll be--
When you pass.
When I pass, I'll have
the interview right after.
- Babe, that's great.
- Right?
- I'm a little nervous, but--
- You got this.
- Gimme some, gimme some.
- We got this.
Gonna both be
killing shit this week.
- [laughing]
- Now, how you do this?
[soft music]
- Hey.
I must have missed you
this morning.
No, I'm actually headed over
to take my agility test.
Okay, well, good luck.
Thanks.
I won't keep you any longer.
Let me know how it goes, okay?
Will do, thanks, um,
- enjoy your run.
- Will do.
- All right, bye.
- Thanks.
Good morning, everyone.
I'm Sergeant Armstrong.
I'll be conducting
your agility test.
You'll be given 15 minutes
to run a mile and a half.
I'll be taking your times,
each lap you pass.
You'll call out
your last name
each time you pass me.
And if you don't
shout out your name,
I won't record your progress.
On your final lap,
I'll call out your time.
If you pass,
I'll see you inside.
If not,
I'll see you next time.
[grunts]
Lawson!
13.55.
Big boy ain't
going to make it.
He's out of steam.
Hey, man, you almost there.
What you doing?
I can't breathe. I don't think
I'm gonna make the time.
Well, look, I got news for you.
If you sprint this last 100,
last 100, you make the time.
But you got to go
right now, though.
- All right, all right.
- All right, come on.
Push! Push!
Sanders.
14.59.
And you made it.
- [sighing]
- Thank you, man.
I wouldn't have made it
without you.
It's all you, boss.
It's all you.
You got heart.
They'll go with sense.
Right here.
You surprised me
out there, Lawson.
Well, sir, I'm sure
anyone would have
helped that man out
in my position.
I'm talking about the nearly
14-minute mile and a half.
I would have expected somebody
that put in ten years
in the army
would have performed
better than that.
Well, sir, with all due respect,
I haven't ran since the service.
[chuckling]
I'm just busting
your chops, Lawson.
I mean, the key is,
is that you passed.
Hell, I put in 20 years,
and the very thought
of running hurts my feet.
That was very impressive
what you did
with Pork Chop out there.
We need more men
like you on the force.
Well, sir,
we can't leave a man behind.
Well, I'll be doing
a background check
in the next couple of days
and checking your references,
calling your past employers,
and talking to your neighbors.
If everything checks out,
I'll let you know
where we go from there.
Sounds good, sir.
I appreciate
the opportunity.
All right, then.
- Thanks for coming in, sir.
- Thank you, sir.
[soft music]
[sports commentator chatter]
[doorbell ringing]
- [doorbell ringing]
- [knocking on door]
- Hey... my guy.
- Hey.
- What's up, G, you aight?
- What's up, brother?
- Come on in, man.
- Hey.
Game just started.
COMMENTATOR:
Thirteen-point lead for Boston.
[commentator continues]
...and it's gonna be
Celtic ball.
Great defensive play
from Kevin Garnett.
- One beer.
- There he is.
Hey...
- You got a nice place.
- Thank you, man.
- I appreciate it.
- Thank you for that invite.
Oh, no problem, no problem.
I didn't take you
for a hoops guy, though.
- Really, I'm a football guy.
- But, you know,
If LeBron playing,
I'm watching, no doubt.
No doubt about that.
I'm watching, too.
Hey, is Joy coming
to watch the game with us?
Oh, no, no, man.
Joy's out of town on business.
She'll be back in a couple days.
That worked out perfect.
Yeah.
Keisha out
getting her nails done.
Hey, if you didn't call me...
I'd probably be playing
spades or something
- with old man George.
- Hey, old man George be
busting them spades, though.
I heard he was nice.
- Man cold.
- Mm.
Don't let the age fool you.
He sharp as a tack.
Look, why don't you set
something up then?
You know I love a challenge.
Back home,
all we did is play spades
and watch the game
on the weekends.
- Really?
- Yeah, yeah.
Hey, man, we should
start our own tradition.
You can get your ass
whooped anytime you want.
Whoa-whoa-whoa,
whoa-whoa-whoa...
Who, me?
- Yes.
- You sadly mistaken.
But bet, set it up.
- Me? Mistaken.
- Yeah.
- Very much so.
- I don't even eat meat.
[doorbell ringing]
Let me find out
if Keisha gave you permission
- to be outside.
- What? I'm the man in my house.
Plus, I let her know
where I was going before I left.
- Hi.
Oh, sorry to disrupt
you and Brandon.
Oh, no, no.
Just watching the game.
- Would you wanna join?
- Oh, no, thank you.
I'm actually here for Joy.
I came to ask her a question.
Is she home?
Uh, no, she isn't in.
Is it something
maybe I can help you with?
No, no, I don't want
to disturb you.
Thank you for asking, though.
No problem.
Hey, wait, uh...
I passed the fitness exam.
Congratulations.
I'm not surprised at all.
I feel safer already.
- Oh...
- [chuckling]
I'll see you later.
- See you later.
- Good night.
Good night.
My bad, man, that was Becky
looking for Joy.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
I could have swore
she was here looking for you.
Oh, no, no, man,
I don't need those problems.
- Mm.
- No, sir.
She's very suspect.
Hey, how long has she been
living in the neighborhood?
She probably moved in, like,
right before you all moved in.
Really?
Oh, I thought
she'd been here for a while.
Nah-- maybe, like,
a few months, if that.
Oh, okay.
Why you ask?
Oh, no reason.
I'm just curious.
Oh.
You know,
she tried to get at me
- once or twice.
- Really?
Yeah, I played dumb
the entire time, though.
[scoffs]
Hey, I'm surprised
she didn't try to get at you.
Well, wait-wait--
why you say that?
She seems to like
her coffee black,
you know what I'm saying?
Coffee black.
Yeah, that's crazy.
And how will
we target the audience?
Please turn to the last page.
So, this graph illustrates
first quarter projections
if we focus on marketing
and advertising
to the urban community
of Atlanta
from ages 18 to 35
using the major
social media platforms.
I'm talking Facebook,
Instagram, and TikTok,
as well as getting the major
influencers behind this.
Now, by doing this,
I am certain
that Film Life Clothing will
not only take over
the Atlanta market,
but the other major
surrounding cities.
I'm talking
Charlotte, Houston,
New Orleans, and Miami.
Well...
thank you, Mrs. Lawson,
for that presentation.
You've given us
a lot to think about, and...
- Yes.
- ...we'll be in touch.
Thank you, Mrs. Brown.
I know you're a busy lady.
Of course.
Thanks for taking the time.
And we have a meeting.
- Okay, thank you.
- Take care.
You too.
[engine rumbling]
- Hello?
- Hey, babe.
- How are you?
- Hey, baby. I'm good.
I'm good. Just out here
cutting grass. How are you?
I'm good.
You behaving yourself?
Of course,
of course, uh...
But I did have a little
friend over last night, though.
Who?
Friendly neighbor.
Boy, don't play with me.
I know you didn't have
that Karen next door
- at our house.
- Girl, no.
I had Brandon
from next door come over.
We chilled
and watched the game.
Don't mess with me like that.
[laughing]
Wait, and why she gotta
be a Karen, though,
baby, like,
is my wife a racist?
[scoffs]
Black people can't be racist.
It's a known fact
by default, no.
You have nothing
to worry about, sweetie.
I better not.
How'd the meeting go?
It went well. I think
we closed Film Life Clothing.
Oh, that's good news.
Thank you.
Well, I don't wanna
take up too much more
of your time.
I'll let you get back
to the yard work.
Yeah-yeah, let me get
back to it, I miss you.
I miss you, too.
- I love you.
- Love you more.
- Bye.
Bye.
[engine rumbling]
[text chime]
[laughing]
Yeah...
[whispering to self]
GREG: [whispering]
Oh, man...
Hey, what you smoking?
They call it Spider.
That smells good.
Yeah... uh-oh.
You gonna come over here
and arrest me or something?
[chuckling]
I'll let you off
with a warning if you share.
Deal.
KEISHA: Uh...
Ooh... I know he didn't.
Girl, what are you doing?
Over here watching
Greg and Becky smoke one.
Get away from the window.
Over here looking
like you on a stakeout.
Shh! Shh shh shh.
They can't hear us
from the house, nosy.
What's so funny?
Do you date Black guys?
I'm sorry.
What, do I give off
that aura?
No, no, you just...
you seem real comfortable
around Black people.
I mean, most of the white people
I know, where I'm from,
they're real distant,
but I don't know.
You seem to speak
at arm's length.
So what does it mean...
if I'm within arm's reach?
[coughing]
You know what?
Niggas ain't shit.
He just talking.
I better not catch your ass
over there just talking.
Why you put me in this?
I didn't even do nothing.
Mm-hm.
Oh, wow.
Who lives there?
- Over there?
- Yeah.
- No one.
- It's a beautiful house.
Yeah, it did belong
to the Miltons.
They moved a few weeks ago.
Great family.
Ooh, and they have
a badass pool.
- Really?
- Yeah.
We should go check it out.
You know that
I'm trying to be a cop, right?
Nobody owns it.
I'm sure there's
a bank out there
- that would disagree.
- Oh, come on.
It'll only be for a minute.
[giggling]
Hit that for reparations,
my nigga.
- What you say?
- Huh? I ain't say nothing.
Whatever.
Oh... where they going?
To mind their damn business,
just like me.
I'mma stand right here
because this is
the true show right here.
Ooh-whoo!
[sighing]
All these trees.
- Where are you taking me?
- Calm down.
I think
the lights are over here.
Hold this.
Hey, you were right.
This pool is badass.
Man, I love this.
- Yeah, told you.
- Wow, I like the lighting.
Everything seemed like
it's in this rightful place.
Like it's...
this is something else.
Oh, my God.
The water is still warm.
- Is it?
- [chuckling] Yeah.
This is dope.
And nobody stays here?
[chuckling]
Whoa-whoa-whoa, Becky,
Becky, what are you doing?
Becky, what are you--
Becky, get your ass
out of this pool.
Come and make me,
Mr. Officer!
Becky, I'm not jumping
in that pool with you.
Becky.
Shit.
[chuckling]
- My hero.
- Man, are you serious?
I thought you were
drowning, Becky.
That's messed up.
Swim to the deep end with me.
No, I'm not, I'm gonna stay
on the shallow side.
Where it's safe.
Well, I can't leave you
over there all by yourself.
- Yes, you can.
- Nn-nn.
- [chuckling]
I have to thank you
for saving my life.
You don't have
to thank me, Becky.
Oh, come on.
Are you serious?
- What? I was thanking--
- You don't have to thank me.
What, so you're just gonna
leave me here like this?
Good night, Becky.
Whatever.
WOMAN: So, how have you been
since our last meeting, Rebecca?
I'm doing well.
Writing in my journal,
reading, running, sleeping.
And the alcohol.
One year sober.
And your triggers?
None as of late.
Great.
Have you been practicing what
to do when you are triggered?
Go into a safe space
in my mind
and think positive thoughts.
Terrific.
Seeing anyone socially?
Yes, actually.
I met someone.
He's a great guy.
Wonderful.
How did you meet?
It's kind of
embarrassing actually.
He saved me from drowning
in my neighbor's pool.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
Sounds like fate.
I think so too.
He seems pretty perfect.
Now, no one is perfect.
Take things slow.
See, you have a tendency
to run off on a feeling, and--
That's not what I'm doing.
I mean, I hear you,
Dr. Robinson.
♪♪
Hey, stranger.
How are you?
I'm good.
Just glad to be home.
I had some business meetings
in Atlanta the last few days.
I love Atlanta.
The city, the men.
[mouthing "Oh, my God"]
You know.
[laughing]
Anyway, how were your meetings?
It went very well.
Thank you for asking.
Congratulations.
We should go grab
a cup of coffee to celebrate.
Oh, no, ma'am.
No coffee.
I have a serious
caffeine allergy.
It almost took me out
when I was younger,
- so water.
- Oh, oh.
But thanks
for the offer, Becky,
but I just really
want to relax,
take a warm bath,
and just cuddle with my husband.
Okay, I understand
that you're jet-lagged,
but tomorrow,
dinner, my house.
I won't take no for an answer.
- Uh, I...
- Please, come on.
I still owe you and Greg
a housewarming present,
and dinner was supposed
to be my treat.
Okay, sure.
- Just let me know what time.
- Eight o'clock is fine.
Okay.
I'll see you then.
Oh, there she is.
Hey, what is all of this?
Look who's home.
All of this is for you.
Oh...
I should leave you alone
more often.
[laughing]
No, no...
Thank you for the roses.
You're welcome--
hey, look, why don't you go
and have a seat?
[clears throat]
They're my favorite.
You're welcome, babe.
And also made your favorite.
Barbecue?
And potato salad
and ranch baked beans.
- [sighing]
- [squealing]
Whoa-whoa, hey...
[imitating motor]
Oh...
It says Joy.
"For my beautiful wife, Joy.
I miss you."
Ahh--
-Baby, what's this?
- Open it.
Baby, it's beautiful.
Baby, can you afford this?
Do you like it?
I love it.
That's all that matters.
- To us?
- To us.
Uh-huh.
- This feels so good.
- Oh, does it, now?
You like that?
Mm-hm.
Mm-hm, spoils
of a businesswoman
conquering
the business world.
Thanks, babe.
Oh, by the way,
Becky invited us over
for dinner tomorrow.
And when did you talk to her?
Mm...
right before
I came in the house.
She kind of stopped me
as I was getting out the Uber.
Nah, I'm good.
Just, uh... wanna
spend some time with you.
Get some much-needed alone time,
you know what I mean?
I feel that, but...
she's kind of not taking
"no" for an answer.
And, plus, she owes us
a housewarming gift.
Southern hospitality.
- Southern hospitality.
- Mm-hm.
I don't know, babe,
I just, um... I mean,
she probably doesn't even
season her food right.
What's the deal?
Thought y'all was cool.
Did something happen?
No, no, nothing happened.
Um... no,
I just want to spend
all my time with you,
that's all.
I get that.
Let's just go,
get it out the way,
and then come back
and be alone.
- Okay?
- All right.
Okay.
[coughs]
Looks like you got
the good stuff.
Girl, if you're calling
a $15 bottle of wine
the good stuff,
then I'm guilty as charged.
[laughter]
Besides, we can't
stay over here too long.
I got to get back
and take care of some things.
I got some work I got to do.
What you gotta do?
You ain't got no job,
tell me!
[mock-laughing]
Very funny.
[door chimes]
Hi, I'm so glad
you made it. Welcome.
Thank you for inviting us.
We didn't get the memo.
- Right?
- We underdressed.
No, no, not at all.
Don't be silly.
You look perfect.
Come on in.
[mouthing words]
Well, I hope
you two are huggers,
because you're
in the South now.
Come here.
- Mmm.
- Wow.
[chuckling, sighing]
You, too, Greg.
Come here.
Hey-- yeah, look,
we bought some wine.
- Oh, thank you.
- Yeah.
- Ooh, the good stuff.
- Told you.
Oh, yeah, well...
Hm.
I... I hope I didn't make
the food too spicy for you.
No, actually...
it's really good, I'm...
- I'm pleasantly surprised.
- [laughing]
Thank you.
I guess I have Greg's approval.
He hasn't said
a word all night.
It's very good.
- Becky.
- Hmm?
These greens, though?
Girl, they off the chain, like,
who taught you
how to cook like this?
[clears throat]
So, my first boyfriend
in high school
was African-American,
and his mom and I were
really close.
She's from Louisiana, and...
she doesn't cook
by measuring anything, right?
It's all from, like,
feeling and love,
- out of the heart.
- [laughter]
Oh, would you like
some more wine?
Absolutely.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome. Greg?
Mm-- I'm fine,
thank you.
Okay.
So, Becky,
are you from Houston?
Born and raised.
I love it here.
Aside from the heat.
Oh, girl, look,
the heat is smothering.
But... ooh...
anyways, what do you do
for a living?
Um...
well...
since my husband died, I...
I'm sorry, I didn't know.
It's kind of
still hard to talk about
while... because
I'm still grieving him.
He died unexpectedly
in a hiking accident.
Um...
He left me
a little bit of money.
I'm just trying to start over.
Live life,
whatever that means.
You know? I'm sorry.
No, I'm so sorry
I brought it up.
I'm sorry.
No, no, it's fine.
It's okay. I'm okay.
- You sure?
- Yes... sure.
[clears throat]
Okay.
Who wants dessert?
I have sweet potato pie
in the fridge.
Sweet potato pie,
or pumpkin pie?
Because there's a difference.
Girl, I know, okay?
- [laughter]
- Believe me, I know.
You know what, Becky, you...
you all right with me.
[mouthing "Well, thank you"]
[laughter]
But I'm gonna have
to take a rain check
- on your pie, okay?
- Okay.
But this wine, though,
it is going through me.
Please tell me
where your restroom is.
Yeah, it's going to be
straight down the hall
- to the left.
- Okay. Thank you.
Excuse me.
How was the food?
It was good.
Thanks for the invite.
Are you done
with your plate?
Yeah.
[sighing]
You know...
you've been kind of
quiet all night.
Any reason why?
Look, I thought we were
gonna keep our distance
for a while after...
you know.
I promised you and Joy
I'd cook y'all dinner.
I've got to keep my word.
You're a widow?
I didn't know that.
Well, it could have
been pillow talk
after our quickie,
but you decided
to grow a conscience.
[laughing]
Oh, don't worry.
It'll be our little secret.
[clicks tongue]
Look, I'm sorry
if I misled you
in any way,
but I love my wife.
Oh, so you want to forget
that you were all up in me?
What? I never touched you.
That's not
how I remember it.
In my mind,
you did all kinds of freaky shit
to me in that pool.
You're crazy.
Becky, thank you
so much for dinner.
Of course.
It's my pleasure.
I washed my hands.
- I promise.
- Oh, I trust you.
Okay, so do you need us
to help you with
- any of these dishes?
- No, I got it.
Are you sure?
Because Greg doesn't mind.
- Do you, Greg?
- [chuckling]
You know what?
We gotta go.
Thank you so much
for the lovely meal, Becky.
- Yes.
- Of course.
Let me walk you
out the door.
Now, Becky, I need
the recipe to those greens.
Enjoy the rest of your night.
You, too.
[chuckling]
[sighing]
[sighing, chuckling]
[sighing, moaning]
I cannot believe
Becky can throw down
in the kitchen like that.
Oh, it was all right.
I mean, I guess
I shouldn't be too surprised.
She's dated enough brothers.
Oh, so you know her type?
Yeah.
Girl talk, sweetheart.
Girl talk.
So before you left, you didn't
want to talk to the woman.
Now, y'all besties,
all 'cause she done
hit your taste bud spot?
That what you're telling me?
Now, you know
no one hits my spot like you.
Ooh, I know
that's right, mm!
Mm, right... on top...
like that.
Mm!
Put those legs...
right there.
Oh, baby.
This smells delicious.
Mm, after I'm done
with this, you next.
Deal.
Becky, what the hell are
you doing in my house?
What's it look like?
I fixed us breakfast, silly.
Aren't you supposed
to be a cop?
This is what they call a clue.
If I was a cop, I can have
your ass arrested for burglary.
Mm... no,
it's only burglary
if I trespass in conjunction
of depriving you
of loss of property
or committing a felony.
This is more like breaking
and entering-- eggs?
Take your eggs
and get the fuck out, Becky.
Why are you acting this way?
I thought we were really
feeling each other.
Rebecca...
hear me when I say this.
The other night was
a mistake, okay?
And for that, I apologize.
Now, I'm gonna say this
in the most polite way
that I know how.
Please stay away
from me and my wife.
I'm really sorry,
Greg, but...
you're gonna have to get used
to seeing a lot of me.
I don't know
if you've noticed,
but Joy and I are
getting pretty close.
And, shit,
we're damn near besties.
Have you lost your damn mind?
Stay the fuck away from me
and my wife, you crazy bitch.
Get your damn hands
off of me.
So, how have you been?
I've been better.
Have you been taking
your medication
and staying away
from the alcohol?
When I saw you last time,
you were so optimistic
about life and the future.
What changed?
We have to continue exploring
the trauma left on you
when your parents left you alone
when you were a little girl.
You know what, Doc?
It's funny.
Men want to act brand new
when you let them in.
What do you mean,
let them in?
I mean here, here...
and here.
Rebecca, I warned you
about falling too hard,
too fast.
Mm...
You don't understand.
It's not him, okay?
It's his wife.
Rebecca, are you having
an affair with a married man?
It's not an affair
if we're both in love.
And his wife is getting
in the way of that.
I just have
to get rid of her.
You mean divorce?
Sure.
I thought
you were referring
to harming his wife.
Under Texas state law,
you're obligated
to contact the authorities
if a patient plans on harming
themselves or others, so...
...that couldn't be the case,
Dr. Robinson.
Dr. Robinson,
will you excuse me?
I need to use
the little girl's room.
- Sure.
- Okay.
[gasping]
[ominous music]
[groaning]
[gasping, straining]
[sighing]
♪♪
Hi.
Sorry to bother you.
I'm Sergeant Armstrong with
the Houston Police Department.
Oh, it's no bother at all.
How can I help you, Officer?
I was wondering if you could
answer a few questions
about your neighbor,
Greg Lawson.
I'm doing a background check.
He's a candidate
for the police academy,
and it's common for us
to ask neighbors
about our prospects.
[clearing throat]
Sergeant Armstrong,
would you mind
if we move this inside?
It's getting
a little hot out here.
Sure. Whatever's
best for you.
Wonderful.
Please, have a seat.
[clears throat]
May I get you
something to drink?
Water's fine, ma'am.
It's a very nice home.
You live here alone?
Yes, I'm a widow.
Oh, sorry to hear that.
It happened a while ago.
So, how often do you communicate
with Greg and his wife, Joy?
I actually had them over
for dinner recently,
trying to be a good neighbor
and welcome them
to the community.
That's very neighborly of you.
How'd that turn out?
Great.
Until his wife went
into the restroom.
[sniffling]
I really don't wanna--
I don't wanna talk about it.
Here.
Did something happen?
When Joy went
into the restroom...
Greg made a move on me.
Really?
Could you please
elaborate more?
He grabbed my arm,
and he told me
he didn't want us to end.
So you and Greg are
having an affair.
No.
No, um...
[clears throat]
It only happened once.
You know, we were both drinking,
and one thing led to another.
Anyways, um...
He grabbed my arm,
and he wouldn't let it go
until I promised
that I would see him again.
Where did he grab you?
On my right arm.
Did he threaten you
or cause any bodily injuries?
Um... no.
No, uh...
[clears throat]
I see what you're trying to do,
Sergeant Armstrong,
but...
Greg is a good man,
and I don't want him
to get in any trouble.
Look, if he harmed you,
you need to let me know.
We can go down
to the police station right now
and file a police report.
No...
he didn't hurt me.
[clears throat]
No.
If there isn't anything else,
Sergeant Armstrong,
I have some errands
that I need to run.
Well, you've been very helpful.
Thank you for your time.
Will... Will my statement
keep Greg from getting
into the police academy?
He really isn't a bad man.
Well, let's just say
we have a standard
at HPD that needs
to be upheld.
Thank you for your time.
Have a great day.
- Thank you, ma'am.
- Mm.
[laughing]
Hey, Sergeant Armstrong.
I see you're
in the neighborhood.
Yeah, just interviewing
your neighbors
for your background check.
That one lady, Becky,
she had a lot to say about you.
Really?
I barely even know her.
That just goes to show you can't
believe everything you hear.
Well, let me tell you something.
We have a high standard
of ethics and morals
at the Houston
Police Department.
Getting involved
in an entanglement
with your next-door neighbor,
being a married man,
doesn't display
the proper judgment
- we seek in a candidate.
- Wait, wait.
Sergeant Armstrong, wait.
Hold on a second.
- Can I just explain?
- Also, learn to keep
your hands to yourself.
And if you ever touch her again,
I'll put you in cuffs myself.
Oh, hey, Margaret.
How you doing today?
Blooming gracefully.
Yes, you are.
Oh, I haven't
forgotten you, Fran.
We're saving
the best till last.
For a second there,
I thought you were
another crazy old lady
talking to herself.
Ho.
Excuse me.
Pass me that ho over there.
Okay.
[clears throat]
Don't get self-conscious on me.
Oh, I'm not ashamed
of anything that I've done.
You know,
George and I were watching
a film last night called
"The Home Wrecker."
I couldn't help
but think about you.
You know,
back in my day...
we called women
like you hussies.
We've been here 30 years,
and that couple
across the street,
they're some good people.
I don't want
any drama on my street.
It was quiet
before you got here,
and that's the way
it's gonna stay.
[sighing]
I don't know
what you think you saw,
but if I were you,
I would go back
to minding my own business,
because I would hate...
for something unfortunate
to happen to you and George.
[soft chuckle]
You know,
I may be old
and occasionally senile...
but I know a troubled thot
when I see one.
Nice talk, neighbor.
[door chime]
Hey, did you tell
Sergeant Armstrong that
I put my hands on you?
Honestly?
- I don't remember what I--
- Damn it, Becky!
Stop playing games.
You're fucking with my life.
Oh, baby, don't worry.
I have plenty of money.
And once we're together,
you'll never have to work again,
so...
You're delusional.
Man, you must have really
lost your damn mind.
You really think
that I'm gonna leave my wife
to be with you?
You must be crazy.
Don't call me crazy.
- Hi, Joy.
- Hey, girl.
I'm gonna call you
later, okay?
Okay.
I'll be there in a minute, baby.
- Okay, baby.
- Yeah.
Just leave us alone.
Me and you?
We will never be together.
You got it?
[soft chuckle]
[soft chatter]
[eerie music]
[mouthing words]
[coughing]
[eerie music]
♪♪
[coughing]
[coughing continues]
[deeper coughing]
[halting coughs]
[phone ringing]
RESPONDER:
911, what's your emergency?
[sniffing]
Good morning.
What'd you find out?
Her labs came back
with high amounts of caffeine.
Caffeine?
She's allergic to caffeine.
I stopped drinking coffee
because she would
break out in hives
after we kissed.
After I had a cup.
That doesn't make sense.
Do you think
maybe somebody at work
could have got
their cups mixed up?
No, no-no,
I doubt it, I mean,
she takes her allergy
really seriously.
She's very cautious.
Well, regardless,
she's gonna have to be
very careful from now on.
She's lucky to have
survived this incident.
I mean...
we're probably gonna
have to keep her
for observation
for a few more days,
make sure she's okay.
If she does well,
we'll let her go home.
- Thanks, Doc.
- You're welcome.
♪♪
[gas hissing]
- [doors squeaking]
- [engine starting]
[sad music]
I was thinking,
maybe something...
you know,
could've triggered this.
What's going on?
I don't have a clue.
Stay there. I'm gonna go
find out what's happening.
Hey, guys.
What happened?
Keisha and Brandon
died last night.
What? How?
Carbon monoxide poisoning.
Their gas from the stove
was left on all night.
Jesus.
[ominous music]
[phone vibrating]
Hello?
BECKY: I love you.
And I know you love me.
Who is this?
Now you're gonna pretend
you don't know
the sound of my voice?
Let's stop playing
these games.
How did you...
You must have the wrong number.
Get rid of her.
Or I will.
[ominous music]
[thunder crashing]
Hey, babe...
Hm?
Why don't we go outside
and enjoy this beautiful day?
It's nice outside.
- I gotta work.
- You gotta work?
Mm-hmm.
But you're the boss.
Tell them
you're not coming in.
you're still recovering.
That way, we can
go get some breakfast,
we can go to the park,
and we can just enjoy
this beautiful weather.
And at the end of it,
we go into the hotel,
and we can do
your favorite thing.
Order room service?
You got it.
- Really?
- Really.
I mean...
we do deserve it.
- We deserve it.
- We do.
Yeah, we do.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
[giggling]
Mm-hm, you better walk.
- What? Shut up.
- You better walk.
- What am I gonna do with you?
- Uh-huh.
Put all that in there--
just put it in there.
- [laughing]
- Put it in.
That's what you do.
[engine starting]
[soft music]
[sighing]
[moaning]
[soft music]
[sighing]
Home, sweet home.
Don't that sound good?
Doesn't it? I love it.
Home, our love house.
[Greg chuckling]
GREG:
What the hell...
[soft gasp]
Just hang tight, I'm...
I'm gonna call the police.
Yeah...
hey, babe, I...
I gotta tell you something.
What is it?
I know who trashed our house.
Who?
Who would do
something like this?
Becky.
Becky?
Our next door neighbor Becky?
Why would she do this?
Baby, look,
she's obsessed with me.
She won't leave me alone.
Why?
What'd you do?
Nothing.
I didn't do anything.
- I swear.
- Greg...
do not lie to me.
All right, look...
while you were away
in Atlanta,
we shared a beer
and a joint together.
She wanted to show me
the Miltons' backyard.
So...
we went to the pool...
look, she jumped in,
and I went in after her,
because I thought
she was drowning.
But turns out
she wasn't drowning at all.
She tried to kiss me,
but I rejected her.
And I got out of the pool,
baby, and I came home.
That's it.
That's all that happened.
Baby...
say something, don't...
So you're telling me
that while I was out of town,
you went skinny-dipping
with that white bitch?
It wasn't like that.
That's not what
- I'm saying at all.
- Did you fuck her?
No, I didn't fuck her.
Are you serious, Joy?
How do I know that?
Damn it, I knew
from the moment I saw her,
I knew that bitch was trouble.
[exhaling]
Feels like you're telling me
about any of this
because this bitch
done fucked up our house.
It's okay, it's cool.
It's okay,
because...
I'm gonna show this bitch
what crazy really looks like.
Get the fuck out my way.
Baby, wait.
Babe, what are you doing?
Joy.
Joy, what are you--
what are you doing?
Look, I don't-- I don't think
you have to talk to her.
Why don't you just let this
whole thing work itself out?
- [laughing]
- Babe, are you serious?
You wait on that. I'm gonna
go beat this bitch's ass.
Shit.
Where are you going?
Could you slow down?
[groaning]
Look, Joy, I don't think
this is a good idea.
[door chime]
That whistle ain't
gonna save you
from this
ass-whooping, bitch.
Come on, Becky, open up.
I just want to talk.
[door chime repeats]
Whoa.
Why's the door open?
I don't know.
The lights ain't working.
You know
we're trespassing, right?
Now you worried
about crossing the line?
I'm just saying,
she can kill us
if she wanted to.
Fuck that.
Bitch, where you at?
[eerie music]
Becky?
Becky!
Becky.
Becky...
[gasping]
[grunting]
[groaning]
So you killed them-- why?
Why?
Because these
old-ass neighbors
kept sticking
their noses in business
that doesn't concern them.
So, Brandon and Keisha
wasn't an accident, huh?
Hmm.
You're a smart one.
I can see why Greg likes you.
Girl, fuck you.
And stay the fuck away
from my husband, bitch.
Greg and I are in love, okay?
You're coming between us.
You are one crazy bitch.
Don't call me crazy!
[screams]
[grunting]
[gasping]
[coughing]
[whimpering]
Greg told you not
to come into this house.
You should have listened
to your man, bitch.
Why don't you
put that bat down?
Say it to my face.
[grunting]
Come on... let's go.
[screaming]
[choking]
[groaning]
- [coughing]
- [groaning]
And to think...
we could've been friends.
Aah!
[gurgling]
[sighing]
Babe... babe?
Huh?
You good?
Yeah.
No... oh, no.
We're going to jail.
♪♪
VOICE:
Hey, um, I know you probably
don't wanna hear from me,
but you've been
on my mind lately,
and you know
how I am with my dreams,
and I had a dream
about you yesterday.
So I hope that all is well.
Take care of yourself
if I don't hear from you.
Okay, bye.
♪ I beat a premonition ♪
♪ Torn down
by ordinary words ♪
♪ He says I'm gonna get him ♪
♪ I said
I'm gonna get to work ♪
♪ Her thing is demolition ♪
♪ Tearing down all my barriers ♪
♪ She's got a new edition ♪
♪ I say the more,
the merrier ♪
♪ I wear my sunglasses
at night ♪
♪ Because my eyes
deceive me ♪
♪ I've been moving like
a thief while in the night ♪
♪ I hope no one can see me ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been moving
like a raging madman ♪
♪ I've been moving like
someone who's lost his mind ♪
♪ When it comes to the girls,
I'm the bad man ♪
♪ And my love is
forever lost in time ♪
♪ Someone please
come quick ♪
♪ She broke
her heart again ♪
♪ And I didn't mean
to go this far with her ♪
♪ 'Cause she was
just a friend ♪
♪ No, I'm not going back,
not this time ♪
♪ I'm a whisper in the wind ♪
♪ So you can stay with him,
waste his time ♪
♪ Because this is
where my love ends ♪
♪ She feeds on superstitions ♪
♪ I am the truth
that haunts her mind ♪
♪ I'll have no need
for vengeance ♪
♪ Just tell that girl
that she's not mine ♪
♪ My heart is cold
and missing ♪
♪ She hates the fact
I don't rewind ♪
♪ I'm gone,
you should have listened ♪
♪ And I'm not
coming back this time ♪
♪ I wear my sunglasses
at night ♪
♪ Because my eyes deceive me ♪
♪ I've been moving like
a thief while in the night ♪
♪ I hope no one
can see me... ♪
[song fades]
VOICE:
I'm... about to drown!