That's nice, thank you.
Thanks very much.
I appreciate it.
Thank you very much.
Thank you all, thank you.
I appreciate that.
Thank you, thank you...
So, let me ask you something.
Let me ask you, how is everybody
doing tonight, huh?
Good, well, fuck you!
Just trying to make you feel at home.
Now listen... I've been
out here all this time
and I haven't been
complaining about anything yet,
so I think it's time to go
into the complaint department.
This is just a series of things
that are pissing me off.
Okay?
A series of things that are pissing me off,
'cause I don't have pet peeves,
I have major psychotic
fucking hatreds, okay?
And it makes the world
a lot easier to sort out.
First thing on my list
tonight... airport security.
Tired of this shit.
There's too much of it,
there's too much security at the airport.
I'm tired of some guy with a double
digit IQ and a triple digit income
rooting around inside of my bag for
no reason and never finding anything!
Haven't found anything yet!
Haven't found one bomb in one bag!
And don't tell me, "Well, the terrorists
know their bags are gonna be searched",
"so now they're leaving their bombs
at home." There are no bombs.
The whole thing is fucking pointless!
And it's completely without logic!
There's no logic at all!
They'll take away a gun,
but let you keep a knife!
Well, what the fuck is that?
In fact, there's a whole list of lethal
objects they will allow you to take on board.
Theoretically, you could take... a knife,
an ice pick, a hatchet, a straight razor,
a pair of scissors, a chainsaw, six knitting
needles, and a broken whiskey bottle,
and the only thing
they're gonna say to you is,
"That bag has to fit all the way
under the seat in front of you."
And if you didn't take
the weapon on board, relax,
after you've been flying for about an hour,
they're gonna bring you a knife and fork.
They actually give you a fucking knife!
It's only a table knife, but you
could kill a pilot with a table knife.
Might take you a couple of minutes,
you know... especially if he's hefty, huh?
Yeah, but you could get the job done,
if you really wanted to kill the prick.
Shit, there's a lot of things
you could use to kill a guy with,
you could probably beat a guy to death with
the Sunday New York Times, couldn't you?
Or suppose you just have
really big hands.
Couldn't you strangle a flight attendant?
Shit, you could probably strangle
two of them, one with each hand...
you know, if you are lucky enough to
catch them in that little kitchen area...
before they give out
the fucking peanuts, you know?
But you could get the job done,
if you really cared enough.
So, why is it they allow a man with big
powerful hands to get on board an airplane?
I'll tell you why.
They know he's not a security risk
because he's already answered
the three big questions.
Question number one: "Did
you pack your bags yourself?"
No, Carrot Top packed my bags.
He... He and Martha Stewart and Florence
Henderson came over to the house last night,
fixed me a lovely Lobster Newburg,
gave me a full body massage
with sacred oils from India,
performed a four-way around the
world, and then they packed my bags.
Next question!
"Have your bags been in your
possession the whole time?"
No, usually, the night before I
travel, just as the moon is rising,
I place my suitcases out on the street
corner and leave them there unattended
for several hours... just for good luck.
Next question!
"Has any unknown person asked
you to take anything on board?"
Hmm... Well, what exactly is
an "unknown person"?
Surely, everyone is known to someone.
In fact, just this morning,
Karim and Yusef Ali Bangaba
seemed to know each other quite well.
They kept joking about which one
of my suitcases was the heaviest.
And that's another thing they
don't like at the airport... jokes.
You know? Yeah,
you can't joke about a bomb.
But why is it just jokes?
What about a riddle?
How about a limerick?
How about a bomb anecdote?
You know... no punch line,
just a really cute story.
Or suppose you intended to remark,
not as a joke, but as an ironic musing,
are they prepared
to make that distinction?
Why I think not.
And besides, who's to say what's funny?
Airport security is a stupid
idea, it's a waste of money,
and it's only there for one reason:
to make white people feel safe.
That's all.
The illusion, the feeling
and illusion of safety,
'cause the authorities know they
can't make an airplane completely safe,
too many people have access.
You notice the drug smugglers
don't seem to have a lot of trouble
getting their little packages
on board, do they?
No, and God bless them too!
Oh and by the way, an airplane
flight shouldn't be completely safe.
You need a little danger in your life.
Take a fucking chance
once in a while, will you?
What are you gonna do? Play
with your prick for another 30 years?
What, are you gonna read People Magazine
and eat at Wendy's till the end of time?
Take a fucking chance!
Besides, even if they made all
of the airplanes completely safe,
the terrorists would simply start
bombing other places that are crowded:
porn shops, crack houses,
titty bars, and gangbangs.
You know, entertainment venues.
The odds of you being killed
by a terrorist are practically zero!
So, I say relax and enjoy the show.
You have to be a realist, you
have to be realistic about terrorism.
Certain groups of people...
certain groups:
Muslim fundamentalists, Christian
fundamentalists, Jewish fundamentalists,
and just plain guys from Montana,
are gonna continue to make life in this
country very interesting for a long, long time.
That's the reality, angry men in combat
fatigues talking to God on a two-way radio
and muttering incoherent
slogans about freedom
are eventually gonna provide us
with a great deal of entertainment,
especially after your stupid fucking
economy collapses all around you
and the terrorists
come out of the woodwork
and you'll have anthrax
in your water supply,
and saran gas in your air conditioner,
there'll be chemical and biological
suitcase bombs in every city
and I say, "Enjoy it, relax, enjoy
the show, take a fucking chance",
"put a little fun in your life." To me,
terrorism is exciting, it's exciting.
I think the very idea that you
could set off a bomb in a marketplace
and kill several hundred people
is exciting and stimulating
and I see it as a form of entertainment!
Entertainment... that's all it is.
Yeah.
But... but I also know that most
Americans are soft and frightened
and unimaginative and they don't realize
there's such a thing as dangerous fun.
And they certainly don't recognize
a good show when they see one!
I have always been willing to
put myself at great personal risk
for the sake of entertainment,
and I've always been willing
to put you at great personal
risk for the same reason.
As far as I'm concerned, all of
this airport security, all the searches,
the screenings,
the cameras, the questions,
it's just one more way
of reducing your liberty,
and reminding you that they can
fuck with you anytime they want
as long as you put up with it...
as long as you put up with it,
which means, of course,
anytime they want,
'cause that's what Americans do now,
they're always willing to trade
away a little of their freedom
in exchange for the feeling,
the illusion of security.
What we have now is
a completely neurotic population
obsessed with security and safety and
crime and drugs and cleanliness and hygiene
and germs...
there's another thing... germs.
Where did this sudden fear of
germs come from in this country?
Have you noticed this?
The media, constantly running stories
about all the latest infections:
salmonella, E-coli,
hanta virus, bird flu,
and... and Americans are...
They panic easily, so now
everybody's running around,
scrubbing this and spraying that
and overcooking their food
and repeatedly washing their hands,
trying to avoid all contact with germs.
It's ridiculous and it goes
to ridiculous lengths.
In prisons, before they give you
a lethal injection,
they swab your arm with alcohol!
It's true!
It's true! It's true!
Well...
Well, they don't want you
to get an infection!
And you could see their point, wouldn't
want some guy to go to hell and be sick!
It would take a lot of the
sportsmanship out of the whole execution.
Fear of germs...
why these fucking pussies!
You can't even get
a decent hamburger anymore!
They cook the shit out of everything now
'cause everybody's afraid
of food poisoning!
Hey, where's your sense of adventure?
Take a fucking chance, will you?
You know how many people die in this
country from food poisoning every year?
Nine thousand... that's all,
it's a minor risk!
Take a fucking chance...
bunch of goddamn pussies!
Besides, what do you think
you have an immune system for?
It's for killing germs!
But it needs practice...
it needs germs to practice on.
So... so, listen!
So, listen.
If you kill all the germs around
you, and live a completely sterile life,
then when germs do come along,
you're not gonna be prepared.
And never mind ordinary germs, what
are you gonna do when some super virus
comes along that turns your
vital organs into liquid shit?
I'll tell you what you're gonna do...
you're gonna get sick, you're gonna die,
and you're gonna deserve it
'cause you're fucking weak
and you got
a fucking weak immune system!
Now... Yeah, goddammit.
Hey. All right.
Let me tell you a true story
about immunization, okay?
When I was a little boy
in New York City in the 1940s,
we swam in the Hudson River, and
it was filled with raw sewage, okay?
We swam in raw sewage!
You know... to cool off!
And at that time, the big fear was polio,
thousands of kids died from polio
every year, but you know something?
In my neighborhood,
no one ever got polio!
No one! Ever!
You know why?
'Cause we swam in raw sewage!
It strengthened our immune systems!
The polio never had a prayer,
we were tempered in raw shit!
So... so, personally, I never take
any special precautions against germs.
I don't shy away from people that sneeze
and cough, I don't wipe off the telephone,
I don't cover the toilet seat, and if I drop
food on the floor, I pick it up and eat it!
I eat it! Yes, I do.
Even if I'm at a sidewalk café!
In Calcutta!
The poor section!
On New Year's morning
during a soccer riot!
And you know something? In spite
of all that so-called risky behavior,
I never get infections, I don't
get them, I don't get colds,
I don't get flu, I don't get headaches,
I don't get upset stomach,
and I... You know why?
'Cause I got a good strong immune
system and it gets a lot of practice.
My immune system is equipped
with the biological equivalent
of fully automatic military assault
rifles with night vision and laser scopes,
and we have recently acquired
phosphorous grenades,
cluster bombs, and
anti-personnel fragmentation mines.
So, when my white blood cells are on
patrol recon ordering my blood stream
seeking out strangers and other
undesirables, if they see any...
any suspicious looking germs of
any kind, they don't fuck around!
They whip out the wa... weapons,
they wax the motherfucker
and deposit the unlucky fellow
directly into my colon!
Into my colon!
There's no nonsense,
there's no Miranda warning,
there's none of that "three
strikes and you're out" shit,
first defense, bam...
into the colon you go!
Yeah! Yeah! Sure!
Yeah! Hey. All right. Oh...
And speaking of my colon,
I want you to know I don't
automatically wash my hands
every time I go to the bathroom,
okay? Can you deal with that?
Sometimes I do, sometimes I don't.
You know when I wash my hands?
When I shit on them!
That's the only time.
That's the o...
And you know how often that happens?
Tops, tops, two,
three times a week, tops!
Tops!
Maybe a little more frequently over
the holidays, you know what I mean?
And I'll tell you something
else, my well-scrubbed friends...
you don't always need to shower
every day, did you know that?
It's overkill, unless you
work out or work outdoors,
or for some reason
come in intimate contact
with huge amounts of filth and garbage
every day, you don't always need to shower.
All you really need to do
is to wash the four key areas:
armpits, asshole, crotch, and teeth.
Got that? Armpits, asshole,
crotch, and teeth.
In fact, you can save yourself
a whole lot of time
if you simply use the same brush
on all four areas!
Thank you!
Hey, thank you.
I appreciate it, thank you.
All right, now, listen... I got a few more
items of things that are pissing me off,
and this one comes
in the form of a question.
Haven't we had about enough of
this cigar-smoking shit in this country?
Huh? Huh? Thank you. God!
When is this gonna end?
When is this shit gonna go away?
When are these fat, arrogant, overpaid,
overfed, overprivileged, overindulged,
white-collared, business-criminal,
asshole cocksuckers
gonna put out their cigars and
move along to their next abomination...
white pussy businessmen
sucking on a big brown dick?
That's all it is. That's all it is.
That's all it ever was...
Yeah! A big brown dick!
Sigmund Freud said, "Sometimes
a cigar is just a cigar." Oh, yeah?
Well, sometimes it's a big brown dick...
with a fat, arrogant, white-collared,
business-criminal asshole
sucking on the wet end of it!
But hey, hey, the news is
not all bad for me, not all bad,
you wanna know the good part?
Cancer of the mouth.
Good! Fuck 'em!
Makes me happy, it's an attractive
disease... goes nice with a cell phone!
So light up, suspender man, and suck
that smoke deep down into your empty suit
and blow it out your ass,
you fucking cocksucker!
Now... Thank you. Thank you.
Hey... here's another question
I've been pondering...
what is all this shit about
angels? Have you heard this?
Yeah... three out of four people
now believe in angels.
What are you, fucking stupid?
Has everybody lost their
fucking mind in this country?
Angels... Shit!
You know what I think it is?
I think it's a massive, collective,
psychotic, chemical flashback
of all the drugs, all the drugs smoked,
swallowed, snorted, shot, and absorbed rectally
by all Americans from 1960 to 1990,
30 years of adulterated street drugs
will get you
some fucking angels, my friend!
Angels... Shit! What about goblins, huh?
Doesn't anybody believe in goblins?
Never hear about them
except on Halloween,
and it's always
negative shit too, you know?
And zombies... where the
fuck are all the zombies?
That's the trouble with zombies,
they're unreliable.
I say if you're gonna buy the angel shit
you might as well go
for the zombie package as well.
Here's another horrifying example,
an aspect of American culture,
the... the... the pussification,
the continued...
the continued pussification
of the American male
in the form...
Yeah? All right.
In the form of Harley Davidson
theme restaurants.
What the fuck is going on here?
Harley Davidson used
to mean something.
It stood for biker attitude, grimy
outlaws and their sweaty mamas
full of beer and crank,
rolling around on Harleys,
looking for a good time, destroying
property, raping teenagers,
and killing policemen... all very
necessary activities, by the way.
But now? Theme restaurants.
And this soft shit obviously
didn't come from hardcore bikers,
it came from these weekend
motorcyclists,
these fraudulent two-day-a-week
motherfuckers
who have their bikes trucked into
Sturgis, South Dakota, for the big rally
and then ride around like
they just came in off the road.
Dentists and bureaucrats
and pussy-boy software designers
getting up on a Harley 'cause
they think it makes them cool.
Well, hey, skeezics, you ain't cool,
you're fucking chilli and
chilli ain't never been cool.
And here... as long as we're
talking about theme restaurants,
I got a proposition for you.
I think if white people are
gonna burn down black churches,
then black people ought to
burn down the House of Blues!
Huh? What a fucking disgrace that place is!
The House of Blues...
they ought to call it
the House of Lame
White Motherfuckers,
inauthentic, low frequency,
single-digit, lame, white motherfuckers...
especially these male movie
stars who think they're blues artists.
You ever see these guys? Don't
you just wanna puke in your soup
when one of these fat, balding, overweight,
overaged, out of shape, middle aged,
male movie stars with sunglasses jumps on
stage and starts blowing into a harmonica?
It's a fucking sacrilege!
In the first place... in the first place,
white people got no business
playing the blues ever at all
under any circumstances
ever, ever, ever!
What the fuck do white people
have to be blue about?
Banana Republic ran out of khakis?
Huh?
The espresso machine is jammed?
Hootie and the Blowfish
are breaking up?
Shit, white people ought to understand
their job is to give people the blues,
not to get them... and certainly
not to sing or play them.
Tell you a little secret about the blues,
it's not enough to know
which notes to play,
you gotta know why they need
to be played, and another thing...
I don't think... I don't think white people
should be trying to dance like blacks.
Stop that!
Stick to your faggoty polkas and waltzes
and that repulsive country line-dancing
shit that you do, and be yourself,
be proud, be white, be lame,
and get the fuck off the dance floor!
Now... Ah, thank you.
Now, listen...
long as we're discussing minorities,
I'd like to mention
something about language.
There are a couple of terms being used
a lot these days by guilty white liberals.
First one is "happens to be."
"He happens to be black."
"I have a friend
who happens to be black."
Like it's a fucking accident, you know?
Happens to be black?
"Yes, he happens to be black."
Ah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
he had two black parents?
"Oh, yes, yes he did. Yes, that's right."
Ah! And they fucked?
"Oh, indeed they did... indeed they did."
So where does
the surprise part come in?
I should think it would be more unusual
if he just happened to be Scandinavian!
And the other term is "openly."
"Openly gay."
They say "he's openly gay." But
that's the only minority they use that for.
You know, you wouldn't say
someone was "openly black."
Well, maybe James Brown...
or Louis Farrakhan,
Louis Farrakhan is openly black.
Colin Powell is not openly black,
Colin Powell is openly white,
he just happens to be black.
Thank you. Thank you!
Thank you! Yeah...
Oh! Thank you. Thank you.
And while we're at it,
when did the word "urban"
become synonymous
with the word "black"?
Did I fall asleep for eight or nine years?
Urban styles, urban trends, urban
music, I was not consulted on this at all,
didn't get an email, didn't get a
fax, didn't get a fucking postcard,
fine, let them go,
and I don't think white women should
be calling each other "girlfriend," okay?
Stop pretending to be black!
And no matter what color you are,
"You go, girl" should probably go!
Right along... Right along with "You
da man." "Hey, you da man!" Oh, yeah?
Well, you da fucking honky!
Now, something
a little more positive for you,
don't want you to think the
whole show is just negativity.
This is about a festival.
This is my idea for one of those
big outdoor summer festivals.
This is called "slug-fest."
This is for men only.
Here's what you do... you get
about 100,000 of these fucking men,
- you know the ones I mean, these macho motherfuckers...
- Whoo!
...yeah, these strutting,
preening, posturing,
hairy, sweaty, alpha-male
jackoffs... the muscle assholes.
You take about 100,000
of these disgusting pricks
and you throw them in a big
dirt arena, big 25-acre dirt arena
and you just let them beat the shit
out of each other for 24 hours nonstop,
no food, no water,
just whiskey and PCP!
And you just let them punch and
pound and kick the shit out of each other
until only one guy is left standing,
then you take that guy
and you put him on a pedestal
and you shoot him in the fucking head!
Yeah. Yeah.
Then you put the whole thing on TV.
Budweiser would jump
at that shit in half a minute...
and guys would volunteer,
guys would line up,
all you gotta do is promise them
a small appliance of some kind.
Men will do anything,
just give them something
that plugs in the wall
and makes a whirring noise.
Here's another male cliché... these guys
that cut the sleeves off of their T-shirts
so the rest of us can have an
even more compelling experience
of smelling their armpits.
I say, "Hey Bruno,
shut it down, would you please?"
You smell like an anchovy's cunt, okay?
Ugh... not good. Ugh... ugh...
Whoa... not good, Bruno,
"and definitely not for sharing."
This is the same kind of guy
that has that barbed wire tattoo
that goes all the way around the
bicep. You've seen that, haven't you?
That's just what I need, some guy who
hasn't been laid since the bicentennial
wants me to think he's
a "bad mother fuck a"
because he's got a picture... Aah-aah!
A painting of some barbed wire on his...
I say, "Hey, Junior, come around
when you have the real thing on there,
I'll squeeze that shit on
good and tight for ya, okay?"
No kidding, no kidding,
this is the same kind of guy,
that if you... if you smashed him in the face
eight or nine times with a big chunk of concrete,
and then beat him over the head with a steel
rod for an hour and a half, you know what?
He'd drop like a fucking rock.
Like a rock.
Here's another guy thing that sucks...
these T-shirts that say, "Lead,
follow, or get out of the way."
You ever see that? This is more
of that stupid Marine Corps bullshit,
obsolete, male impulses
from 100,000 years ago.
"Lead, follow, or get out of the way!"
You know what I do
when I see that shirt?
I obstruct!
I stand right in the guy's path, force him
to walk around me, gets a little past me,
I spin him around, kick him
in the nuts, rip off the shirt,
wipe it on my ass, and shove
it down his fucking throat!
That's what I do when I see that shirt.
Yeah. Hey, listen...
that's all these marines
are looking for... a good time.
And speaking of tough guys,
I'm getting a little tired of
hearing that after six policemen
get arrested for shoving a floor
lamp up some black guy's ass
and ripping his intestines out,
the police department announces
they're gonna have sensitivity training.
I say, "Hey, if you need special
training to be told not to jam
a large cumbersome object
up someone else's asshole,
maybe you're too fucked up to be on
the police force in the first place, huh?"
Maybe, maybe not, maybe not,
I don't know, listen... yeah.
That's right.
You know what they ought to do?
They ought to have two new requirements
for being on the police:
intelligence and decency!
You never can tell, it might just work,
it certainly hasn't been tried yet.
No one should ever have any
object placed inside their asshole
that is larger than a fist and
less loving than a dildo, okay?
Now... now, this next thing
is about our president.
This is about our president.
Bill Jeff, Bill Jeff, Bill Jeff,
Clinton... I don't call him
"Clinton," I call him "Clit-tin'."
"Clit-tin'. C-L-I-T, T-I-N apostrophe!"
His big deal was JFK, isn't that right?
Loved JFK, wanted to emulate JFK
in every way.
Well, JFK's administration
was called "Camelot."
Well, it really should've
been called "Come-a-lot,"
'cause that's what he did, he came a lot!
So Clinton's looking for a
legacy, that's what he should call...
Well, maybe, "Come-a-little"
would be better for him
'cause he came a little,
you know... little on the dress,
little on the desk, not a whole lot, really.
Hey, he was no match, no match
for Kennedy in the pussy department.
Kennedy aimed high: Marilyn Monroe.
Clinton showed his dick
to a government clerk.
There's a drop-off here.
There's a drop-off.
Thank you.
Thank you! Now... I appreciate it.
Something else I'm getting tired
of... there's all this stupid bullshit
we have to listen to
all the time about children.
It's all you hear in this country... children.
"Help the children!"
"What about the children?"
"Save the children!"
You know what I say?
Fuck the children! Fuck 'em!
They're getting
entirely too much attention!
And I know what you're thinking, you say,
"Jesus, he's not gonna attack children is he?"
Yes, he is!
He's going to attack children!
And remember,
this is Mr. Conductor talking,
I know what I'm talking about!
And... I also know...
I also know all you single dads
and soccer moms
who think you're such fucking
heroes aren't gonna like this,
but somebody's gotta
tell you for your own good,
your children
are overrated and overvalued.
You've turned them into little cult objects,
you have a child fetish,
and it's not healthy!
And don't give me... don't give me
that weak shit, "Well, I love my children!"
Fuck you!
Everybody loves their children,
doesn't make you special.
John Wayne Gacy loved his children...
kept them all right out
on the yard near the garage.
That's not what I'm talking about.
What I'm talking about is this constant
mindless yammering in the media,
this neurotic fixation
that somehow, everything...
everything has to be
revolved around children.
It's completely out of balance.
Listen, there are a couple of things
about kids you have to remember.
First of all, they're not all cute!
Okay?
In fact, if you look at them close,
some of them are rather
unpleasant-looking.
And a lot of them
don't smell too good either,
the little ones in particular seem to have
a kind of urine and sour milk
combination or something.
Stay with me on this. The sooner you
face it, the better off you're gonna be.
Second premise, not all
children are smart and clever.
Got that?
Kids are like any other group of people:
a few winners, a whole lot of losers!
There are a lot of loser kids out
there who simply aren't going anywhere,
and you can't save them all,
you can't save them all,
you gotta let them go,
you gotta cut them loose,
you gotta stop overprotecting them,
'cause you're making them too soft.
Today's kids are way too soft.
For one thing, there's too much emphasis
on safety: Child-proof medicine bottles
and fireproof pajamas, child
restraints in car seats, and helmets!
Bicycle, skateboard,
uh, baseball helmets!
Kids have to wear helmets now
for everything but jerking off!
Grown-ups have taken
all the fun out of being a kid
just to save a few thousand lives.
It's pathetic! It's pathetic! What's happening is...
All right, what's happening...
You know what it is?
These baby-boomers, these soft, fruity baby-boomers
are raising an entire generation of soft,
fruity kids who aren't even allowed to
have hazardous toys, for Christ's sakes!
Hazardous toys, shit, whatever
happened to natural selection?
Survival of the fittest?
The kid who swallows too many marbles
doesn't grow up to have kids of his own!
Simple as that! Simple!
Nature! Nature!
Nature knows best.
We're saving entirely too many
lives in this country, of all ages.
Nature should be allowed to do its job of killing
off the weak and sickly and ignorant people
without interference from
airbags and batting helmets!
Just think of it
as passive eugenics, okay?
Now, here's another example
of over protection.
Did you ever notice on the TV news,
every time some guy with an
AK-47 strolls onto a school yard
and kills three or four kids
and a couple of teachers,
the next day, the next day, the
school is overrun with counselors
and psychiatrists and grief counselors
and trauma therapists trying
to help the children cope?
Shit! When I was in school, someone came to
our school and killed three or four of us,
we went right on with our arithmetic!
"Thirty five classmates minus four equals 31."
We were tough... we were tough.
I say if kids can handle
the violence at home,
they ought to be able to handle
the violence in school.
I'm not worried about guns in
school. You know what I'm waiting for?
Guns in church.
That's gonna be a lot of fun
and it'll happen, you watch,
some nut will go...
fucking ape-shit in a church
and they'll refer to him
as a "disgruntled worshiper."
Here... Here's another bunch of
ignorant shit... school uniforms.
Bad theory, the idea that
if kids wear uniforms to school,
it helps keep order.
Don't these schools do enough
damage making all these kids think alike?
Now they're gonna get them
to look alike too?
And it's not a new idea, I first saw
it in old newsreels from the 1930s,
but it was hard to understand
'cause the narration was in German!
All right.
One more... Thank you. Thank you.
One more item about children,
and that is the superstitious nonsense
that blames tobacco companies
for kids who smoke.
Listen, kids don't smoke because
a camel in sunglasses tells them to,
they smoke for the same reasons adults do,
because it relieves anxiety and depression.
And you'd be anxious and depressed too
if you had to put up with these pathetic,
insecure, striving, anal, yuppy
parents who enroll you in college
before you're old enough to know
which side of the playpen smells the worst!
And then they fill you full of Ritalin
and drag you all over town in search
of meaningless structure: Little league,
club scouts, swimming, soccer, karate, piano,
bagpipes, watercolors, witchcraft,
glass blowing, and dildo practice.
They even... they even have
play dates, for Christ's sakes,
playing is now done by appointment!
Whatever happened to "you show me
your wee-wee and I'll show you mine?"
Hey, no wonder kids smoke, it
helps... not as much as weed, but, hey...
...you can't have everything.
You know it's true, parents are
burning these kids out on structure.
I think every day, all children should
have three hours of daydreaming.
Just daydreaming, and... You could
use a little of it yourself by the way,
just sit at the window, stare
at the clouds, it's good for you.
If you wanna know how you can help
your children, leave them the fuck alone!
Thank you very much.
What am I talking about? Okay.
All right, now, a little change of
pace, a little change of intensity.
I want you to know what's on
television tonight on the other channels,
always like people to know what it is
they're missing by listening to my shit.
First of all, on the Playboy
channel... on the Playboy channel,
yeah, tonight, they have one of those
new reality shows where the people at home
send in their own tapes, it's called
"Home Videos of Bad Fucking."
And speaking of that delightful
activity, I guess you know last week,
Ricky Lake had a special program,
"Women Who Fake Orgasms,"
so tonight, not to be outdone, Jerry
Springer has a night time special,
"Men Who Fake Bowel Movements."
Yeah, I think they're running
out of topics on those shows too.
Sally Jesse's next show is "Rapists Who Force
Their Victims to Play 'Yatzee' Beforehand."
Getting a little strange on daytime TV.
Then, later on tonight on the Nostalgia
channel, they're gonna play back to back
two of my favorite episodes
of "Little House on the Prairie,"
first of all, the 1975 Christmas
show, "A Douchebag for Clara."
Wasn't that good? Aw...
And it was sad toward the end
when she cried
'cause she stuck it in the wrong hole!
Yeah...
But as they say in the U.S.
Navy, "There is no wrong hole."
And then, right after that,
they're gonna play
my favorite "Little House
on the Prairie" of all time,
"Missy Takes a Big Dump in the Woods."
And that was interesting, I thought,
'cause she had on the high heels
and the long dress, and it was fun
to watch how she had to maneuver
through the poison sumac, and they
didn't have toilet paper in those days,
she had to use a series of pinecones.
Yeah, and she was pulling them
in the wrong direction!
Yes, I understand toward the end
of the show, they had to bleep out
a lot of screaming and foul language.
And then, hey, hey, later on
tonight on... on the Pay-Per-View...
on Pay-Per-View, Willie Nelson...
Willie Nelson's concert is on
and TV Guide listed
all the songs he's gonna sing.
He's gonna start out with one of
my favorites, "Too Drunk to Jerk Off."
Isn't that a good one?
God, I love that song!
Then he's gonna do a series of
love songs, "Kiss Me, I'm Coming."
Aw, that's a good one. "Kiss me,
I'm coming, hold me, I'm humming."
Well, I can't help it, I am a romantic
and I do enjoy the sentimental tunes.
Here's a sad song, "I Should've
Fucked, Oh, 'Whatshername'."
Remember that? "I should've
never played the game,
I should've fucked, oh, 'whatshername'."
Here's one my mother
used to sing around the house,
"Your Love Ran Down My Leg
and Now, You're Gone."
Yeah, yeah, that one always got to me.
I'm glad you feel the same way.
Here's a fine love song,
"You Blew My Mind, Now Blow Me."
He's even...
he's even gonna do
a Stevie Wonder song,
"I Just Called To Say I Tested 'Positive'."
Yeah. Well, you don't wanna leave
anybody out, you know what I mean?
And hey, and hey, what would
a Willie Nelson show be
without a couple of cowboy songs?
He's gonna do that one George
Jones and Weyland Jennings wrote,
"Drinking Beer,
Taking a Shit, and Passing Out."
Then he's gonna do a kind
of a traditional western song,
one that Gene Autry used to sing
when I was a little boy,
"It's Midnight in Montana and I
Can't Get My Dick Outta This Cow."
Yeah.
I love that song. I always liked it.
Yeah. You know
why I like that song so much?
'Cause it's a real cowboy song.
And by the way,
speaking of cattle-fucking,
do you know why it is
when a rancher fucks a sheep,
he does so at the edge of a cliff?
It's so the sheep will push back.
Little something for ya.
Yes.
Just a little tip for you outdoors
men when you're out camping.
Now, this next thing is
about names, that's all, names.
Names are an interest of mine, not a hobby,
hobbies cost money, interests are free.
This is just about names. Did you
ever notice how they name singles bars?
Singles bars all have the same kinda cutesy
little one-word names that end in 's'.
Scamps, Tramps, Chaps, Rumors,
Cahoots, Cheers, Chances, Mingles, Risks,
Gambits, Notions, hey, if I had a
singles bar, you know what I'd call it?
Nipples and Dicks! Huh?
A little truth in advertising!
The Sperm Club!
Snatch o' Rama!
The Crotch-e-teria!
Frankie's Fuckery!
Café Vagina!
Open all night!
Well, I'm an old-fashioned guy.
I'm old-fashioned because I believe
the name on the outside of a place
ought to let you know
what's going on on the inside.
Here would be a good name for a
gay restaurant, "The Mouthful." Huh?
Come on, that's clever shit, that's a double
pun goddammit, you didn't think of it!
Besides, you don't have to
eat there if you don't want to.
No, no, just go in, have a cocktail...
...or a high-ball.
Here's another name
I don't care for, TGI Fridays,
you know these cutesy-ass
little places? TGI Fridays!
That whole "T-G-I-F" thing was cute
for about an hour... about an hour...
and that was 65 years ago when
someone first said it on the radio,
not cute anymore, time to
start bombing these locations!
TGI Fridays, if I had a place
like that, you know what I'd call it?
HSIOW...
Holy Shit, It's Only Wednesday.
I think people
would drink a lot more liquor
if they thought
it was Wednesday all the time.
Well, I'm just looking for a
little honesty in these names.
A little honesty, that's not asking a lot.
I'm thinking of opening up a motel
and calling it "The Sleep n' Fuck."
Wouldn't that be
a good honest name for a motel?
Who needs this "Shady Pines" bullshit?
"The Sleep n' Fuck" motel,
get me one of them big
neon signs, "Sleep... Fuck..."
Sleep... Fuck... Sleep n' Fuck!
Sleep n' Fuck! Sleep n' Fuck!
Sleep... Fuck...
"Sleep... Fuck..."
Sure.
"Sleep n' Fuck! Sleep n' Fuck!"
You put it right at the Jersey entrance
to the Holland tunnel, you know?
Actually, "Fuck n' Sleep" would
be a little more accurate, wouldn't it?
Best name for a motel would be "The
Fuck n' Smoke n' Sleep n' Roll Over
and Get Out of Bed and Wash
Your Crotch and Grab a Bite,
Two Cans of Mr. Pibb and Go
Home and Fuck a Whole Lot More."
A whole lot more.
'Cause that's all they ever have left in
those soda machines on Sunday night,
Mr. Pibb and Diet Shasta Orange.
And that yellow can of Canada
Dry Tonic Water that nobody wants!
And speaking of naming things, am I the
only person in this country who's laughing
when these commercials come on
television for "Snapper Lawn Mowers?"
Isn't there anyone else in this fading
Republic who knows what a snapper is?
- Whoo!
- A snapper is a pussy, okay?
That's what it means,
"snapper" means "pussy."
It's derived from an older, more
specific term, "Snappin' Pussy,"
which describes
a particular type of pussy,
one with good, quick muscular control,
kind of an elasticity in the vaginal wall
that can grab a hold of you
and give you a decent hump,
you know what I'm talking about.
A snappin' pussy!
But now, now "snapper"
means any kind of pussy
and they've named
a lawn mower company after it!
Now, I have seen a few snappers in
my day, never seen one that'll cut grass!
No, no, maybe do a little edging,
a little edging along the
driveway after a party,
that's all you can hope for.
But you know, "weed whacker"
you can understand!
Now, a lot of these company
names and product names
are influenced by marketing
and advertising people
and this next thing is about advertising.
By the way, if you should have
any cognitive dissonance
about the fact that I do
commercials for 10-10-220
and still attack advertising up here, well,
you're just gonna have to figure
that shit out on your own, okay?
Now, this is called "Advertising Lullaby,"
keeping in mind, of course,
that the whole purpose
of advertising is to lull you to sleep.
Quality, value, styles, service, selection,
convenience, economy savings, performance,
experience, hospitality, low rates,
friendly service, name brands, easy terms,
affordable prices, money-back
guarantee, free installation.
Free admission, free appraisal, free alterations,
free delivery, free estimates, free home trial,
and free parking.
No cash? No problem.
No kidding, no fuss, no muss, no risk, no
obligation, no red tape, no down payment,
no entry fee, no hidden charges, no
purchase necessary, no one will call on you,
no payments of interest till September.
But...
limited time only though, so act
now, order today, send no money,
offer good while supplies last,
two to a customer,
each item sold separately, batteries
not included, mileage may vary,
all sales are final, allow six weeks
for delivery, some items not available,
some assembly required,
some restrictions may apply.
So, come on in... come on in...
...come on in for a free
demonstration and a free consultation
with our friendly professional staff.
Our experienced and
knowledgeable sales representatives
will help you make a selection that's just
right for you and just right for your budget,
and say, don't forget to pick up your free
gift, a classic, deluxe, custom, designer,
luxury, prestige, high quality, premium
select, gourmet pocket pencil sharpener...
yours for the asking,
no purchase necessary,
it's our way of saying, "Thank you."
And if you act now, we'll include an
extra, added, free, complementary,
bonus gift, a classic, deluxe, custom,
designer, luxury, prestige, high quality,
premium select, gourmet
combination key ring,
magnifying glass, and garden hose
in a genuine, imitation, leather-style,
carrying case with authentic vinyl trim...
yours for the asking,
no purchase necessary,
it's our way of saying, "Thank you."
Actually, it's our way of saying,
"Bend over just a little bit farther"
so we can stick this big advertising
dick up your ass a little bit deeper! Pbbt!
A little bit deeper! Pbbt! A little
bit deeper! Pbbt! Pbbt! Pbbt! Pbbt!
"You miserable, no-good,
fucking consumer asshole!"
'Cause you do know,
folks, living in this country,
you're bound to know that every
time you're exposed to advertising,
you realize once again,
that America's leading industry,
America's most profitable
business is still the manufacture,
packaging, distribution,
and marketing of bullshit...
high quality, grade-A, prime
cut, pure American bullshit,
and the sad part is, is that most
people seem to have been indoctrinated
to believe that bullshit only comes
from certain places, certain sources:
advertising, politics, salesmen...
not true, bullshit is everywhere,
bullshit is rampant, parents are
full of shit, teachers are full of shit,
clergymen are full of shit, and law
enforcement people are full of shit.
This entire country... this entire country...
is completely full of shit
and always has been,
from the Declaration of Independence
to the Constitution
of the Star Spangled Banner,
it's still nothing more
than one big, steaming pile
of red, white and blue,
all-American bullshit.
Because think of how
we started... think of that.
This country was founded
by a group of slave owners
who told us, "All men are created equal."
Oh, yeah... all men, except for
Indians and niggers and women, right?
Always like to use that
authentic American language.
This was a small group of unelected,
white, male, land-holding, slave owners
who also suggested their class
be the only one allowed to vote.
Now that is what's known as being
stunningly and embarrassingly full of shit.
And I think... I think Americans
really show their ignorance
when they say they want
their politicians to be honest.
What are these fucking cretins
talking about?
If honesty were suddenly introduced into
American life, the whole system would collapse!
No one would know what to do!
Honesty would fuck this country up!
And I think deep down,
Americans know that.
That's why they elected
and re-elected Bill Clinton!
That's right.
Because... because the American people
like their bullshit right out front
where they can get
a good strong whiff of it!
Clinton might be full of shit,
but at least he lets you know it.
Dolle tried to hide it, didn't he?
Dolle kept saying, "I'm a plain
and honest man!" Bullshit!
People don't believe that!
What did Clinton say?
He said "Hi, folks! I'm completely
full of shit and how do you like that?"
And the people said, "You know
something? At least he's honest."
At least he's honest about
being completely full of shit.
It's just like the business
world, same as business,
everybody knows by now, all
businessmen are completely full of shit,
just the worst kind of low-life,
criminal, cocksuckers,
you could ever want to run into... a
fucking piece of shit businessman.
And the proof of it... the proof of it
is they don't even trust each other!
They don't trust one another!
When a businessman sits down
and negotiates a deal,
the first thing he does is to
automatically assume that the other guy
is a complete lying prick who's
trying to fuck him out of his money!
So, he's gotta do everything
he can to fuck the other guy
a little bit faster and a little bit harder...
and he's gotta do it
with a big smile on his face.
You know that big,
bullshit, businessman smile?
And if you're a customer, whoa,
that's when you get the really big smile!
Customers always get
the really big smile
as the businessman carefully positions
himself directly behind the customer
and unzips his pants and
proceeds to service the account!
"I'm servicing this account...
this customer needs service."
Now you know what they mean...
now you know what they mean when they
say, "We specialize in customer service."
Whoever coined the phrase
"let the buyer beware"
was probably bleeding from the asshole.
But that's business.
That's business.
But in the bullshit department...
in the bullshit department
a businessman can't
hold a candle to a clergyman...
'cause I gotta tell you the truth,
folks, I gotta tell you the truth.
When it comes to bullshit,
big time, major league bullshit,
you have to stand in awe...
in awe of the all-time champion
of false promises and
exaggerated claims... religion.
No contest! No contest!
Religion... religion easily has
the greatest bullshit story ever told.
Think about it... religion has actually
convinced people that there's an invisible man
living in the sky who watches everything
you do, every minute of every day,
and the invisible man has a special list
of ten things he does not want you to do!
And if you do any of these ten
things, he has a special place
full of fire and smoke and
burning and torture and anguish
where he will send you to live and
suffer and burn and choke and scream
and cry forever and ever
till the end of time...
but he loves you.
He loves you...
he loves you and he needs money!
He always needs money!
He's all-powerful, all-perfect,
all-knowing, and all-wise, somehow...
...just can't handle money!
Religion takes in billions
of dollars, they pay no taxes,
and they always need a little more.
Now, you talk about a
good bullshit story... holy shit!
Thank you!
Thank you. But... Thank you,
thank you, thank you.
Thank you very much.
But I want you to know... I want
you to know something, this is sincere,
I want you to know when it comes
to believing in God, I really tried,
I really, really tried.
I tried to believe that there is a God who
created each of us in his own image and likeness,
loves us very much, and keeps a close eye
on things, I really tried to believe that,
but I gotta tell you, the longer
you live, the more you look around,
the more you realize
something is fucked up.
Something is wrong here... war,
disease, death, destruction, hunger, filth,
poverty, torture, crime,
corruption, and the Ice Capades.
Something is definitely wrong.
This is not good work.
If this is the best God can do,
I am not impressed.
Results like these do not belong
on the résumé of a supreme being.
This is the kind of shit you'd expect
from an office temp with a bad attitude.
And just between you and me... between
you and me, in any decently run universe,
this guy would have been out on
his all-powerful ass a long time ago.
And by the way, I say "this guy" because
I firmly believe, looking at these results,
that if there is a God, it has to be a man,
no woman could or would
ever fuck things up like this!
So... so...
...if... if...
if there is a God, if there is,
I think most reasonable people
might agree that he's at least incompetent
and maybe, just maybe, doesn't give a shit.
Doesn't give a shit...
which I admire in a person
and which would explain
a lot of these bad results.
So, rather than be just another mindless
religious robot mindlessly and aimlessly
and blindly believing
that all of this is in the hands
of some spooky, incompetent
father figure who doesn't give a shit,
I decided to look around
for something else to worship,
something I can really count on,
and immediately, I thought of the sun.
Happened like that, overnight,
I became a sun worshiper.
Well, not overnight,
you can't see the sun at night,
the first thing the next morning,
I became a sun worshiper.
Several reasons... first of
all, I can see the sun, okay?
Yeah. Unlike some other Gods I
could mention, I can actually see the sun.
I'm big on that, if I can
see something, I don't know,
kinda helps
the credibility along, you know?
So every day, I can see the sun
as it gives me everything I need:
heat, light, food, flowers in the
park, reflections on the lake...
and occasional skin cancer, but,
hey, at least there are no crucifixions
and we're not setting people on fire
simply because they don't agree with us.
Sun worship is fairly simple.
There's no mystery, no miracles,
no pageantry, no one asks for money,
there are no songs to learn, and
we don't have a special building
where we all gather once a week
to compare clothing.
And the best thing... the best thing about
the sun, it never tells me I'm unworthy,
doesn't tell me I'm a bad person
who needs to be saved,
hasn't said an unkind word,
treats me fine.
So, I worship the sun, but...
I don't pray to the sun.
You know why?
I wouldn't presume on
our friendship, it's not polite.
I often thought people treat
God rather rudely, don't you?
Asking trillions and trillions of prayers
every day, asking and pleading and begging
for favors, do this, give me that, I
need a new car, want a better job,
and most of this praying takes
place on Sunday... his day off.
It's not nice, and it's no way
to treat a friend.
But people do pray and they pray
for a lot of different things...
you know, your sister needs
an operation on her crotch,
your... your brother was arrested
for defecating in a mall,
but most of all, you'd really like to fuck
that hot little redhead
down at the convenience store...
you know, the one with the eye
patch and the clubbed foot? Huh?
Can you pray for that?
I think you'd have to.
And I say fine,
pray for anything you want,
pray for anything,
but what about the divine plan?
Remember that?
The divine plan... long time ago,
God made a divine plan,
gave it a lot of thought,
decided it was a good plan,
put it into practice,
and for billions and billions of years,
the divine plan has been doing just fine,
now you come along
and pray for something.
Well, suppose the thing you want
isn't in God's divine plan.
What do you want him to do?
Change his plan? Just for you?
Doesn't that seem a little
arrogant? It's a divine plan!
What's the use of being God if every
run-down schmuck with a $2 prayer book
can come along and fuck up your plan?
And here's something else,
another problem you might have.
Suppose your prayers aren't
answered, what do you say?
"Well, it's God's will, thy will be done."
Fine, but if it's God's will and he's
gonna do what he wants to anyway,
why the fuck bother praying
in the first place?
- Yeah!
- Seems like a big waste of time to me!
Couldn't you just skip the
praying part and go right to his will?
It's all very confusing.
So, to get around a lot of this,
I decided to worship the sun,
but, as I said, I don't pray to the sun.
You know who I pray to? Joe Pesci.
Joe Pesci. Joe Pesci.
Two reasons... first of all,
I think he's a good actor, okay?
To me, that counts.
Second... he looks like a guy
who can get things done.
Joe Pesci doesn't fuck around.
Doesn't fuck around.
In fact...
in fact, Joe Pesci came through on a couple
of things that God was having trouble with.
For years, I asked God to do something
about my noisy neighbor
with the barking dog...
Joe Pesci straightened that
cocksucker out with one visit!
It's amazing what you can
accomplish with a simple baseball bat!
So, I've been praying to Joe for about
a year now, and I noticed something.
I noticed that all the prayers
I used to offer to God
and all the prayers
I now offer to Joe Pesci,
are being answered at about
the same 50 percent rate.
Half the time, I get what I want,
half the time, I don't,
same as God, 50-50,
same as the four-leaf clover
and the horseshoe,
the wishing well, and the rabbit's
foot, same as the mojo man,
same as the voodoo lady
who tells you your fortune
by squeezing the goat's testicles,
it's all the same, 50-50,
so just pick your superstition,
sit back, make a wish,
and enjoy yourself.
And for those of you who look to the Bible
for moral lessons and literary qualities,
I might suggest a couple
of other stories for you.
Uh, you might wanna look at "The
Three Little Pigs," that's a good one,
has a nice happy ending,
I'm sure you'll like that.
Then there's "Little Red Riding Hood,"
although it does have that
X-rated part where the Big, Bad Wolf
actually eats the grandmother,
which I didn't care for by the way.
And finally, I've often
always drawn a great deal
of moral comfort from "Humpty Dumpty."
The part I like the best, "All the
king's horses and all the king's men,
couldn't put Humpty Dumpty
back together again."
That's because there is no
Humpty Dumpty and there is no God,
none, not one, no God, never was.
In fact, I'm gonna... I'm gonna
put it this way... if there is a God...
if there is a God, may he strike
this audience dead!
See? Nothing happened!
Nothing happened!
Everybody's okay! All right?
Tell you what... tell you what,
I'll raise the stakes.
I'll raise the stakes a little bit.
If there is a God, may he strike me dead!
See? Nothing happened... Oh, wait...
Got a little cramp in my leg...
and my balls hurt...
plus, I'm blind... I'm bli...
Oh, now I'm okay again...
must've been Joe Pesci, huh?
God bless Joe Pesci! Thank
you all very much! Joe bless you!
Thank you very much! I appreciate it!
Bye-bye! Have fun! Good!
Thank you very much! Have a good
time! Have a good time! Thank you!
Good-bye!