Shit.
Sam.
- Hm?
- Sam, wake up.
What's wrong?
What'd you do, Tiger?
We didn't crash?
- You tell us, asshole.
I guess I fell asleep.
- Yeah.
With the engine running.
Fully charged.
Did you kill the battery, too?
You hear the radio?
There's a skating rink about 11 miles
from here. Big parking lot.
Ice skating or roller skating?
Just says they're open. Why?
Hockey players whoop more ass.
I don't know, dude. I've seen some
pretty bad-ass roller skaters.
At seven am?
All right. I'll come with.
Sam?
- Tad.
Awesome. Hey, uh, I work nights,
but I'll catch up with you guys for breakfast.
Okay.
I'm in 2-R up the stairs. Just crash
wherever. Uh, park in the side lot.
Rear doors touch the wall
so no one steals your shit.
All right. Yeah?
These all have mushrooms.
This dude's legit.
Why, 'cause he wakes up at
five in the morning to put jizz in his hair?
Mm. No, he's true.
Riri.
Who are you callin'?
Is it your business?
I get the bills.
I'm goin' to bed.
We're gonna drink.
Morning.
- Morning.
You the first to fall asleep?
Okay, I'm with The Ain't Rights
from Washington, D.C.
Uh, technically,
we're from Arlington.
Nice. Uh, and this is
for Seaside HCFM.
Not for The Zine?
I'll do a print version for that,
but this'll run on our college station.
- Uh, if that's cool.
- Yeah.
So, you guys working on
anything new?
Hm, yeah. A few songs.
Maybe enough for, like, a seven inch.
Sweet. Will you actually press one?
Yeah, if we can afford it.
Yeah, no, I really dig the analogue style.
Uh, which brings me to the fact...
you guys are hard to find.
Why no social media presence?
That's because booking more shows,
selling more records would blow.
It's not hard rock.
No one wants to starve, but when you
take it all virtual, you lose...
good texture.
- What do you mean texture? - Just...
You gotta be there. The music is for effect.
It's time and aggression.
Technical wizardry.
And it's shared live... and then it's over.
The energy can't last.
- Unless you're Iggy Pop.
- Yeah, well good for him
but I don't think I want to be in my 70s
still listening to Minor Threat.
- Tiger does.
- I won't live to be 70, so...
Okay, so, uh, this is a good seg
into one of my traditions.
Uh, for each of you,
name your desert island band.
Only one?
If I were to say Black Sabbath,
would I get Ozzy and Dio?
No caveats, just name the band.
Okay.
Misfits.
No, The Damned.
Umm...
- No, fuck it. Misfits.
- Poison Idea.
- Cro-Mags.
That's a good one, also.
Okay, say something, dude.
What about Steely Dan?
- Hm, no, Candlebox.
- He's a Juggalo.
Uh... Uh...
- Britney Spears?
Hey, hey, you're, you're...
you're gonna edit this, right?
I can chop it up a bit.
- No, you should let it go raw, man.
Um, when is this gonna air?
Like maybe we should plug the show.
Yeah, um...
My last show at the
Muni Center didn't end well.
Uh, lots of vomit, some fecal matter.
The county commissioner got wind
and pulled my permit.
You guys were already en route.
Nah, you gotta give us a kill fee.
- We went 90 miles out of our way.
I've got a back-up lined up.
Um, lunch, 50 percent cut on the door
and you guys would headline.
Is anyone still on the bill?
No.
♪ I'm always broke, and I'm alone.
I ask myself...
♪ What have I become?!
♪ I must be drunk, I must be stoned
♪ I ask myself what have I become?! ♪
Turn that shit off.
I gave you my cut, uh,
the house got theirs, but I didn't...
Split four ways it's six bucks each.
Six eighty-seven.
Eighty-eight if you just round up.
You dipshit fashion-punk
clown mother fucker!
Christ.
- Uh, easy there, Jujitsu.
Yeah, we don't want to go to jail, too.
- I think you just ended this tour.
- Fuck yes. Let's call it.
All right.
So we'd have to beeline to D.C.
We have enough for one tank.
We'd have to siphon the rest of the way.
That's not a problem.
We got rice and beans.
We could head up north,
take the 80 all the way.
What the fuck you doin', man?
Let me call my cousin.
I can get you guys a solid gig.
Where? Here?
The scene's dead.
You'd have to dip down closer to Portland.
I say we just gank his vinyl.
All right. So all set. Uh, matinee tomorrow,
doors at one, you guys are on at three.
I texted the addy.
- How much?
Uh, three fifty. Minus your tab.
And, um, just so you know, it's mostly
boots and braces down there.
The skins?
There's some at every show.
What? DMS? Sharp?
Uh, right-wing, or technically ultra-left,
but not affiliated.
But your cousin's cool?
Yeah. Yeah, uh, don't talk politics,
but stick with Daniel.
I'd tag along, but he and his girl are coming
here to crash. Gotta vacuum and shit.
So they're not like burning crosses or
anything, right? Like we just play rock.
Uh, I'd play your earlier stuff,
heavier stuff.
I usually keep the originals, but, uh,
since this one never happened...
Can I still run that interview?
Yeah. What station is it on?
Uh, FM 85.5, Breakfast of Champions.
Thanks.
Yo, Tad-pole.
I'm sorry I almost obliterated you, man.
Not a problem.
Take it easy.
At least the dude can draw.
Yeah, it's pretty sweet.
Yo, Pat.
You know,
there's something I never told you.
Or anyone, for that matter.
What?
Was that real? Ew.
Open your window.
You Tad's friends?
Oh, he sent us. Are you cousin Dan?
Daniel.
You guys look hammered.
- One night at Tad's will do that to you.
And if your girl's gonna be crashing...
- Don't mention that.
Okay, I was just...
- Yeah, no worries whatsoever.
Just shut the fuck up about him and me and her.
- Yeah.
Drummer? Drummer?
Using the house kit or using yours?
I'll use mine.
Okay, load-in's here.
That's bullshit.
Aren't Rights? Yeah.
Stage the rest in here.
Don't block the hallway. The owner doesn't
fuck around with the fire codes.
Sound check in 15, you're on in 20.
Got it.
Hey Tiger.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Are these guys not creeps?
They run a tight ship.
Except it's a U-boat.
Hey y'all. I got a dumb idea.
Where'd you say the power supply was?
It's like a mini-transformer
three females- like an XLR, but not-
- Testing, testing, one, two. Meow.
Got it!
There's no guitar.
Hey, we're not, are we?
This was your fucking idea.
You back out now,
I tell them you're Jewish. Go.
Evening, ladies and gentlemen.
We are the Ain't Rights or the Aren't Rights.
Either one.
♪ Two, three, four!
♪ Punk ain't no religious cult,
Punk means thinkin' for yourself
♪ You ain't hardcore 'cause you spike your hair,
when a jock still lives inside your head
♪ Nazi punks, Nazi punks,
Nazi punks! Fuck off!
♪ If you've come to fight, get outta here,
you ain't no better than the bouncers
♪ We ain't trying to be police.
When you ape the cops it ain't anarchy
♪ Nazi punks, Nazi punks,
Nazi punks! Fuck off!
♪ Ten guys jump one, what a man
♪ You fight each other,
the police state wins
♪ Stab your backs
as you trash our halls
♪ Trash a bank if you've got real balls
♪ You still think swastikas look cool,
the real Nazis run your schools
♪ They're coaches, businessmen and cops.
In a real fourth reich you'll be the first to go
♪ Nazi punks, Nazi punks,
Nazi punks! Fuck off!
♪ Don't you know, you'll be the first to go.
You'll be the first to go
♪ Unless you think! ♪
Fuck off!
Thank you. That was a cover.
What should we do next?
- Coronary.
This one's a treat.
Here.
What happened to fire code?
Yeah, sorry guys.
We had to make room for the headliner.
Cowcatcher, right?
Yes. Gotta clear out, okay? Here you are.
And it's all there. And you guys
follow me? Okay? All right.
I'll get you one more
for the road. Okay, come on.
You got that?
I'll be careful. I understand.
- Aw, shit. My phone...
- What?
My phone. I, I'll catch up...
- I got you.
Thanks.
- Yeah.
- Excuse me, all.
Holy shit.
Call the cops.
- Fuck that.
Hey, stop! Mother fuck!
I told you to follow.
- No!
- Go!
Go, go, go!
Uh, yeah. I, yes, I am. I don't know.
There's been a... been a stabbing!
She... Whoa!
God damn it!
- They didn't lock the door.
They didn't lock the door!
No! Don't talk and don't touch them.
Stay put! It's fine.
What the fuck happened?!
- Just give me a minute.
Something terrible.
Okay. It's okay.
- Shit.
It's okay. Don't worry. Don't worry.
Just get back inside.
- What the fuck's going on, man?
Up, in the room. Hey, go! Go!
Up the stairs. It's okay. Let's go.
Oh, what the fuck, man?
- It's okay, it's fine.
Uh! Uh!
Turn the PA down!
You didn't lock the door.
- You were right there!
Until I wasn't!
- Quiet!
Hello?
Yeah, we got cut off,
I was calling to report a stabbing.
A stabbing.
Did you call Darcy?
- He's on his way. He knows about that.
Not this.
You can't keep us here, man.
You gotta let us go.
We're not keeping you.
You're just staying.
You're up.
- What the fuck that supposed to mean?
Just relax!
Everyone just relax.
Cops are coming.
See how easy that is?
- Mother fucker! What have you done?!
- Amber, chill the fuck out!
- Yes, please.
Darcy here?
- Not yet. I need six hundred cash.
You just signed out three fifty.
Somebody is dead.
Still gotta keep the books.
What else do you need?
A true believer.
How 'bout two?
Maybe she's not dead.
I'm just saying...
There's not a lot of blood, you know?
So like, maybe she's just...
And who are we to say if she...
Come on, man. What are you doing?
- Oh, fuck, man!
There it is.
Oh my god.
We gotta go.
We gotta fuckin' go right now.
C'mon. We didn't see shit.
We, we, we were so drunk...
All right. Just wait, okay?
Cops are on the way.
Above and beyond, gentlemen.
You need me to do it?
- Nope.
- Won't even be the first time.
Hurry up.
- Go.
All right. That's it.
Let them see it.
The knife.
It's an inch too short for felony possession,
so you don't have to worry about the...
Actually, give me that money back.
- What?
- It's like vouchers and shit.
We'll hold it for you. Come on.
If you do any time, we'll double it.
I'll talk to them.
You the victim?
- Yes, officer.
Kneel down,
both of you, ankles crossed.
That's the owner.
I, uh, called him, too.
All right, let's give 'em
some room to work, folks.
Are you the owner?
Yes, ma'am.
Cowcatcher.
Clear out.
Hey, where are the cops?
- Get your stuff.
- What about us?
- What are you doing?
- I'm sorting it out. Just hang tight, Amber.
Your set was pretty good.
What?
What was the name of your
second to last song?
Uh, To... Toxic Evolution.
It's fucking hard, man.
That's the one I did her to.
All right.
Well he's got six bullets.
For real?
- If we all go at once...
Christ, hold off a second.
- For what?
- We haven't done anything.
- Doesn't matter.
Okay.
They're called cartridges.
The bullet is the part that enters
your brain if you keep talking shit.
And this gun only has
five cartridges, not six.
'Cause they're big as fuck
and only five fit the cylinder.
So please shut the fuck up
and don't test me.
Reece, you're making it worse.
We sit.
And we wait.
And we die.
Not if you sit and you wait.
It's just the one to 911 at 3:45.
And then mine was at 3:47.
- You called?
911 called back and I answered.
Be clear. Who else knows besides...
You said Daniel's cousin.
Tad. There was a text from him
last night with our address
but he doesn't know anything.
Except who they are, where they are
and maybe where
they're supposed to be next.
Fuck. Check emails.
They played their set to the crowd.
Then we'll assume the wide world knows.
And they'll be tracking that.
Give it to me. I was trying to buy some time
and contain this until we could...
Contain?
It was pretty rapid fire.
- I appreciate your initiative
and we all love Werm.
He's a brother.
Ah. Then you might have
visited him in prison.
Makes a difference.
Now we're all in the stew.
For an impulsive act.
For a selfish act. Under my roof.
You see a way out of this?
For them? No.
- We still have to find one.
Okay. This is good.
No guns. You have a "no trespassing"
sign posted at the residence?
We got "beware of dogs."
That's better.
Does anyone even know we're in here?
No one who cares. Tad?
I think we go.
- I think we go too.
The next person that moves...
- Everyone okay?
Just about.
Gabe?
- Yeah, open up.
No.
- Where are the cops?
Okay, do you want me
to open the door
or do you want me
to blow your fucking head off?
Back the fuck off!
- What's going on?
They're trying to run at me!
Do not shoot them.
- You know what? That's on them.
- Where are the cops?
Give them the gun.
Say again?
It's over. Give them the gun.
Okay, I told you they just tried to run at me...
- Then take the bullets out!
Just hand it over.
Now. Do not shoot them!
Is Darcy here?
- He is.
- I am.
- Gentlemen, I'm the owner.
- Why the fuck didn't you just tell me...
Truly sorry about this.
I'm playing catch-up here myself.
They're playing a fucking show.
Uh, thank you. But we open the door
for the police. Or we keep the bullets.
Uh, the cartridges.
- I've got no problem with that.
Okay. I handed them the gun. I'm gonna head out now.
- No you're not.
Let him open the door.
- Hang on.
He gave us the gun.
Nobody is letting me do anything.
I gave you the goddamn gun, okay?
- How we doing?
He's right.
Pat, do the math.
Where are the police?
- It takes a while out here.
- Stay back.
I just want to be sure that
no one else gets hurt in the meantime.
Okay. I gave you the damn gun.
- Get off!
Get him now! Get him now!
What's happening?
- Shh!
- Justin.
Shouldn't have locked the door.
Shit! Sam!
Come on.
Get the bullets.
Alright, load the gun.
- How's it going in there?
- Not good!
- Fine! But we would rather wait for the police.
Justin?
He's fine.
But he's gonna wait, too.
Understood, gentlemen. Okay.
Think they know?
I think they're smarter than you!
Darcy.
Man.
I apologise.
We'll do it here.
Stage it up the road.
Hey, what was that gonzo shit, man?
- So, in a tournament
I snap his arm or he taps out
and we all go get burgers.
Snap it.
- Come on.
Look we got the gun. Why don't we just let him...
- Wait. Wait. I don't want it.
Alright? I don't, I don't feel good with it.
Who wants it?
Not me.
No, I, I can't shoot.
I can.
- No, not you.
Then fucking keep it.
- Keep it, Sam. I'll take it when I'm up.
When I let go, what are you gonna do?
Butt fuck everyone in the room.
You're gonna say
"crisscross applesauce." Say it.
I'm gonna say crisscross apple sauce...
Nice.
- Now lean against the chair.
Hey.
Is there another way out of here?
No.
You fed 'em yet today?
It doesn't matter. They're professionals.
You might lose a couple by morning.
Maybe a bunch.
Like I said, they're pros.
They earn.
You'll be compensated.
Christ, how many people on that list?
It's twelve hundred for a prospect,
two for a bait dog. No studs, no champs
unless you want to pay
twenty grand a head.
This might cost you your
livelihood, Clark.
As long as it doesn't cost me mine,
you're covered.
There are gonna be cops,
so clean up the residence.
Maybe leave a roach in that ashtray.
Put Daniel on that door and
bring the van around.
Shit. Keys.
In there with them, I guess. I don't know.
- We need 'em.
I got a ton of shit to do.
- Go on.
This is a fire hazard.
I wouldn't put Daniel on the door.
Fine. Plenty to do.
Where's Daniel?
He stepped out; I'm covering.
Everything okay?
Meet me at the utility shed.
This a new ride?
Yeah. Just turning it over.
Think it's getting choked. Wrong filter.
She's a beaut.
What's up?
Need some of the squad.
Red laces only.
Tonight?
- Now. The list.
This is everybody who knows?
- Yeah. Including the band.
Knows what?
Manageable.
From here on out
not a single name gets added
unless they have red laces.
That's 80 people in there.
You plus four. Give Gabe the keys
in case we have to play valet.
We're losing light.
- Got it?
- Yeah.
Oh, watch out.
That could be asbestos.
- It's not asbestos.
- You don't have a phone, do you?
They took it. Hers too.
I want to search her, okay?
- Careful. That one could be a live wire.
- It's a speaker wire.
What'd you find?
Uh, Fleisch wolf?
Fleisch means, uh, flesh or meat.
Like a fleisch salad. It's German.
So meat-wolf?
Yeah.
This shit's solid.
- Great.
There's nothing here.
Okay. Empty out your pockets.
Come search me, faggot.
Just shoot him.
Come on.
Can I get up?
On the chair.
Slowly. Slowly.
Turn 'em out.
Come on, man. Other one.
Good call.
Turn it out, for fuck's sake.
What is that? Give that to me.
Hand it over.
- Oops.
- Wait, was that a phone?
Oh, shit. Point it,
point it at the door...
- Oh, maybe it's the police. It's a raid.
- Are you serious?
- Shhh.
- Fuck off, Ilsa!
Yo, quiet. Okay Justin, don't move.
Nobody move.
- Now if we get all behind...
- Nobody talk.
Careful, now.
Smoke this.
Deal.
And if the cheery does something
that you don't like, shoot.
Thank you, Amber.
Get comfortable.
Pretty smart for a Nazi.
I'm not a Nazi.
How do you fall for this shit?
Let's just say the people
who hurt me weren't white.
Any of them women?
It's a problem where I grew up.
Guys.
What about tonight? Think we got a
white people problem?
- Guys, shh.
- Fuck you.
It looks like we tripped our main.
Our back-up gennie is fired up
but we're gonna to have to call it
a day, do some troubleshooting.
We'll try again on Sunday.
No door charge.
Hell, free drinks from two to four.
Those of you attending the racial
advocacy workshop on Wednesday
assume it's on
unless you hear otherwise.
And remember,
this is a movement, not a party.
Alright.
Stay safe! Godspeed.
Who hasn't smoked yet?
All right, you guys
are gonna come with me.
You're not worried they'll talk?
They got priorities.
Tell them the party is on us
if they hole up for a couple of days.
Put this fire out first.
Grove Street?
My dope, nigger stamps, in case one of these
meatheads gets booked for possession.
All right. Let's get y'all somewhere safe!
Treasure?
Daylight. Underneath.
They're moving our gear.
- Yes?
Gentleman. We're loading you out.
Are the cops here?
They've come and gone.
It got a little complicated.
We are so fucked.
- Uh, I'm getting hoarse.
Can you hear me
if I speak at this volume?
- Yes.
Good. Um, and can we please
elect just one voice?
Yes.
Okay, now, you're trapped.
That's not a threat. It's a fact.
Well, we have a loaded gun.
That's also just a fact.
Uh, we have plenty more guns on hand.
We just want you out. Not harmed.
Now the firearm you have
is not registered.
I wanted it out of the picture
before the authorities arrived
but you refused, so here we are.
Bullshit.
- Yeah.
Here we are.
Oh, I do apologise for
my associates. They panicked.
Yeah. No shit, man!
- Listen. Listen.
No one is trying
to wipe the slate clean.
Whatever you saw or did
is no longer my concern.
You tell whoever you want
whatever you want.
All I ask is that you understand
you were held here for your own safety
before you were released.
Okay. Yes, thank you.
But just, uh, just to be clear,
the police are coming back?
They've come and gone.
Well, that's what concerns us, man!
I just want that gun out of the picture.
Okay.
- Careful, man.
- Sorry.
What do we do?
We dig through the fucking floor.
While they just wait?
They could shoot us at any time.
Yeah, but they haven't.
How do we even know that they have guns?
They have guns.
No question.
We're gonna trust you?
- We've got zero leverage.
Ask for a phone.
For the gun.
Right.
And what about him?
Yeah, I mean the minute
we give it up, what if he just like...
Then I'll wrap him up.
Okay. Should we see what they think?
- Mm-hm.
All right. Uh, we'll give you
the gun for a cellphone.
Sorry, no.
Okay, well how about
a registered firearm?
Funny. Justin, you alive and well?
I'm alive.
Okay, good. Gentlemen,
I hope you appreciate the situation.
Things have gone south, no doubt.
But you know if you don't hand over
that gun, it won't end well.
You see, for all I know,
I... I come to my place of business
and there is an out of town band locked
in a room with an unregistered firearm.
Oh, come on!
- Somebody's hurt inside there.
And I, I... and maybe there's a
hostage, too. So what do I do?
Am I within my rights to intervene?
Should I kick down the
door and start shooting?
Or, can we just remove the
guns from the equation.
These are my questions.
You got 30 seconds to answer.
Okay, hold on. Hold on.
Great, anyone got any smart ideas?
Justin, get on the floor.
Get on the fuckin' floor right now. Go.
Right, Sam. Come round here.
Slowly, I want you to take the gun from me.
- Okay.
- You got it? - Got it.
Okay, nice and easy.
You play nice and I'll be nice.
Please, don't do anything.
This is fucking retarded.
- No one's saying it isn't
but we either hand over the gun
or we open fire with it.
I vote for that.
- You don't have a vote! Okay?
I mean we're taking chances either way, so...
- We are so fuckin' dead, guys.
At least this way we find out.
All we're doing now is buying time.
For them.
- Amen.
At this point, I'm just fucking curious.
Okay. We'll give you the gun.
But we're gonna keep the ammo.
Fine. Safer for everyone.
All right, let's move this fucking couch.
All right. Keep still.
Okay, stand back!
- You got it.
Here we go.
- May I approach?
- No! No, I'm gonna throw it.
Careful. It was a gift.
They're killing us.
- Keep the gun!
Get the fuck off!
- Okay, okay!
Okay, okay!
Oh my god!
Put it up!
Holy fuck.
Yo, help me move the couch.
Help me move it.
Oh, shit.
- This'll be over soon, gentlemen.
I'll fuckin' crush you.
Whores!
Get the box cutter!
Get the fucking box cutter
out of his hand!
Tell me when he's out.
- Okay!
Pat! Pat! Look at me. Look at me.
Look at me. Shush! Shush!
He's out. He's out!
Oh. Oh, fuck.
Put pressure on it! Put pressure!
- I know. I know. I know. Just breathe.
Breathe.
He's not out!
You got this?
- Shhh, shhh.
How long does it take,
until you know?
For sure?
Holy fuck.
Oh, Jesus.
Any and all firearms.
Clark will handle it from here on.
He give you an ETA?
You said no calls.
Right. Good. Phones...
What happened in there?
- Set Neal up for tomorrow.
New drywall, pour a floor.
Tell him we had a leak.
Door with a frame, too.
- What happened?
Uh, a bit of a maelstrom tonight.
Visiting band hurt one of ours.
- Who?
- Emily.
Maybe Big Justin, too.
What the fuck are we doing, then?
Let's get in there.
We're not coming apart
is what we are doing.
We're saving questions until this
pig fuck is transferred off site.
Darcy.
Okay. Last chance
if anyone needs to take a leak.
I lost the gun.
You held on longer than I would have.
I'm going.
There's no air shaft.
There's no sewer system. No nothing.
There it is.
- What time is it?
- It's not daylight.
It's something.
Out the way.
Fuck.
Now look for a door.
Just let me know.
Hey.
I'm sorry about your friend.
Okay, move.
- Fuck.
Is there a lock?
Other side, maybe.
We're burning time.
Wait, but... well there's,
there's ventilation.
Six inch ducts. Good luck.
- Shouldn't we look around more?
- We just did!
Go. Go, go, push.
Heroin.
It's not about her or us.
It's a big-ass bunker.
- Give me your hand.
- Big-ass dead end.
- Give it to me.
Hold it up. Up there.
All right, look away. Look away.
- Maybe we can use this to our advantage.
We're done.
I'm done. Okay, you can close the door
behind me if you want to strategise.
We're not ready!
- What do you think they're doing out there?
That's just it. We don't know.
- We fucking know they mean us harm!
It's just, if they have guns, okay,
why haven't they mowed us down already?
We can't just go missing.
They need us found.
Right. Grab some shit.
Get ready to run.
Then we die.
Yeah, but the longer we wait,
the surer that is.
Tiger, You ready?
- Almost, man.
We can't take it so seriously.
We gotta treat this like paintball.
What?
Rick Silva.
Helped organise the paint ball
for Skate-o's bachelor party.
And we were short a few players
to book the whole field
so they paired us up
with these ex-marines.
And the first few rounds,
these guys just tore us to shreds.
I mean zero casualties on their side.
And I just cowered behind
these trees 'til I got shot.
Covered in paint. But Rick...
Tiger, you done?
Okay.
Pat, you're done, too.
Sorry, man. We gotta go.
That's okay.
- Was that a pep talk?
Ready?
Now we won't all live, but, uh,
I don't know, maybe we won't all die.
Here.
- No, I'm just gonna run.
I got it.
All right, fuck it.
Simon and Garfunkel.
Desert island band.
Prince.
I, uh...
I'm still the Misfits.
- True school, man.
Are we going?
Yeah.
Madonna and Slayer.
Here we go.
Watch it!
What the fuck?!
They loaded us out.
How many exits are there?
Uh, the main, the back,
maybe the kitchen. I always...
What about windows?
See for yourself.
- What the fuck.
- Quiet.
Oh, shit.
Should we hide?
Do whatever you want, man.
We should split up.
Totally.
- Fuck.
- Tiger!
Tiger!
Shit.
Oh, shit.
Save it.
Fas! Fas!
Voran! Fas! Fas!
Oh, fuck.
Come on.
They're everywhere!
Where's Reece?
It's us.
Come on, move.
Sam, look.
Fleischwolf.
It's a song.
It means "meat grinder".
Up! Up! So ist brav. So ist brav.
You're retiring him?
- He's worked up.
Send in another one.
Send two, finish it.
Kill that feedback first.
And if I send in two fight dogs,
what do you think they'll do?
Send me in there. I'll finish up.
Just give me the rules.
Alright.
Blades only. Sloppy is fine.
Try not to hit the bone.
Okay.
Take Jonathan.
- Brute squad.
- Keep him caged until we tag out.
He breathing?
A little bit, yeah.
Let him bleed.
Later is better for time of death.
Keys?
No.
They're coming.
I can't do this.
- Get back!
- No!
Where's Emily?
What the fuck are you doing?
Hey!
Which one did it?
- Werm did it. - Bullshit.
Which one?
- What did they tell you?
What, you want to know?
You want him to know?
Know what?
- Werm found out that she was leaving
but she didn't say that it was with you.
Meat grinder.
That song was their cue.
You should go.
Get goin'.
This is taking too long.
Gabe?
You didn't want Daniel on door duty.
Why?
Nothing concrete.
He and... and Emily...
Little lovebirds.
Recognise this?
No, sir.
Of course not. You were still handing out
leaflets when these boys made their bones.
It's from last Easter.
Supposed to disappear after the boot party.
He just started talking.
Amber's alive saying Werm did it.
Never mind that.
You. Werm saved us all.
Sam?
It's okay.
I mean, it's not okay.
You didn't know either?
- He's with us.
- Not where.
We gotta split.
This has a wider duct, I think.
We're not gonna fit through there
Daniel, uh, he can help.
Why? Who's he?
A traitor. If they don't
already know, they know now.
I can get us out of here.
Wow. A conspiracy.
No, just a cluster-fuck.
There is still blades and fangs for the visitors,
but we are getting lean on time.
Now, if you have to shoot, shoot once.
If more than once keep it a tight grouping
'cause you'll be digging the slugs out yourself.
As for Daniel and Amber, they can...
What did we forget?
There's a river on two sides,
the quarry's on another.
We can parallel the main road back,
go for help.
Well, how will we get past the door?
I know something you don't.
Good, what?
I know where we keep...
- Too slow.
Should we go? Now?
We have the gun. I guess.
Yes.
- Yes!
Give me two.
Easy! Not her!
Don't fire!
- Fas! Fas!
- No!
- Sam!
We're never getting out.
Fuck
You know, I'm lucky.
I guess at least
they were gonna shoot me.
Three'll do, gentlemen.
The fourth can disappear.
Time to start the clean-up.
I'm gonna need a push broom.
This is supposed
to have happened already.
Time to sprint.
- Yes, sir.
Well done.
Thank him.
Nearly got away from me. Us.
Shouldn't we be panicking?
I'm hungry.
I can't die here with you.
So don't.
You know, feel free just to...
Hey, I want the rest
of your pep talk.
Oh no. It no longer applies.
Oh, come on. I'm curious.
It was paintballing;
you were cowering.
Yeah, Rick Silva.
We were getting slaughtered
by these legit Iraq vets.
It totally applies.
Full camo, a thousand dollar
automatic paintball guns.
They knew real war
and they played real war.
Tactics, hand signals, flanking.
Just wiped us all out.
So Rick gets fed up
and says fuck it.
Didn't care about getting shot.
Didn't take about taking cover.
- It was hopeless, man.
So, the last match,
the whistle blows
and he just tears out there,
full jackass
in... in sneakers and cut-offs
and he wipes out
their whole team.
Doesn't stop.
Just keeps running
and laughing and shooting
until they're all dead.
Pretend dead.
And we're up against real guns.
Yeah.
Either way, we can't play real war.
Let's pretend.
For you.
We're just mopping up tonight.
You already earned these.
Maybe push Neal,
depending on the mess.
Start looking for
a new house band.
We really gotta
get back to a routine.
You think Cowcatcher's
gonna talk?
I'm more worried
about their habits.
Really have to stay away
from that nigger dope.
There's a bad batch
doing the rounds.
Good to go.
We're set.
This all hinges on
nothing having happened here.
Now, let's be clear...
This should keep him
alive for another hour.
I would consider it a personal favour
if he dies with meat in his teeth.
Come on. Come on.
The bite command is Fas.
It's all you'll need.
Disregard. Just shoot who is left.
They don't have
to be accounted for.
Forensics is no longer a concern.
We call this in late,
all is for naught.
You guys got any 12 gauge?
- Not in the office.
Try the bar.
- How many shots you have left?
- Three.
- So you have one extra.
No shells.
Behind the bar.
Better get started.
- Shit!
- Easy! Easy!
Easy!
No buckshot!
- What's happening?
Dog freaked. And turn this shit off!
I tried! It's not coming
from our mixer.
Go, we got this.
And don't tell Darcy.
Or Clark.
We going?
Hey!
Down there, dip-shit fashion punk
clown mother-fuckers!
Turn around!
- Shazbot!
What? What, who is that?
Odin himself.
Give me the shotgun.
- No, I got the shotgun.
Then you go down
this fucking hole.
Three shots?
- Yeah.
You hear me fire twice,
you come down no matter what.
This is a trap.
- Yeah, no shit.
You wanna go tell Darcy?
He's gonna be pissed.
Watch my back.
Fuck this.
Get Gabe, man. We need two
down here and one up there.
Who's got the nine?
- I think Alan does, but I'm not su...
- Oh! Fuck! Block it!
Pat!
He's got three shots left!
Bitch.
Gabe!
- Amber!
- Yeah?!
Uh, never mind!
Two shots left!
Nice fuckin' try.
Go fuck yourself!
Oh shit!
Pat! One shot left!
Fuck.
Zero.
Oh, shit!
Got him.
Totally.
Flabbergasted
that motherfucker.
If I had any idea...
Any more dogs?
People?
No. Not here.
They're up the road.
I don't want to go to jail.
Does anyone know
how to hotwire a car?
No.
I'd stay off the road anyway.
Are you gonna shoot me?
Where's Werm?
We sent him home, but I wouldn't...
- Stay quiet 'til we're out.
It's the residence.
What are they doing?
- Something you don't want to see.
We can call the cops
when we get to the orchard.
Did you see them die?
Two. Not the third.
I think I'm going.
Call the cops
when you get there.
If you disappear, I'll find you.
I will.
I promise.
You should go, too.
Just hedge our bets.
You've got three rounds.
And I've seen you pump a shotgun.
Fair enough.
Do you believe him?
Shh.
- Nimm futter...
Nimm futter!
Nimm futter! Nimm futter!
- Jesus.
- Nimm futter!
That ought to be enough.
Lass es! Lass es! Lass es!
- So ist brav.
- Wipe it down.
You think they'd leave the engine on?
Yeah. It'll run
the gauge down too.
Call this in.
Aus, Aus.
You got the dog?
I got the dog.
Tie him up.
Give me your gun.
I don't have one.
I'll shoot you either way
if you don't hand me one.
Throw it.
They're making it our fault.
You were trespassing.
It looks fishy to me.
The cloth is to make it seal.
I wouldn't do it like that.
They got my gun.
- Shut up.
- Listen.
So we're doing that?
- Why else would we walk up here?
I don't know. And I was gonna
ruin the crime scene.
Oh. I thought we'd
leave a new one.
This is a nightmare.
For us all.
Tell me those stupid
fucking words are his last.
Do you have a phone?
It's funny. You were
so scary at night.
We need the police.
I know what it is.
What what is?
My desert island band.
Tell somebody who gives a shit.
♪ When the sky is grey
♪ And the moon is hate
♪ I'll be down to get you
♪ Roots of earth will shake
♪ Sinister purpose
♪ Knockin' at your door
♪ Come and take my hand
♪ Burn away the goodness
♪ You and I remain
♪ Did you see the last war?
♪ Well, here I am again
♪ Sinister purpose
♪ Knockin' at your door
♪ Come and take my hand
♪ I can set you free
♪ Make you rich and wise
♪ We can live forever
♪ Look into my eyes
♪ Sinister purpose
♪ Knockin' at your door
♪ Come and take my hand
♪ Mm-mm-mm-mm...
♪ Mm-mm-mm-mm... ♪
MUSIC: 'Right Brigade',
performed by Bad Brains
♪ You can't disappear anymore
♪ I see your face lurking
outside the window
♪ You say you're a trife,
I'm a bore
♪ You touch yourself,
put your face in the pillow
♪ But the funny thing about you is
♪ You remembered to leave it behind
♪ And the funny thing about me is
♪ I'm a member of the Right Brigade
♪ Makes no difference to me
♪ What side you choose,
what side will lose
♪ All there is to perceive
is what I want
♪ And I know how to get it
♪ But the funny thing about you is
♪ You remembered to leave it behind
♪ And the funny thing about me is
♪ I'm a member of the Right Brigade
♪ Right Brigade
♪ Right Brigade ♪