♫ Silent night ♫
♫ Holy night ♫
♫ All is calm ♫
♫ All is bright ♫
♫ Round yon Virgin, Mother and Chi..♫
- I have an urgent delivery.
Please sign
- Tell him to take his present and
shove it up his ass,
so if there is anything else up there,
so it will shift  very nicely.
- The package is back.
He says he's still too vulnerable to accept it,
but he wishes you a merry Christmas.
- Tell him to...
Tell him to take the damn package.
It is not a Christmas present
It is dvds, his tooth-brush and some underwears.
- He says it is not a present,
even though he'd wanted to give you one.
It's just few things you've left behind
reminding him of you
and it's too painful.
- Take it back
and tell that bastard it's only fair
that he is the one hurt for a change.
There is plenty of his crap lying around here
and that is painful too.
He could at least have the balls
and pick them up in person.
- He says he misses you
and if it is not too much trouble
would you mind picking up your things,
then he can see you before the year is out.
- Oh, his lordship misses me...
- Hmm, hmmm...
- Wow, very interesting.
Tell him to accept that fucking package or
I’ll throw it all in the trash
and, since I want my cds back,
tell him to be more specific about
when I should drop by.
- When would it be convenient for him to visit ?
He doesn't want to cause you more stress.
He is just very sorry and
wants you to have a drama free Christmas.
- Wait a minute.
He wishes me
a drama free Christmas ?
Oh, that cake are fucking cakes !
- He had tears in his eyes.
- Fine...
he can come by if he wants to.
I'm not doing anything.
Maybe some nice little presents...
I don't care. Give me the package.
- He had tears in his eyes ?
Oh, yeah... well...
I could drop in on Christmas eve.
I'm not really in a festive mood, anyway
if he has no plans...
- And of all the people in the world,
he wants to spend Christmas eve with you.
It's hard for him to admit it
after all that happened,
but it's you or no one.
- Tell him to come over and I stuff the chicken,
but he can at least bring the wine
and not some two bucks shop either
and not Christmas tree or other romantic crap.
- Okay, I'll buy the tree
but it pisses me off that he falls over that tacky shit.
- Merry Christmas.
I love you.
- I love you too.
♫ Sleep in heavenly peace ♫