Honey?
- Frank?
- What's the matter, he kicking again?
No, it's time.
You always make me feel so...
Frank!
- You're awful.
- All right, let's get ready, huh?
Frank?
Oh, honey,
you better go wake up Chris.
Chris.
Come on, I got your number.
Come on.
Thattaboy.
- Dad, what time is it?
- What time is it? Time to get up.
I have to drop you off at Charley's house.
You have to go to school from there.
- Why?
- Well, I wonder why.
- I don't know.
- "I don't know."
- Oh, is Mom having the baby?
- Yes. A trick she does every 11 years.
- I guess so.
- Why don't you get dressed...
...and don't forget your books.
- Okay.
- Dad?
- Yeah?
Anything happen to her? I saw on TV
in a movie once, where the mother died.
Well, you know something?
Things like that
happened a long time ago.
They don't happen that way anymore.
She had you, didn't she?
Yeah, look at the size of you,
you big ox.
Okay, now, here you go.
Let's get ready. Attaboy.
Why can't I go with you
to the hospital?
We'd love to have you, but the doctors
don't allow little boys in hospitals.
If I have my tonsils out again
I can go there.
You'd be there for a week
and we'd be home in three days.
You young whippersnappers.
You're not like the old team.
Out with old Mr. Dunson, out on the
plains and prairie, driving those cattle...
...getting their tonsils out in the middle
of the night, no doctors.
Oh, boy. You're not a chip off
the old block there, scout.
Well, maybe Charley
won't like having me around.
Charley won't like having you around.
Charley only sees his own boys two
Sundays a month and he loves kids.
Now, you young whippersnapper,
kiss your mother goodbye.
Listen, we'll give you a call
as soon as we find out...
...whether you've got
a baby sister or a brother.
I don't care, as long as you're okay.
And you give me one of the puppies.
Charley!
Honey, your book.
- Hi, Charley!
- Okay, Lenore, good luck to you.
Call me, Frank. Call me.
Well, pal, let's go and whip up
some French toast.
I'm having my baby.
Nurse, you know what they call them?
In Ireland, my mother used to call them
the "wee cuddies" and the "wee cubs."
The wee cuddies and wee...
Where could you get that?
Wee cuddies and wee cubs.
I hope I have one like that.
Would you please come to the labor
room now? It's the time to go back.
- The labor room?
- Yes.
- All right.
- This way.
How did you know about
the wee cuddies and the wee cubs?
I learned about them a long time ago.
- You speak Gaelic? Are you Irish?
- Yes. No, Scottish.
- Scottish? And you speak Gaelic?
- I do.
- You do speak Gaelic?
- This way.
An Irish and a Gaelic.
An Irish and a Scotsman.
- An Irish and a Scotsman.
- Yes.
Hang on to my hand.
Honey, I'm not very brave.
Oh, this little guy's gonna kill me.
- Well, maybe I'll get a doctor.
- No, no.
He's just different than Chris,
that's all.
I tried to talk to the doctor
and make him understand...
...but I couldn't make him understand.
It seems like it's different.
Honey, you better get the nurse.
Nurse, hurry up, please.
- You better go to the waiting room.
- Just a minute, please. I love you.
I'm glad. I'm glad we decided to
have the baby, aren't you?
We both want it.
Don't worry about a thing.
It's not gonna tie you down,
is it, sweetheart?
Are you gonna feel trapped
like you did last time?
- Calm down. Take a deep breath.
- I can't!
Take a deep breath. Calm down.
Relax. Try to relax.
Take a deep breath.
Hey, listen, have you got something
to stir the coffee with?
Yeah, here, use that. I've been using it
for the past three hours.
You get used
to the taste of lead in coffee.
There is an overabundance of lead
in all the things we eat nowadays.
We're slowly but surely
poisoning ourselves.
Fine world to bring a kid into, fellas.
- I could cite examples...
- You don't have to lecture.
Take a look at that smog.
What difference does it make...
...if we breathe it or eat it?
- Maybe we'll adapt to it.
I'm an exterminator. We service
the Beverly Hills-Westwood area.
Here. Here's my card.
I'm not trying to drum up business
or anything. No.
The point is, years back, we developed
this spray to kill roaches...
...and other household pests.
Well, all we ended up doing
was creating a new breed of roaches.
- Is that right?
- Bigger, stronger and harder to kill.
You wanna play poker?
Five-card draw.
- Come on.
- Might as well.
Let's clear some of this stuff away
and get going.
I just hope my wife isn't gonna have
any trouble, you know?
She did the last baby in 45 minutes.
- No kidding.
- That's a fact.
I thought they said
the second one came faster.
You got nothing to complain about.
My wife's been in labor for six hours.
Son of a bitch of a thing
stole my 50 cents!
Hey, hold it.
Here's your 50 cents.
No, really. No, no. Here's 50 cents.
Go on. Sit down and read a magazine
or something.
You know what's the biggest problem
in Beverly Hills?
Snails. Yeah, snails and slugs.
They can wipe out a lawn
in just a few weeks.
Folks feel sorry for them.
They're not like
your usual pest, you know?
Folks just hate to see all them snails
laying on their lawns, dead.
Snails and slugs and bugs.
Any of you guys
in a happier profession?
I think we've got
a really effective anesthetic.
We'll check you before
we really do anything.
- You know, I hurt...
- But you're doing just great. Just relax.
- It's been different than...
- You've done your share, we'll do ours.
She's fully dilated.
The head's on the perineum.
- I know something's wrong.
- It's nothing really wrong, honey...
...it's just a very, very big baby.
- Gonna be fine, but I need your help.
- I know something's wrong.
How big was your last baby?
How big, did you say?
Seven pounds, 4 ounces. I told you
that this baby was different than Chris.
This baby is just gigantic.
It's probably 10, 101/2,
maybe even 11 pounds.
Got a gigantic head,
but she's got a big pelvis.
And she's got plenty of relaxation.
I'm trying to cooperate.
All right, all right. Relax. Relax.
This thing is just immense.
Now, we're just putting forceps
on the baby's head. Just breathe deep.
Don't push, just pant.
Now, we're just easing the baby out.
- Something's wrong.
- All right.
Now, we just cut you.
You didn't feel that, did you?
- No.
- Okay, fine.
Now, the baby will be out
in just about 30 seconds.
Davis! Davis! Wait!
What does my baby look like?!
What's wrong with my baby?!
Doctor!
- Doctor!
- Davis, out of here!
The umbilical cord's been severed.
Looks like it's been chewed off.
Where's the baby?!
The baby, doctor!
- Get off of me!
- Get your hands off me!
Darling!
- Lenore! Lenore!
- Come on, let's go!
Let me go! Let me go!
Let go of me!
- We're gonna calm you down.
- Let me go! My wife!
Who stole my baby, doctor?
Don't. Don't touch me.
Don't you touch me.
They stole my baby.
Frank!
I don't want my baby to be dead!
I don't...
Tell me my baby isn't dead, please.
I assure you, Mrs. Davis,
your baby is very much alive.
Oh, thank you. Thank you.
Located a broken skylight
on the third floor.
Blood and excess tissue on the roof.
Lieutenant, what's it look like to you?
Something small.
Doctor.
She's coming out of sedation now.
Lenore?
Can you hear me, darling?
Somebody might have abducted our baby
and I'm holding this hospital responsible.
That hole in the skylight isn't large
enough for a full-sized human being.
There's no other way out
of that delivery room.
- The doctor's correct.
- Let's not have a discussion about it.
I've asked your husband
to submit to some tests.
And I've refused.
You've never been exposed to
radioactivity and radioactive material...
...or undergone extensive x-rays?
- No, doctor, I told you.
Well, we can't rule out genetic damage.
I notice you did inquire
about abortion eight months ago.
Doesn't everybody inquire about it now?
It was just a question of convenience.
- We decided to have the baby.
- We all make mistakes.
I apologize for that crack.
Let me talk to you outside. Come on.
You're not afraid of me, are you?
I've always been afraid of you.
Especially those eyes.
I wanted a boy so badly.
I think he was probably very frightened.
I know he's different.
Yeah, I just...
I think he was probably afraid
they were gonna hurt him.
He's not ugly.
Oh, you're so exhausted, sweetheart.
You don't know what you're saying.
I'm gonna check up on those two.
I don't trust them.
I mean, can you imagine?
Can you imagine those guys,
trying to blame us?
We are the parents, sweetheart.
- I'll be right back.
- Okay.
Doctor Norton decided
your wife can go home.
- First thing in the morning.
- You realize...
...it's in everyone's interest
to keep this quiet for the time being...
...at least until we can find out
what's become of the infant.
- You have heard no word about it?
- No.
I don't see how it could survive
without clothing and nourishment.
- Of course, like any animal, it may be...
- Well, it's not an animal, doctor...
...you know that very well.
Whatever it is,
you can't classify it as an animal.
It's human, doctor, and that's
what's disgusting to you, isn't it?
It kills like an animal.
And when we find it,
we're gonna have to destroy it like one.
Well, I don't care.
I suppose you have
to do what's necessary.
I'm glad you feel that way.
I only hope your wife
understands as well.
What's there to understand?
- Better not to think about it.
- Hey, look...
...why not say good night to your
wife and maybe I drive you home.
No, thanks.
Okay, darling,
I'll see you in the morning.
Stay on duty.
Police still offer no explanation
in the five deaths...
... which occurred early today
at Saint George Medical Center.
Officers are still working
around the clock.
Sources at the hospital alleged
the deaths resulted...
... from attacks by an infant
born only today in a mutated form...
... but officials declined comment.
This station has acquired information
naming Mr. And Mrs. Frank Davis...
... of West Los Angeles as the parents
of the infant in question.
The whereabouts of the newborn child
are not known.
They named us.
The bastards, they named us.
Barbara, would you
come here for a minute, please?
- Yes?
- I have to pick up my wife...
...at the hospital tonight. Reschedule
the Sturbridge dinner for tomorrow.
- I think Mr. Clayton wants to talk to you.
- And about the Marcus affair...
...I think we can have cocktails at 6:30
tomorrow. I know he wants to approve...
...the campaign by the end of the week.
- I think you better see Mr. Clayton now.
All right.
I'll be right back.
- Well, well, come on in.
- Hello, pal.
You must be exhausted.
You eaten anything?
Get Frank a couple of poached eggs
on an English muffin...
...with a side of bacon
and a tall glass of fresh orange juice.
Should do the trick.
Don't want you collapsing.
Frank, don't let it get you down.
These things happen,
or at least that's what they say.
- Who's they?
- I spoke to the hospital.
They give you information?
Well, I got connections over there,
you know.
I'm the vice-chairman of the fundraising
committee. If there's anything I can do...
No. Thanks.
I'm getting her out of there tonight.
You think that's wise?
Say, Barbara told me
you want to rap with me.
Yeah, Frank.
Frank, you...
- You've accrued three weeks vacation.
- Yeah.
You think it'd be a good idea
if you took it now?
I can't, Bob.
I mean, I got the Marcus account...
...and the Sturbridge campaign.
I'm just bogged down in work.
Besides, I need to work.
It keeps my mind off things.
Frank, we're running
a public-relations business here.
Our job is creating an image. And right
now, well, you're a little controversial.
See, our clients want
their PR men to be anonymous.
Maybe after a little while,
when you're a little less of a celebrity.
You're not taking those accounts
away from me, are you?
I mean, not now. Last-minute?
These things happen, Frank.
Look, you know O'Connors down
in accounting? He's got a retarded kid.
Insists on keeping him in the house too.
Well, nobody thinks a thing of that.
Nobody blames him.
We're not talking about a retarded kid
and you know it.
We're talking about
a monstrosity of some kind.
Yeah, well, maybe we better
not talk about that.
Bob.
I wouldn't wish this on my worst enemy.
Just that I...
I don't know what to do, Bob.
How to behave.
And they...
Putting microphones in my face. They're
asking me questions I don't understand.
You know, what you need
is a good public-relations firm...
...to handle all of that for you.
That's very funny.
Bob...
Bob, this is all gonna be all right,
isn't it?
When whatever this thing is
is dead. Right?
Maybe it already is.
Look, Frank, why don't you go down
the service elevator...
...you won't have to meet
all those media people.
Bob...
Take care.
Have them empty out his desk.
Send his personal articles to his house.
He won't be coming back.
- Mr. Davis, what did it look like?
- I got nothing to say.
- What are you afraid of?
- Get out of my face.
I got no comment.
Get that goddamn thing out of my face!
Get out of the way!
- What did it look like?
- I don't know.
Never mind my baby!
Leave my wife out of it, you understand?
Aren't we almost home?
We'll be there in a few minutes.
I feel better already,
getting out of that terrible place.
I don't have to take more shots, do I?
I don't like taking shots.
- I don't like being made to go to sleep.
- Well, I engaged nurses in three shifts.
I'm surprised anybody
would even wanna work for us.
- Well, Dr. Norton took care of it.
- Oh, good.
And I'm gonna be there all the time.
- What about...
- Yeah, I told the office...
...I have to have those three weeks
vacation they owe me.
Oh, what about that Marcus account?
That was very important to you.
You're more important.
What about Chris? Have you told him?
Does he know anything?
I spoke to Charley.
He kept him home from school.
Hasn't told him anything.
- Good.
- Sooner or later, he'll switch on the TV.
It's only so long you can keep
a secret like that.
Dad, why can't I go to school or go out
or have friends over?
Chris, I can't tell you now, son.
You'll have to trust me.
You do trust me, don't you?
- Sure, Dad.
- You have to spend all your time...
...with Charley this week.
You wouldn't mind that.
Chris. Chris, hey, buddy,
you don't wanna hurt his feelings.
I like Charley, but I wanna
see Mom and the baby.
- The baby's not home yet.
- Is it sick?
Yeah, that's right, son.
The baby's sick.
And everything here's a mess.
So it would be much better...
...if you stay where you are.
- You tell Charley to let me watch TV.
- Okay, put him on.
- Okay.
Okay, Frank. Look, we'll take care
of everything. Hey, I had an idea.
I'll take Chris up to the lake
for fishing.
Okay, Charley. Thank you.
Oh, and give my love to Lenore.
Thanks, Charley.
Hunting and killing babies
doesn't seem to be my specialty.
So, what do you want, a transfer?
Well, my wife's in her eighth month.
Since I started this,
she hasn't gotten any rest.
Me being so involved
really brings it home.
Besides, I guess you know
we lost our last baby.
Look, you're lucky you don't have
grown kids nowadays.
People without children
don't realize how lucky they are.
Take these.
Make you feel much better.
Did you see it, Mrs. Davis?
Surely you must have gotten
one glimpse.
They say it has teeth and claws.
Did you know that?
How should I know that?
Were you aware that it killed
another person just last night?
A musician on Santa Monica Boulevard.
He was on his way home from work...
...about 2 in the morning...
...and that was the last anybody
saw of him.
They found him in an alley.
Well, they can't be sure that it was...
There's no doubt about it.
The wounds are the same
as the doctor and nurses suffered.
Well...
- Well, what do you want me to say?
- Just say anything you feel.
- What's under that napkin?
- There's nothing there.
A recorder! A tape recorder!
I'm a nurse. You can tell me anything.
- Who are you working for?
- I really am a registered nurse...
...and I write a little on the side.
She's taking interviews
on a tape recorder.
Get out.
Frank?
We just have to get rid
of everybody.
- Let's not have any more nurses, honey.
- All right.
We'll let them all go.
Should have known better...
...than to trust anybody.
Actually, already in excess
of $ 100,000 has been allocated...
...by the university for examination
of this phenomenon.
We have some of the leading men
in the field.
It's hoped this might lead to a
breakthrough to a better understanding...
...of why mutations occur.
You wanna experiment on it?
My department has already cautioned
the police about excessive violence.
If it could be dispatched with a bullet or,
better still, some kind of a gas.
Undoubtedly, it's small and any kind of
bodily harm, especially from gunshots...
...or explosives...
- In other words, you want me...
...to sign away the body?
Well, it's your right. After all,
you are the child's father.
It's not my child.
That's very wise...
...to disassociate yourself emotionally.
Just sign each copy, please.
- Pen?
- Give him a pen.
You know, it seems that out of every
tragedy, out of every evil...
...some good can come if we
only apply ourselves.
I suppose that's gonna be in all
the medical journals?
History books?
"The Davis child."
"The Davis monster."
It's like Frankenstein.
In my opinion, this will be remembered
long after each of us is forgotten.
When I was a kid, I always thought...
...the monster was Frankenstein. Karloff
walking around in big shoes, grunting.
I thought he was Frankenstein.
Then I went to high school
and read the book...
...and I realized that Frankenstein
was the...
...doctor who created him.
Somehow the identities...
...get all mixed up, don't they?
One must not allow oneself
to be impressed by escapist fiction.
You forgot one.
Pen.
Frank, darling?
Hi, darling.
Mrs. Davis, I don't suppose you
took the pills I gave you.
You really should, you know.
Maybe it's all the pills I've taken
over the years that brought this on.
You really shouldn't be downstairs.
Maybe you'd both like
to have dinner with us.
I have wonderful lamb chops
in the refrigerator.
No, I'm afraid not.
Honey, why don't you go down
to the basement and get a bottle...
...of that nice Beaujolais. Won't that
go nicely with the lamb chops?
We have quite an extensive wine cellar.
It's one of Frank's many hobbies.
My husband's a many-faceted man.
I'll show these gentlemen to the door.
I'll get that wine.
Oh, great, great. Good. Good.
Boy, that basement's filthy.
How long had she taken birth control
pills before this pregnancy?
- Thirty-one months.
- You realize...
...I came from the East
specifically for this matter.
I realize that it is a police problem.
But once the thing is killed,
it becomes a medical problem. Now...
...you are in charge of that department?
- Yes, I suppose so.
- Now...
...nobody knows how
this thing happened.
It's really a matter of speculation
and perhaps that's for the best.
After all, if we find out that the cause
is medication that we manufacture...
...and it was administered over
a long period of time...
...it'd be bad for you and worse for us.
We're susceptible to lawsuits.
We'd think the government hadn't tested
and approved of those products...
...that we put on the market.
What do your interests recommend?
Absolute destruction of this thing.
Well, they've already signed over
the remains to the university.
But if there was nothing left of it...
...we would be most grateful to you.
You have had
a very successful career...
...until this freak incident.
You know, it could
work out for the best.
We have an opening on the board of our
research and development department.
Now, we wouldn't want people
to lose faith in us, would we?
- Hello?
- Dr. Norton, please.
No, Dr. Norton stepped out
for a moment. May I take a message?
Tell him they've cornered the infant
at the Hawthorn School...
... in West Los Angeles.
That's a few blocks from here.
Ask the doctor to get over there
if he can. Thank you.
I have to go out for a while.
All right.
You don't mind staying alone?
I'll keep everything warm.
Wait a minute, I'm Frank Davis.
I wanna see Lieutenant Perkins.
All right, take him.
Wonder what's the matter with him.
Screwed-up genes or something.
Wait here.
Davis, how the hell did you
find out about this?
There was a phone call for Dr. Norton.
I took the message.
My son Chris goes to school here.
I've been here a million times,
PTA meetings.
- Your kid goes here?
- That's right. He's in the sixth grade.
Listen.
Probably just a coincidence.
Look, Perkins, I want this thing
destroyed as much as anybody else.
- I realize that.
- Yeah, you realize.
Then why is everybody looking at me?
Yeah.
Like it's my own flesh and blood
or something.
Well, it's not! Understand?
It's no relation to me.
Nobody's looking at you.
Say, you have my deepest sympathy.
You and your wife.
Is it all right
if your driver drops me off...
...a block from my home?
I don't want my wife to see me.
You don't want her to know
you were here tonight?
I don't think she'd know how to take it.
Maybe I didn't do the right thing.
I'm just trying to show everybody
I feel the same way they do.
- I'm no different from anybody.
- We know that.
I got a boy, 11 years old.
He's healthy.
- He's brilliant.
- I understand.
You don't have
to keep telling us that.
We realize that.
Look, I gotta go back on duty.
Take him wherever he wants to go.
Davis said his kid went to this school.
Now, why, in all of Los Angeles,
would it happen to show up here?
Maybe it's looking for somebody.
I'd like us to all get together again
and be a family.
- I'm really trying very hard, Frank.
- I know, darling.
I can see that.
Wouldn't it be a great idea
to bring Chris home?
He's better off where he is.
Lenore, did you go out?
Lenore?
Lenore.
For chrissakes, answer me.
Are you feeling better?
Where the hell have you been?
- I've been straightening up.
- I've been calling you.
I've been all over the house,
straightening up.
Where? You weren't downstairs.
Didn't you hear me calling you?
Honey, there's a good movie on
with Paul Newman.
I gotta get something in my stomach.
- Excuse me.
- Yeah.
Chris come back here today?
I said,
has Chris been back here today?
No.
Why do you say that?
You wouldn't lie to me?
I know you wanted Chris to come
back, but I specifically told you...
Chris.
Chris?
Chris, are you hiding someplace?
Don't fool around, now.
I wish somebody would respect
my feelings around here.
Why are you watching that stuff?
I thought you wanted
to watch a movie.
Who are you calling?
Don't call anybody.
Please don't call anybody.
Who are you calling?
- How's Chris?
- Had a hell of a time keeping him...
...from the newscasts and papers.
But the teacher sent over schoolwork,
so he's been keeping busy.
You've been with him all the time?
We just got back
from that fishing trip.
He hasn't been out of my sight
for a minute.
- Look, you wanna talk to him?
- No, I don't wanna talk to him.
- Hi, Dad. When can I come home?
- Did you come back here today?
Is the baby home
from the hospital yet?
Did I do anything wrong?
- Hey, how about something to eat?
- No, I'm not hungry. I wanna go to bed.
- I'm sorry, Charley. I'm not mad at you.
- That's okay, kid.
Honey, I want you to make love to me.
I want you to hold me and love me.
You know, there are other ways.
- Come on, sweetheart.
- There's no ice in there.
I'll get the ice. Wait a minute,
I'll get the ice. Wait, I'll get the...
Chris?
Oh, my God. Chris!
Lenore?
What were you doing down
in the basement?
You know.
What are you gonna do?
What are you doing?
Why are you so anxious
to be the one to do it?
Who is it? Mom? Dad?
Frank. Frank, wait. Wait. Wait.
Frank, he could've killed you
when you were upstairs sleeping!
- Let go of me.
- He could've killed you!
Do you know why he didn't kill you?
Hello?
- He knows you're his father.
- What are you, crazy?
He knows.
He knows you're his father.
Don't worry. Don't be scared.
I'll protect you.
It's a boy, you know. It's a boy.
- I'll protect you.
- Chris, look out.
I hit it. I'm sure I hit it.
Charley! Look out, Charley!
Charley!
Go on, get down. Did you see it?
Did you see it? What does it look like?
It's no relation to us, Chris.
It can't be.
See what your baby did to Charley?
What did you do?
Will you tell him
about the doctors in the hospital?!
Lenore, take my son upstairs.
The doctors at the hospital were trying
to suffocate your little brother.
He just wants to live.
You should've called us soon as you
began to suspect it was near the house.
It's lost a lot of blood.
And it's my opinion that our troubles
are very nearly over.
- So shall we go?
- I wanna leave some men here.
In case it decides
to double back to the house.
I would...
I would like to go with you.
- Haven't you done enough already?
- No. Not yet.
You have to be the one to do it,
don't you?
Have you seen it?
Got a real good look at it?
It was too dark. It wouldn't matter.
I could do it.
You may have done it already,
if it doesn't stop bleeding.
Will you excuse us
for a moment, please?
We just can't take a civilian...
Look, I advise you to let him come along.
After all, it found its way home by itself.
It may be that it'll search out its father,
especially when he put a bullet in it.
What have we got to lose?
One more life.
You know how to use a gun?
Beg your pardon?
Do you know how to use a rifle?
Sure.
We'll issue you one,
for your own protection.
Okay.
The shot that wounded the infant was
fired not by the police but by its father...
... public-relations executive
Frank Davis...
... who currently is accompanying police
on the manhunt.
That's it.
That's how it can travel
without anybody seeing it.
Units converge
at interceptor point 682 of project 9401.
Close off block sections 21218...
Divide units to cover all Sacatella,
L.A. River and...
Drains 26 and 34, 1663560-O...
... are now completely closed off
by our units.
Hold position and stand by.
Let me have that.
Davis, you stay right here.
Here, take this.
Let's go. You stay here.
It's back there somewhere.
The damned fools must have walked
right by it. Now, I want that thing.
- Where's Davis?
- I don't know.
- He was supposed to stay here.
- Davis! Davis!
Stay where you are,
we'll come get you!
Davis! Davis, come back.
Frank!
Frank, do you hear me?
Proceeding to Los Angeles River inlet,
as ordered.
No.
I know it...
I know it hurts.
I know that.
But everything's gonna be all right.
See, I was...
Well, I...
I was scared, like you are.
No, no. You mustn't cry.
Because if you cry,
they'll hear you and they'll come.
No, no. It's all right.
It's gonna be all right.
Okay.
Davis, come on out!
Come on out, Davis!
Where are you?
Davis!
Davis has been seen moving through
the tunnel in possession of the infant.
Keep her here.
Drain stopped up ahead, impassable.
Can you hear me, Frank?
It can't be saved. It's gotta die.
Just drop it and get the hell away
from it. Do you hear me, Frank?
Frank! Can you hear me?
All right, just stop there.
Stop right there.
It can't hurt anybody.
Look, lock it up. Study it.
But let it live, please.
Put down your weapons. It's wounded.
It can't hurt anybody.
Just drop it. Just drop it.
Just take it easy and drop it.
Back away. Back away!
If you fellas shoot, you're gonna shoot
me. Put the weapon down. It's harmless.
That son of a bitch dies here and now!
Drop it and stand aside, Davis.
In one second, whether you're holding it
or not, I'll put a bullet through it.
- Don't shoot.
- Kill it, lieutenant. Kill it!
Kill it! Kill it now!
Stop firing! Stop firing! Stop firing!
Yeah, I'm bringing them home.
Lieutenant Perkins,
call for you on the private line.
Right.
Perkins.
I understand.
Another one has been born in Seattle.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
[ENGLISH]