I don't know how it started!
- Jacob, how much did you pay for this?
- Do me a favor?
Don't talk about my car.
It's a 1928 Ford.
How do you have patience with this man?
C'mon C'mon!
All good.
He is alive!
Turn it up!
...an Orthodox-Jewish organization, Irgoun,
is responsible for the attack in Palestine.
Hated by the British, feared by the Arabs and
rejected by the majority of the Jewish community,
including the "Haganah", another secret Jewish
armed force. An attack repudiated by the majority.
Jacob, come on, turn it on!
Let's go.
Hey, Bobby!
Bobby, where are you going? Bobby!
"Fanelli"
By God, don't you watch where you're going?
It could have killed me!
- Damn, it was you who came in suddenly.
- Are you alone?
Yes, do you see anyone else?
Let's go...
Let's go!
It was at the Kingston Hotel.
British were hit.
Irgoun claimed
responsibility for the attack.
90 deaths.
Shit! For what?
Why did they do it?
- Jew? - Yes and you?
No.
I'm an Arab from Jerusalem.
Said Chahine.
Bobby Goldman.
Where you go?
Fanelli. They have a radio.
Where is Cathy?
Guess what!
It has problems?
She is studying in Colombia.
Said, this is Jane from Montreal.
What a perfect moment!
She's a "digger" like me.
Archaeologist, if you don't mind.
You are cute!
Said Chahine, what are you working on?
What discussion did I just interrupt?
Palestine.
- Said's family is from there.
- Said...
It's a beautiful name, and...
It is...
...I said that maybe Palestine
belonged to the Jews for
two thousand years, but
we have lived there forever.
Yes, but the number of Jews
has been higher for years!
Can we have a drink?
I would love to dance.
Hello!
How are you?
- I'm sorry I arrived late!
- Can you keep quiet?
- I can't think!
- What you mean? - Girls!
Girls? Do I have breasts?
4, 3, 2, 1!
Happy New Year!
You must understand, no one should
force my people to leave their land,
their houses... Jerusalem...
No one is asking you
to leave Jerusalem, Said!
It is a partition, so that both
can live together in peace.
Don't be so naive, please!
To be blunt, listen to me!
Jews will never share Jerusalem!
No one will force my people to leave
their land, their home... Jerusalem...
What about "Fanelli"?
I'll pay for the trip. Let's Dance.
I don't want to see you like this.
No way!
I'd rather be with Jacob.
I have a new car.
Is it true that it's new?
Shut up and go in.
Come on, get in quickly!
It's a 1940 Cadillac; Show
more enthusiasm, please!
When you said you paid almost
nothing, tell me how much is nothing?
I'll give it to you, Said!
What?
The car is yours.
No, it's a joke!
No, I don't need it anyway.
I will go to Palestine tomorrow.
This is wonderful!
I want to be there in time to
participate in the vote and face the Arabs.
And I want to fight!
Shut up, Jacob!
Said, no, wait!
Don't listen to him!
Oh no!
Oh, Bobby!
Listen, I love Said too.
But in reality, he is Arab...
Go to hell!
Said, wait!
He doesn't know what he's saying!
He's right.
- What you mean?
- Read.
What is this?
It's my uncle's.
He gave it to me before my father died.
You want me in Jerusalem
for the same reasons!
Crazy!
They are both crazy!
Look at each other, look at each other!
How can you leave her?
And you, don't you worry?
How can you do this?
Their immigration expectations are good.
Damn Jews! Trying to enter illegally?
Those fields of war are unbearable.
- American from America?
- Yes.
New York.
And Jewish. You have nothing
against New York, do you?
Do you have a kiss for me?
Oh, no, no kiss, no, no!
To Jerusalem!
I will show you my beautiful princess!
Look at this!
Isn't it beautiful?
My car!
Do you have any idea what you're doing?
Excavations stopped until the vote.
Not bad, we just found
an old passage in some
ruins, something from
8th century Judaism.
What the fuck was that?
Something fell.
It's the engine.
I shouldn't have taken it all off!
Curse!
Get your damn asses out of the
car! What the fuck is wrong with you?
Damn it, it's on fire!
Get up, it's burning!
Give me a hand!
What?
The road is now really very dangerous!
Where does it come from?
From New York. Why dangerous?
It's a perfect place for an ambush.
Excellent!
- There's no other?
- Just one, from Tel-aviv to Jerusalem.
Bobby, look!
This is Tel Aviv.
To get to Jerusalem from here, we
need to pass through many villages.
Arab Villages!
There are 3 strategic places:
the sacred monastery of Latroun,
Bab el Oued, and Castle.
Full of riches!
Napoleon, Solomon, everyone knew
that whoever achieved this position...
would have the root,
and whoever has the root...
There is Jerusalem!
- What did he say?
- It's the English.
Stay where you are.
Whose weapon is this?
It's mine!
Follow us.
Wait a moment.
You know why we carry weapons:
to defend us, because they don't!
Please excuse us.
Where are they going to take her?
To the nearest police station.
The nearest post is in an Arab Village.
She is Jewish.
- Take me too. - Take her too.
Bobby, wait for me!
- Where are you going?
- Stay there!
You know how I am! Damn English!
After the vote, the English leave.
Nobody knows what happens.
My mother is scared.
She doesn't understand, because we've
always lived together and well in the city.
For the celebration, Jews offer grain.
We give bread and honey at
the end of the Easter celebration.
Is not the same thing.
She is scared.
She's starting to think that...
all Jews are enemies.
I'm sorry, Bobby.
I offended you.
What did he say?
That every Jew is an enemy.
Thank you very much.
- And you, what do you think?
- I think my mother is obsessed
for her beliefs. Oh, come on!
My God!
Can you say that again?
There...
the holy sepulchre.
Built where Jesus died on the cross.
That is Mount Moriah.
Muhammad ascended to heaven from there.
Over there...
the wailing wall.
Part of the temple that
was built by King Solomon.
If God isn't here, Bobby...
It's nowhere!
Do you know what Jerusalem means in Hebrew?
Jerusalem?
The city of peace.
If I forget ancient Jerusalem,
my right hand will forget to count.
And my tongue will
cleanse the roof of my mouth,
if I do not proclaim
Jerusalem the highest!
He asked what I believe, Bobby.
I am scared.
We have the same God...
you and I.
This day will be engraved
in the memory of men.
After five centuries of Turkish dictatorship
and 26 years of British protection,
the assembly of 56 UN countries will decide
whether Palestine will be divided into two states,
one side Arab and the other Jewish.
M. Husseini, you represent the Palestinians.
What do you think of the vote?
If the UN votes for partition,
the Palestinian will not accept it.
He will throw Jews into the sea.
Where did we go wrong, Rodgers?
We leave chaos behind us.
Thousands of people expect
us to massacre each other.
But as far as all together,
none of our soldiers. None!
From the tragedy of Europe, we know
that the foundation of a strong State
It is the only guarantee not
to repeat the same tragedy.
Tonight, the world will decide our fate.
For those who suffered most among us...
our brothers who died in the fight.
Let's give our blessings.
For this day, for all of them!
Jacob, do you know these people?
Don't worry Bobby, sit down.
Hi Jacob.
- And the vote?
- We are waiting.
Americans are putting
pressure on Greeks, Filipinos...
The UN is a puppet!
We are 40 million Arabs united.
We cannot allow it!
Come, my prince!
What happened to the brothers?
In Damascus I had to buy
15 rifles with my own money.
It seems that our
brothers don't act like us.
I fear...
that we have to fight alone!
Decisions are being
made and will not take long.
I should be in Cairo in 2 hours.
How are your roses?
You didn't come to ask
me about roses, Gordon.
If the United Nations gives the State
to the Jews, we will be out in 6 months.
Until then there will be no
intervention between Arabs and Jews.
London doesn't want any more bloodshed.
Now that the Jews want a state, if they
give it to them, we will see what to do.
In a few months the Arabs
"throw" them into the sea.
So do the English wash their hands
in the midst of this hellish chaos?
Simply defending the
interests of the former British.
Iraq, Suez Canal, oil...
the Arabs are our allies.
Our mission...
should be to bring peace
between Arabs and Jews.
So, I withdraw.
- What will you do about the vote?
- I already know what will happen.
Good luck!
The General Assembly is meeting.
We can start now.
Afghanistan...
no.
Argentina. Argentina... abstention.
Australia... yes.
Belgium... yes.
El Salvador... abstention.
Ethiopia... abstention.
France... yes.
As for the public...
I hope they don't
commit any interference...
in voting and debate.
They must trust this system
as I trust their behavior.
Greece... no.
Guatemala. Yes.
Ukraine... yes.
South Africa... yes.
Soviet Union... yes.
United Kingdom... abstention.
United States... yes.
Paraguay... yes.
Venezuela... yes.
Yemen... no.
Yugoslavia.
Abstention.
Come.
Hang on.
Close the doors, please!
Now...
catastrophe is upon us!
May God protect Palestine!
May God protect us all!
- Hello.
- Said!
What's? I'm waiting for you.
I can't talk now because...
He's Jewish, don't talk to him again!
Come on, take this!
It was our father's.
Are you blind, Said?
I see nothing but hate.
It's not what our father taught us.
This is "Jihad", Said.
"Jihad" is our duty.
No, Amin.
God doesn't want war.
He doesn't want war.
What is happening? Where are they going?
Around the city!
We're going to fight!
It is with her?
Not me...
I tried to kiss her, but
the partition was declared.
Yes, and she pushed him!
Did you call Cathy?
Did you ask if she's coming?
Are you scared?
I understand.
They're scared.
Go home. You two, come back!
One is enough, Bobby.
Idiots! You are few.
The Arabs outnumber them by millions!
- Don't you understand?
- 2000 years in this country...
Yes, we have lived here for over 2000 years.
You didn't vote and I have to leave?
Go to hell! Shut up!
Would you kill, Jacob?
Said, would you kill?
Would they kill each other?
So shut up!
What the fuck is that?
Come back! come back!
Should we go.
The English held them back.
Damn crazy people!
Stop them!
Give me the gun!
Go!
Open up, open up!
Jacob, Jacob!
I'll take you inside!
Go home tomorrow!
Days of violence followed
the partition of Palestine.
The Jewish barracks in
the ancient city are on fire.
I know I know!
No lectures, please, I'm exhausted!
Jacob didn't want me to come.
And that?
Well, now I'm here.
You're on my side, aren't you, Bobby?
What Jews must do is wait.
No Jew should leave home, the
kibbutz, or work without permission.
Father, father!
Here.
Yael!
They're evacuating Scheikh Jerrah,
Katamon, all the mixed districts.
Taking refuge in the Jewish districts.
They are leaving the area free for the
Arabs. We have to change the situation.
Fight hard!
They attacked the Semíramis Hotel.
Call Amin, quickly!
If his brother is there, Said! Go!
Amin!
Where is Amin?
Amin?
Amin!
Amin.
Y... Said!
S... Said.
- Amin, Amin!
- Said, Said!
Amin!
Help!
Swear to me, Said!
Avenge daddy!
Take my gun.
Swear, swear, Said!
My little brother!
No!
Yes.
I swear, my little brother!
I swear to avenge his death, before God!
He'll come with the money right now.
All good?
Very well my friend.
- You do good business, huh?
- Yes.
You need weapons, I need money.
Do you have a cigarette?
I don't like this one, I prefer Americans.
Too weak for me.
I'll bring one in two minutes.
Hey Daoud! Daud!
After the attack on the Jewish Agency,
our mission will be to take
the Jewish district of Jerusalem,
cutting off the only supply route.
We must starve the Jews of Jerusalem,
we must strangle Jerusalem.
We can lose Tel-Aviv, but
we cannot lose Jerusalem.
If we lose it, we will
never have a State.
- We are 2000, they are millions!
- Isaac, do you think I don't know?
There's not much we can do.
To fight!
Do you want us to fight with a few weapons?
Yes, we will fight with Haganah!
They're children, David, not an army.
Today, Haganah will be an army.
Maybe we can avoid a war. The King
of Jordan. We can negotiate with him.
- Go talk to him
- Me?
Talk to him and buy time.
Time!
Salam.
Shalom, your majesty.
We said the word peace twice.
May God show us the way.
Thanks.
I will be direct.
If they want my intervention
with the Arabs they
must deny the proclamation
they made as a State.
If Mr. Ben Gourion refuses this proposal,
I fear it will be an inevitable war.
His majesty...
We can never accept it.
You know. Of course we want peace...
but we also want our own land.
Your Majesty, you
know that if there is a war
We will fight with all our might.
I know.
We can live together.
We were created to live together.
Your Majesty, we are
your only true friends.
I wouldn't be standing before
you if I didn't think the same.
I believe, with all my heart...
that it was...
It was divine providence
who brought the Jews.
But be patient.
How can you ask for patience
after suffering so much in
the extermination camps?
Yes I understand.
Our destinies are in the hands of Allah.
Let's hope he wants to support our cause.
We have to take Castle.
Abdel Kader takes Castle!
We must, we must!
For a day, a few hours...
The time needed for
important trains to pass.
Never ask how, okay?
But... we have 20 men...
Get more...
Where?
I don't know, I don't care!
Everyone, everyone must
participate in this operation.
Did you understand? Each one!
Bobby, the first.
You are the first.
We must go to Jerusalem to find
Golan and make a deal with him.
No Isaac, that doesn't interest him.
David said we need every Jew, every one.
For months, Jews have been
trying to regain control of the road.
We have been fighting them for months.
Many of our men are dead.
We need weapons now.
Otherwise the Jews will cross, and all
these sacrifices will have been in vain!
They promised tanks, give them to us.
We need weapons now!
Come on, calm down!
All your men are irregular.
They don't know anything about weapons.
Is not true! We need weapons now!
What if the Jews surpass you?
And take the weapons we give you?
So, my brothers?
How can you call us brothers...
and then...
refuse to help us?
At least we cut their
supply load from the US
and Europe this week
so they can't get help.
Oil is one thing,
Palestine another, brother.
If the Jews don't take the road,
we can pursue them from Jerusalem
and from every village in Palestine,
in less than two weeks.
Come on, traitors!
Syrians, Egyptians, Iraqis,
Lebanese, all traitors!
The Palestinian blood
will be on your hands.
David!
David, hi!
All good?
We have to take the Castle, we need men.
So Irgoun is no longer
a bunch of killers?
There's only a handful of us left!
You cut the Bab el
Oued road and we attack.
Why don't we take Castelo together?
It does not give.
Do you want my men
and I to risk our lives?
Yes.
Two women starved to death in Jerusalem.
What you want?
Money?
There's nothing to buy.
No.
I want guarantees.
Think about it.
Shalom. Shalom.
The Arabs closed the
only road to Jerusalem.
We need to do...
because there are
100,000 Jewish prisoners
trapped in the old part of the city.
They need supplies...
or they will die.
And with them, our State...
before being born.
We must do...
because Jerusalem...
It is the heart of Judaism.
It belongs to these people, all of them.
We cannot allow what they are doing.
You are hope, children!
I just wanted to say this before you go.
Mazal Tov (good luck), my children!
Come on, Cathy.
You have nothing to do with this war.
Why? Jerusalem is also a
Christian city, did you know that?
Hold fire!
Arrest the prisoners!
Two guards with them now!
It doesn't matter the casualties,
Jews or Arabs! Take care of them too!
I want a guard on the summit now!
The rest over there!
I want three guards as quickly as I can!
It won't be that easy.
Just do it!
Give me the phone.
David!
David, I'm here.
We have controlled the Castelo area.
Listen to me, we can't deal with them!
Are many! We must return through the west.
Gather your men...
Go, go!
Golan, where the fuck are you?
I see the damn Arabs.
We lost Castelo, we are withdrawing.
Come on, let's go!
Why are they screaming?
Abu Musah is dead.
Abu Musah?
They abandoned Castle, let's go!
Come on, let's go back to Castelo!
Bobby...
you killed my uncle.
my uncle!
No.
No!
I killed Said's uncle.
I didn't come here to fight.
I came to find peace.
There will be peace.
No.
Jews kill Arabs, Arabs kill Jews...
Blood brings more blood,
and pain, more pain...
This hatred will grow.
There must be an end.
There is always an end!
Day always follows night.
Ever.
The SS, they wanted...
they wanted young women.
I wanted to live...
They gave me a lot more to eat
than others, all because...
they didn't want thin women.
I did what they wanted.
I wanted to die, every day,
but...
I continued doing what they wanted.
They made me...
one thing.
We thought it would be
Americans who would free us,
but it was the Russians.
Then I knew what awaited me.
The other women pointed
out that I was the Nazis' bitch.
For bread.
I did.
And now I'm here, in Palestine.
It saw?
There's always an end.
Day always follows night.
Look, Bobby!
Look!
"If I forget you, oh, Jerusalem"
...at the same moment, a
few kilometers from Castelo,
Irgoun and Stern,
dissident extremist groups,
attacked the Arab village of Deir Yassin.
The Haganah had nothing to do here.
Is this what you needed our weapons for?
This is outside our jurisdiction.
I assumed it would protect us.
Is this what they wanted?
A victory for yourselves?
For Irgoun.
For this worm.
We tried to warn them,
but the truck's speaker was broken.
Son of a bitch!
Tell your men to drop their weapons.
Do it or I'll shoot, I swear!
Don't move!
Come on, David!
Shoot!
Come on, David, shoot!
My God, Golan!
You can't get things
by killing these people!
Damn you!
Lower your weapons!
Do what you want, damn pig!
Listen to me, all of you!
Let's bury Abou Moussa in the
Dome of the Rock, like a saint!
Abdel Kader will be elevated
to heaven, as Muhammad was.
Then, we will be together,
and we will reproduce
in numbers, for our revenge
and that of our people!
The Jewish Agency
reported that it ignored
the projects of the
Stern group and Irgoun.
David Ben Gourion sent a message
to King Abdullah expressing his regret...
What are you doing?
I'll go see him.
Who?
Said.
You can't do that!
They will kill you! Not now, not today!
I have to find him.
You can't do that!
Don't do that, Bobby!
Don't do that!
Not today!
Not today, they are furious!
He will kill you!
Bobby?
I love you!
Arab leaders ordered
to its people to take to the streets
after the massacre in Deir Yassin.
American journalist. Said Chahine.
I am an American journalist.
Said!
An American journalist wants to see you.
Said, it's me!
Said, please, I...
Said, where are you going?
Did we kill him?
Take care of him.
Let it return to the Jews.
And if you touch a strand
of his hair, I'll kill you.
May 14, 1948.
After 26 years of occupation,
British troops leave Palestine.
In Jerusalem, the British troops
parades for the last time.
With their old trucks, they accompany,
some English soldiers, who go
down the streets of Jerusalem.
Good morning, Rabbin Weingarten.
I understand that after
the 70s, the "key" to
Jerusalem has not been
in the hands of the Jews.
This will be the first
time in 19 centuries
that your people will
have this privilege.
This is the key to the door of Zion.
Our relationship was difficult,
but we can try to be friends.
Goodbye.
It's like the Germans say.
We must strike hard and fast!
Starting with Latroun!
We must decide on a central command.
Jews are united and we must
Form a unified army to fight them.
May I suggest that His Majesty King
Abdullah be our commander in chief?
He is the most experienced.
A royal army cannot receive orders
from a sovereign other than its own.
So we are all in agreement.
We will fight together, apart.
And may Allah protect us!
Gentlemen, please, please wait!
Please follow me!
This country is the birthplace
of the Jewish people.
It was here that a civilization of
universal importance was created.
It was here that the
Book of Books was written.
A gift to the world.
Survivors of the European catastrophe
demand the right to live with dignity,
freedom and work.
They fought ceaselessly
to enter Palestine.
To prevent crimes and
claim the rights of our people,
we proclaimed the
founding of the Jewish State,
in the Holy Land.
The State will be called Israel.
We have solid inspiration... peace!
Let's stand!
The State of Israel was born.
Two days have passed since Ben
Gourion declared the State of Israel.
Armed Arabs lay siege to Jerusalem.
Coming from Baghdad, Amman, Cairo,
Damascus and Beirut, the armed Arabs
and the Palestinian
irregulars declared war
to the new Jewish State.
Is the monastery empty?
No.
We are here, praying.
Yes of course.
I'm very sorry.
Are there no Jewish soldiers?
Major Abdullah Tell, Arab Legion
of King Abdullah of Transjordan.
I request the Latroun Monastery.
The road, Djamal. From now on,
nothing and no one will pass through it.
The Jews of Jerusalem will
starve and finally surrender.
Speak English?
I'm Bobby Goldman.
I'm in charge. Welcome to Israel.
How many?
This boat is another
that is about to arrive.
712 people.
From Czechoslovakia, Russia,
Poland and Hungary.
Military training?
I do not believe this.
They must attack Latroun.
The path to Jerusalem is blocked.
Lord, at least allow them to rest.
Sir.
Why are these unfortunates here?
Because they need a homeland.
And why am I here?
Because your country needs them.
No!
You are ignoring the
seriousness of the situation.
I need them,
men and women, now!
David!
Give them food.
Let them rest.
Make them feel at home.
Tomorrow, a rifle for those
capable and two days of training.
Yael, come translate.
One, for movement.
Hold him here and kick
as hard as you can...
and quickly hit here.
Here, right here.
On the shoulder, here!
Boys, hold on tight and shoot!
They are broken!
They want this road. It's their route.
I didn't want this carnage!
I wanted to enter
Jerusalem, save the holy city.
Yael?
She is dead.
Stop the engine.
Does anyone know where we are?
Let's rest here.
Bobby.
Yael.
Yael is dead.
She is dead.
Stop there, hands up!
Hands up!
What?
David?
I'm so happy to see you!
Thank God!
Where are you from?
Jerusalem.
Bobby, listen to me.
I found a way between
Tel-aviv and Jerusalem.
I'm sure we can supply Jerusalem.
We need to build a road.
Is very difficult!
To build the road we will need
workers, we will need everything
so that the trucks cross every
day, trucks, dozens of them!
Where?
South of Latroun...
The US and Russia are
demanding a ceasefire.
- A ceasefire? - That's right.
This means...
Yes I know.
The Arabs will never accept it.
And the English?
The English only help when it matters.
It would be a miracle.
Lord, sir!
They're calling you on the radio.
It's from Jerusalem, Isaac.
Does Isaac know his daughter died?
No.
David, we need a miracle here.
We need food now.
Without the ceasefire we will have nothing.
We need more than a miracle.
David?
Bags on the back!
It's impossible, I said!
It weighs a ton!
The weight of the bag was calculated.
Where are they going with this? To where?
We are too old to fight.
2000 people are arrested.
At the Synagogue.
That's where we're going.
The only thing they had to
eat yesterday was dry bread.
We can't take much, but we can take hope.
Hope.
So, those who want,
and only those who want,
will take these packages.
The content of each one will
save a life, for another day.
Don't look him in the eye.
Never speak without permission.
Although he speaks his mother
tongue, he will speak to a king.
I know your courage, my
son, and your disappointment.
But what do the English
and Americans demand
is that we accept the ceasefire.
Refuse.
For God!
It won't cost him a soul
to drive away the Jews.
An assault for religion.
Only one.
An intervention in Jerusalem
You will break the agreement
with the British, Your Majesty.
The Jews resist, Your Majesty.
We must accept the ceasefire.
We must use this time
to gather our strength.
Does not make sense.
We haven't had a single defeat
and they want to withdraw?
Do you think the Jews will do
nothing during the ceasefire?
Save the holy city, and you will
become the king of Jerusalem!
How dare you?
Enough.
It's the King, sir.
We can't wait any longer.
Let's save Jerusalem.
The ceasefire will take
effect on June 10th at 10 am.
You have until that day, with
my legion, to take Jerusalem.
At 10 am, on June 11th,
all hostilities activities must end.
They are at the entrance to the palace.
We can go in from behind.
How many?
Many.
I will be back.
We cannot risk lives.
Hang on.
There is an underground passage.
What the hell are you talking about?
From a friend, knowledgeable
about cars and archeology.
I trust him.
This is crazy!
We have to go back!
I love you Jacob!
Thanks.
Is everyone okay?
All good?
Where is Yael?
The synagogue must be
taken before the ceasefire.
I will not let my legionnaires
fight in the city streets.
They weren't trained for that.
This will sentence them to death.
We continue with the snipers.
It will be too late!
The Jews are weak.
Here, in Jerusalem, they will give up.
The Jews?
Jews never give up.
We must act now.
Send your men down the avenue.
My men can't open the door.
There will be hundreds of dead
before they make the first move.
Rest assured.
Get out of here!
Come on, get up!
It is me! It's me, Goldberg!
Help-me!
It's okay, everything will be fine.
I will take care of you.
Who has morphine?
- I need morphine now!
- Bobby... keep her.
I went back. I came back to you.
I can't!
Shabbat!
I love you. I love you lots!
Listen to me.
Marry me!
Are you listening to me?
Be my wife, marry me.
Come on, look at me, marry me.
Yes?
Where is the rabbi?
Come come!
Isaac!
Need you Now!
Take care of him.
Marry us.
Said, be my witness.
David... Issac...
The ring, the ring!
Wait one moment.
Look at me.
Stay with me.
I beg you!
Look at me.
Give her the ring, and say with me:
Now you are my wife forever.
Forever.
Bobby.
"If I forget you,
"oh, Jerusalem..."
May Allah be with you both!
What is that?
Stopped?
It's the time...
of the ceasefire.
There are very few of them, I
thought there would be more.
I suggest you maintain your positions.
- Are they in their positions?
- Yes.
What are your fortifications?
Here.
Djamal, take them to the doctors.
Allah is witness,
they will not do anything bad.
All good? David, how are you?
When hostilities resumed
after six days of attacks,
the Israelis considered
strengthening their positions.
Soldiers and weapons also arrived,
thanks to the route through the hills.
The road.
Thousands of lives
were lost in those battles.
According to the United Nations,
750,000 Palestinians were exiled.
Wars followed wars, creating a
circle of violence, distrust and hatred.
However, men like Bobby and Said
will continue to fight each other for peace.
Despite all the suffering, we must hope
that the struggle for
peace will flourish,
and that one day, the city
of Arabs and Jews can live
under the meaning of his name:
City of peace.
"Pray for the peace of Jerusalem May there be peace within your
walls, and prosperity within your palaces." (Psalm of David)