All drivers to your cars, please.
All drivers to your cars.
- Distracted?
- No, that's not exactly right.
Your son seems to be interested
in only one thing.
All he talks about
all he seems capable
of thinking about
is automobile racing.
Well, you know,
his father designs racing cars.
- And where is your husband?
- Working.
He couldn't be here.
Perhaps the apple hasn't fallen
very far from the tree.
Is your husband's name Rex?
No, that's his older brother, Rex.
Why?
This is the test he turned
in last week.
Bang!
All right, pencils down.
Take your answer sheets
place it into the first part
of your booklet
pack up your things
and bring your... to my desk.
Speed Racer, slow down!
Take it you're ready to go?
- How was school?
- Fine.
Are you going to the track?
Mom said you were.
You don't have to drop me off.
I could just go with you.
- No way.
- Oh, come on. Take me with you.
- Come on, please.
- I can't, Speed.
- Pops would kill me.
- He doesn't have to know.
I won't say anything.
Nobody will know.
Come on, please, Rex, please...
Are you wearing the socks?
Okay. But if you roll us again,
this'll be the last time.
Deal?
Deal.
Oh, yeah!
Come on!
Yeah!
You feel that shimmy?
It's your hind legs
trying to outrun your front.
What do I do?
You stop steering
and you start driving.
This ain't no dead piece of metal.
Car is a living, breathing thing,
all right?
She's alive.
You can feel her talking to you
telling you what she wants,
what she needs.
All you gotta do is listen.
Close your eyes and listen.
You know, they say
that Ben Burns drove the final lap
of the Vanderbilt Cup
with his eyes closed.
- No way!
- No?
Maybe you just can't hear it, then.
Maybe you ought to start
hitting those books.
- No! I hear it!
- Oh, is that so, Mr. Burns?
All right. Tell me when to punch it
for the jump.
Now?
Now!
Local fan favorite, Speed Racer,
is gobbling up this track.
(Italian)
(Japanese) Competing in the Grand
Prix is not a dream out of reach.
(Russian)
He's a new rising star in the sky.
Let us hope he does not make
the same mistakes
that his brother made.
Heads up, Speed. Seven o'clock.
I got Snake drafting Pitter Pat.
I got him.
I figure he'll slingshot after you
in the next turn.
I'm ready.
Great move, Speed!
All right, watch out
for the dog balls coming up.
You may want to ease off a little.
Not this time, Sparky.
Holy cannoli, Speed.
- You know who you're racing?
- Yeah.
Rex is gonna win it, ain't he, Pops?
Nobody's gonna catch him.
He's gonna win it.
He's gonna set the course record.
- Nobody's gonna stop him.
- Quiet, Speed.
- There's still a lot of race to go.
- No way. It's over.
My brother's the best racer
in the world.
Everyone else is running for second.
Yeah!
I told you to take him out!
We're trying, sir, we're trying,
but he's just too fast.
It's unbelievable, folks!
No one has seen moves like this
since that remarkable night
eight years ago.
There's no doubt in my mind.
He's gunning for the record.
(Russian) The record that was held
for the last eight years...
He is not alone out there,
he is chasing someone.
He is chasing the ghost of Rex Racer.
Jeepers, he could do it, Pops.
He could really do it.
What if he does it?
What if he does it, Pops?
I don't know if I can watch this.
There's that Speed Racer.
My daddy told me
that his daddy used to work
for the Mishida Motorworks
but he quit.
My daddy told me that it was
a completely crazy thing to do.
He says the whole family is crazy.
Speed's not crazy.
No. He's just dumb.
Probably the dumbest kid
in the class.
Mrs. Waterstraat had me
alphabetize the IRB tests
and you wouldn't believe
what the retard did...
Speed!
Are you all right?
Who are you?
I'm Trixie. I'm in your class.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, you wanna see my car collection?
I'd love to.
- Hey, Rex. Hey, Pops.
- Hey, Speedy.
- Who's your friend?
- Her name's Trixie.
- She's in my class.
- Hi.
Pleasure to meet you... young lady.
Hey, Pops, a guy told me
to give this to you.
- Says he was a big fan.
- Oh, a fan, is it?
Well, it's not every day
we get people
with such good taste around here.
Where is he?
He was in a hurry,
driving a '68 Fendersin.
- Sweet set of wheels.
- Let me see that.
Cool beans.
No one
from these parts will ever forget
the tragic story of Rex Racer.
(Japanese) How can anyone
forget about the incident?
He nearly ruined racing.
One of the bravest men
to ever drive a racecar.
(French)
Can I come with you, Rex?
Not this time, Speedy.
When are you coming back?
I don't know. I don't know.
Hey. There's something I want you
to have.
But the Mach Five's your car.
Not anymore.
Look, Speed.
One day, people might say things
about me.
But no matter what they say,
I just...
Look, I hope you never believe them.
I won't.
Come here.
So, you're quitting?
I have to.
No, you don't.
This is a choice. You're selling out.
Turning your back
on everything we've built here.
- I'm done arguing with you, Pops.
- Don't you turn your back on me.
You can't tell me what to do.
It's my life to live.
You walk out that door now,
you better not ever come back.
Rex Racer, driving the black
and red Uniron car
got into a tangle with Richenbach,
who was favored to win.
Come on, that was no tangle.
He took Richenbach out.
Well, we don't know that,
but I imagine
the WRL will be reviewing this crash.
That's the third DNF crash
Racer's been involved in.
- Turn it off, Speed.
- Heck, they oughta just suspend him.
- Well, that's...
- I don't want you
- watching this anymore.
- Racer's career if he found guilty.
The trial of Rex Racer shook
the World Racing League
to its very foundation.
Once a rat, always a rat
and in my book,
Rex Racer's nothing but a rat.
Did you see that?
That will definitely leave a mark.
And Rex Racer nearly took
Yokima's head off with that jump.
Hey, there is no doubt in my mind
that Rex Racer
is one of the dirtiest drivers
in the world.
For five years, Rex Racer took orders
from the criminal underworld.
(Italian)
- Fight...
- No! You stop this!
- You stop it right now!
- I just told him the truth!
His crum bum brother doesn't belong
on a race track, he belongs in jail!
- Hey!
- Speed.
The indictment brought down
the perennial racing powerhouse,
Uniron.
Uniron was linked
to the notorious fixer
Blackjack Benelli.
Still in prison today
Benelli was rumored to be behind
the Casa Cristo tragedy.
This is one of the worst crashes
I have ever...
How could this happen?
This is terrible.
This is just terrible.
And still no sign
of driver Rex Racer.
(Italian)
(Russian) He shoots ahead!
What the hell is he doing?
- (Italian)
- (Russian) This is my night.
- (Russian)
"Forget the past," he's saying.
"This is my night!"
- He's coming hard.
- It's gonna be close!
What a race!
- (Italian)
- (Russian) So close!
Unbelievable!
A split second late.
The record still stands.
Come on. Let's go. Victory Lane.
Folks, I knew Rex Racer,
and if he's up there somewhere
watching this race,
you can bet your ass
he's damn proud
of his little brother.
Pulling into Victory Lane,
the winner, Speed Racer!
He's going to be very good.
No, he's going to be the best...
if they don't destroy him first.
Hey, hey! What are you two doing?
Nothing.
Was that the same nothing
that broke my last couch?
Naw. That was
a totally different nothing.
Got it!
- Racer residence.
- Good morning.
May I speak to Speed Racer?
- He's not interested.
- Spritle?
- What?
- Was that for Speed?
Yeah. But Speed doesn't want
to talk to them.
- You don't know that.
- Sure, I do.
Speed's gotta drive for Pops.
He's gotta.
Well, that's for Speed to decide.
Now get dressed.
Tell your father breakfast is ready.
"It was a virtuoso display of talent
the likes of which has not been seen
at Thunderhead since Racer, the Elder
dropped jaws eight years ago.
Now, as we once again pull
our collective jaw up from the floor
we have to ask
"Will it be different this time
or will tragedy..."
That's enough.
I just can't believe
there's not one mention
of Racer Motors in here.
That's because the sponsors control
the media, Sparky.
- Morning, everyone.
- Good morning.
- Is Speed up yet?
- In spirit, anyway.
- Oh, thanks. Hey, Superstar.
- Hey, Trix.
Have you seen the papers
this morning?
- They're all in love with you.
- Really?
Yeah, but there seems to be a lot
of speculation
about which team you'll sign with.
Really?
- What the...
- Earthquake! Earthquake!
Quick, Pops, the kitchen
is the most dangerous place
in an earthquake!
- Everybody, run for your life!
- Spritle, calm down!
- Mr. Racer, morning.
- What?
(I'm... May I?)
Mr. and Mrs. Racer, I hope
you will forgive this imposition.
These are bluebells from Eden, Inc.
I'm told they'll bloom
at least three times
each time a different color.
And Mr. Racer, these are for you.
Straight from the Isle of Kamut,
hand-rolled, premium blend.
Thanks, but who are you?
I am E.P. Arnold Royalton, Esquire
President and Chairman
of Royalton Industries.
And it is my honor to meet you both.
Oh, dear, I seem to have interrupted
your breakfast.
Is that pancakes I smell?
Oh, are you hungry, Mr. Royalton?
A figure like mine requires
constant attention, Mrs. Racer.
And do you like pancakes?
When I was a child, we used to say,
"Pfannkuchen sind Liebchen!"
Pancakes are love.
Gorgeous, Mrs. Racer.
Superb density.
Hints of vanilla. Cinnamon?
- That's right.
- Absolutely gorgeous.
Well, I'm glad you like them.
Like them? I want to buy your recipe.
No. I'll give you the recipe,
Mr. Royalton.
Nonsense!
Cenestro Foods, a subdivision
of Royalton Industries is planning
a new range
of homecooked meals for travelers
and this is just the kind
of magic we're looking for.
I'll have my attorney draw up
the paperwork.
Now, then, we all know the reason
I'm here is because of you, Speed.
I was watching last night
and I have to tell you, young man
you gave me goosebumps.
I knew at once this was
no mere driver I was watching.
This was an artist.
I imagine the phone's been ringing
off the hook.
Yeah. But Speed doesn't want
to drive for you
or any other sponsors.
- Is this your manager, then?
- That's our youngest, Spritle.
Nice to meet you, youngster.
- We got our eye on you, mister.
- Excellent.
The first thing I want
to make perfectly clear is that
I have no intention whatsoever
of trying to get Speed away
from Racer Motors.
What you have here
is what teams spend years
and millions of dollars
trying to achieve, chemistry.
I wouldn't dare touch a thing.
Well, excuse me for asking,
but what do you want?
To help.
I want to make sure you have access
to whatever resources you need
to continue doing
exactly what you're doing.
No offense, Royalton,
but Racer Motors has always run
as an independent.
None taken, I completely understand,
I sympathize.
No, strike that. I empathize.
You may think of R.I.
as a huge corporate conglomerate
but I will have you know, sir,
I still remember working all night
on a Commodore 64 in the basement
of my foster parents' home.
I built R.I.
from below the ground up.
So, while Royalton Industries may
look like a major sponsor to you
it remains in my heart
as independent to me
as the first day I quit my job
at GloBoCom
to start working for myself.
Now, then...
I've had this wonderful opportunity
to meet your family.
All I'm asking for is the chance
to introduce you to mine.
I've never flown
so low through the city.
Special permit.
Only six of them are granted a year.
Take whatever you like.
Thank you.
- Spritle!
- What?
She said we could have some.
All right, maybe one apiece.
Hey, look,
that's the Grand Prix Colosseum.
My brother's gonna win
the Grand Prix someday.
No doubt in my mind, young man.
Given the right circumstances,
no doubt in my mind whatsoever.
This is Gennie, our talent manager.
Ask for anything.
Her job is to make it come true.
Hello, Speed. Welcome to Royalton.
What's this?
To make an informed decision,
you'll have to understand
how we take care of our drivers.
- All aboard.
- Oh, cool!
Royalton Tower is the crown jewel
among the properties that I control.
It functions
as the corporate headquarters
for the top 12 divisions
of our parent corp.
One big industrious family.
Our vertically integrated plant
is the fastest in the world
from initial carbon bond
to finished car in 36 hours.
How long does it take
at Racer Motors?
Several weeks, at least.
This kind of production facility
could be at your disposal, Mr. Racer.
This is our operating theater
where our patented
Refusion Distributor is installed
in the turbine drive.
Is that
an Inner Positive Transponder?
We control the only
transponder foundry in the world
outside of Musha Motors.
Sorry, trade secret.
As you know, a T-180 driver's got
to be in peak physical condition.
No expense is spared to ensure
that when our drivers suit up
they are as perfectly tuned
as the machines they are controlling.
The best drivers
must be able to withstand
over four G's of force
in a typical race.
The will to win is nothing
without the will to prepare.
And at Team Royalton
we prepare our drivers
for any eventuality
and every possible condition.
I'm good!
I hope I didn't scare you, Speed,
with how hard we push our team.
I just wanted you to see
how committed we are to winning.
- I get that.
- Good.
Because I also want you to understand
that R.I. isn't all work and no play.
That's Cannonball Taylor!
Stop the car. Jack!
Jack. Come here.
Someone I'd like you to meet.
Speed Racer.
Allow me to introduce,
two time Grand Prix winner
five time WRL Champion
and future Hall of Famer
Jack Cannonball Taylor.
- Honor to meet you.
- Caught that Thunderhead replay.
Nice piece of work.
Thanks.
There was a rumor
you might be visiting.
It's pretty impressive.
Only thing I cared about
was that wall over there.
That's what sold me.
You want to win in this League,
you're talking to the right guy.
Thanks, Jack.
Sweet!
We treat our thoroughbreds
the way they deserve to be treated.
Sweet!
There's a full maid service,
of course, with personal chef
and masseurs available 24-7.
Sweet!
Thank you.
Should be perfect.
Try it on.
Okay.
So, Mrs. Racer, what do you think
about my family?
Impressed?
- You could say that.
- Good.
Because I want you to understand
the possibilities
that exist for your son right now.
What's wrong, Mr. Racer?
To be honest, Royalton
I'm feeling more intimidated
than impressed.
This kind of company scares me.
People like you
have way too much money.
When someone gets that kind of money
they start thinking that
the rules everybody else plays by
don't mean squat to them.
However, my sons
are the most important thing
I've ever done in my life
besides marrying my best friend.
And if Speed wants us to figure out
some kind of an alliance...
then you can bet your ass
we'll be in business.
- Hubba hubba.
- Oh, honey, you look so handsome.
- Yeah?
- Very sharp, Speed.
Suits you perfectly.
Regardless of what happens,
I want you to have it, it's a gift.
Thanks, Mr. Royalton.
So, how are you feeling, Speed?
It's very...
impressive.
You think that
maybe there's something
that could work out here?
I guess I'd like to think about it...
if I could.
This isn't the kind of offer
I go around making every day, son.
No, I understand that, sir.
So, if I had to give you
an answer now, then
- to be honest...
- Stop right there.
You're right.
You should think about it.
I'm sure you're feeling
a bit overwhelmed.
You should take a little time.
Think about what you saw
and heard here
and we'll get together
early next week.
- Deal?
- Deal.
I thought we had a deal.
I thought we were friends.
Well, maybe where you come from,
that's how you treat your friends.
But around here
we don't take too kindly to it,
do we, fellas?
- It hurts our feelings.
- Problem is I like you, Taejo.
And I've got a real soft spot
in my heart for that sister of yours.
And normally
under circumstances such as this
we'd be pouring you a nice
comfortable pair of concrete shoes.
But I think I thought
of another solution.
How are my babies?
Hungry?
Ready for seconds?
Boys!
No!
Don't worry, it only hurts
for a few seconds
then you'll probably black out.
No, please!
It's gonna be hard to drive
with skellie hands.
No, please!
You even think about turning rat
and next time
it's your sister going in there!
- What?
- Someone's tailing us.
- Is it him?
- It could be.
- Oh, God!
- It's him!
Crush him!
He's out front.
Gotcha!
Damn!
- Boss!
- My babies!
My babies!
Put your finger in there!
Do it!
Nice fishes, nice fishes.
No...
- We can't take another hit, boss!
- Pull over.
But don't stop.
- Are you hurt?
- No.
Then get up.
Thank you. You saved my life.
I didn't save anything worth saving
unless you get smart real fast.
You thought you could take
on the Cartel.
You can't. Not without help.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
You have been
on Cruncher Block's leash for so long
maybe you forgot how it feels
to stand up and be a man.
The only way you'll ever stop
these people
is to bring them to justice.
Justice?
That's a commodity
I don't waste my money on.
Get out.
- I'll see you at Fuji.
- You won't finish.
When you lose
if you can still dial a phone,
call this number.
You're really considering signing
with Royalton.
- I just said it was tempting.
- Why?
Well, they got a really good team.
Cannonball Taylor, Maggie Manifold.
They win a lot of majors.
And since when did winning
become so important?
It is important.
You gotta win
if you want to keep driving
and that's what I want to do.
It's the only thing
I really know how to do.
- That's not true.
- Come on.
I wouldn't have made it out
of high school without your help.
Okay, well, that's true.
But when I'm in a T-180,
I don't know.
Everything just makes sense.
So, are you saying
this doesn't make sense?
Okay, this makes sense, too.
- So, you like this?
- Yeah.
This ain't so bad.
I was starting to wonder.
Wonder what?
Well, with you so busy becoming
Mr. Super Famous Racecar Driver
I was starting to wonder
if you were still interested in this.
- You know I am.
- Do I?
What, like you forgot?
- Maybe I need a reminder.
- Ah, a reminder.
Sometimes a girl could use
a reminder.
You mean like a new igniter
for your helicopter?
Well, how about a tire burn
that spells out your name?
Warmer.
Maybe at the end of some big race,
when I pull into Victory Lane
I scoop you up and kiss you
with thousands
of flashbulbs going off.
Would that be so terrible,
Mr. Super Famous Racecar Driver?
I don't know.
- Maybe we should practice.
- Maybe we should.
- Oh, God, I'm gonna hurl.
- Spritle.
He did not.
- You little sneak.
- Wasn't my idea.
- Oh, no?
- It was his.
- Wait till we tell Pops.
Naw, don't do that.
We couldn't sleep.
We just wanted to hang out.
We didn't know you were going
to In-spew-ation Point.
By the way, cootie shot.
- I'm taking you home.
- Wait. Wait.
Can we stop for ice cream first?
The new GRX has a supercharged
Inner-Positive Transponder
and will be capable of speeds
in excess of 800km an hour.
If such a car were
to win the Grand Prix this year
one would expect the demand
for transponders
to increase dramatically.
One would expect.
And if a single company
gained control
of all the transponder foundries
in the world
one might expect that company
to do very well for itself.
You know what I want, and I know
that for the last few years
you've been trying to buy out
your main rival, Tetsua Togokahn.
The question is, can we make a deal?
Deliver Togokahn at that price
and the transponder foundry is yours.
Done.
- Speed!
- Mr. Royalton.
Welcome!
Come here!
Look at this.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
We're still working on the R and R,
but it's getting there. Come, sit!
We can talk logos later.
Can I get you something to drink?
Water? Bubbly?
- A shot of rye?
- No. I'm okay.
So, I can see you've been giving
some serious thought to this thing.
- I have. Yes, sir.
- Good.
That means you understand
we're talking about
not just your future
but your family's future.
- My family means a lot to me.
- I know. I can tell.
That's why this is so important.
Because you can help them.
All you have to say is yes.
That's all I need to hear
and I can make so many things happen
for you and your family.
You ready for that?
You ready to say yes, Speed?
Jackpot.
Oh, boy, oh, boy.
This isn't an easy decision for me,
Mr. Royalton.
For my family, racing's everything.
I was tooling timing pins with Pops
while I was still wearing diapers.
I mean, there's nothing more perfect
than a picnic at Thunderhead.
But when my brother died,
all that went away.
I can't tell you
how painful that was.
It nearly killed all of us.
Especially Pops.
He didn't set foot in his shop
for over a year.
But one night,
when I was still pretty young
I couldn't sleep
and I went into the living room
and there was Pops
in his beat up robe
watching some old race recordings.
What a move by Burns
coming into that last turn.
Stickleton didn't see
that one coming!
So, I sat with him there
watching old Ben Burns
coming around the last turn
of the 43 Prix and...
all of a sudden,
Pops started screaming.
race out of that last turn.
Go!
And then I started screaming.
And as Burns and Stickleton
duked it out heading for the finish
we were cheering our heads off.
It's gonna be tight!
It's... It's Burns! Burns win!
And the second
the black and white came down
we looked at each other
and we realized
racing's in our blood.
But for Pops, it isn't just a sport.
It's way more important than that.
It's like a religion.
And in our house
the major sponsors
are kind of like the devil.
I don't mean to offend you, sir,
and I do appreciate your offer
but after all we've been through...
I don't think
this kind of deal's for me.
You poor, naive chump.
I'm gonna pretend I didn't hear
that load of sickening schmaltz
and I'm gonna give you
a bit of an education.
And at the end of it,
if you're smart, you'll thank me
and then you'll sign that contract.
Jig's up.
Holy moly.
Hey, this is Marvin,
down at the landing pad.
I think we got mice again.
All right, we'll send someone over
to take care of it. Over.
Look. There is the true spirit
of the golden age of racing.
Benjamin Braddack, Reginald White,
George Wheeler
Diamond Dave Tewksbury,
and Oliver Potter.
The five most powerful men
in the world
at the turn of the last century.
For all intents and purposes
they created the modern
automotive industry.
But the true stroke of their genius
was the invention of the WRL
the world's first racing league.
Interesting that you and your father
were so moved by the 43 Prix.
One of the great finishes
in the history of racing, right?
Everyone remembers Burns
and Stickleton slugging it out
but who remembers Carl Potts?
Driving this rebuilt Wittigan
for lodyne Industries
Potts spun out in the second lap
and went down as a DNF
a forgettable and pathetic finish.
So bad that, afterwards,
Iodyne stock dropped six points.
But, as Ben Burns sat guzzling cold,
fresh milk in Victory Lane
a thousand cameras taking his picture
Sirrus Aeronautics
saw almost a 12-point gain
which immediately blocked
Penninsula Power Cell
from being able to afford the price
of a complete takeover.
This put Joel Goldman,
the CEO of lodyne, Inc.
In the exact position
he wanted to be in.
By first buying controlling interest
in his own company
at a devalued price,
he then brokered a merger
with Sirrus
that immediately sent lodyne
into the gains record book,
the only record book that matters.
Look out that window.
There isn't a single plane
or helicopter or K-Harrier
that isn't powered
by lodyne fuel cells.
That's what racing is about.
It has nothing to do with cars
or drivers.
All that matters is power
and the unassailable might of money.
Dude! Yeah!
Out of the way! Out of the way!
Get out of the way!
You understand?
Burns knew he was going to win.
It was already decided.
A week before the Prix,
Goldman and Sirrus met
with several other major players
at the Cargyle Hotel.
They met there as they had for years.
They met to negotiate
the finish order of the Grand Prix.
No race is more important
and no race is more controlled.
That year, Goldman
was supposed to win
but he knew that
if he sold his win to Sirrus
whatever that win
might be worth was nothing
compared to what could be gained.
That's why I spent $3 million
on this burnt
and twisted lump of metal.
Because it reminds me
of what really matters.
This is the true heart of racing,
boy.
This is my religion.
You don't know how many times
I've seen that same cow eyed
say-it-isn't-so look of disbelief.
Every bumpkin
who comes in from the sticks
looks exactly as you do now.
I won't bother proving it to you.
You walk away from me,
you walk away from this deal
you'll know
how true it is soon enough.
So, last chance.
You ready to put away your toys
and grow up?
Are you ready to make more money
in one year
than your father made
in his whole life?
Are you ready to become
a real racecar driver?
Then sign that contract!
Spearhook.
What's this?
If that's your idea of racing,
you can keep it.
Listen to me and listen good, kid
because I'm gonna give you
one more history lesson.
You're gonna go to Fuji
and you're gonna try and prove
that everything I just told you
is nothing but a lie.
But no matter how well you drive,
you won't win, you won't place.
I guarantee you right now,
you won't even finish the race.
Speed Racer's making his move,
gunning for the lead.
The Harbinger of Boom
once again leaves his mark
a trail of carnage and chaos
cartwheeling behind him!
Oh, but the fans love it, don't they?
They do, God help them.
And they're about to get some more
as lodyne is now slugging it out
with young Taejo Togokahn.
Oh, terrible crash!
They're gonna have to fish Taejo
and Billy Ray out of the drink.
This race is far from over.
And right now, one car stands
between Speed Racer and the lead.
The Gray Ghost.
We got ourselves a real race here!
Show me what you got.
Show me what you got!
- Speed, get out of there!
- I can't, I can't move!
Soon after that
there'll be litigation against some
of your father's designs.
Are you Pops Racer of Racer Motors?
Yeah. But I'm still on vacation.
You are hereby served a summons.
What?
You are being sued
for IP infringement
by Janus Automakers.
- No way!
- That's ridiculous.
That's for a jury to decide.
The legitimacy of the lawsuits
won't matter.
They'll be enough
to discredit his company.
Whatever contracts he has,
he'll lose.
Within a year,
he'll be filing for bankruptcy.
After that, you and the rest
of your pathetic family
will be history.
Pops is right.
You are the devil.
- Mr. Royalton.
- What?
- Speed!
- Spritle?
I found these two sneaking around
the restricted area.
Get this Racer trash out
of my building.
- I'll see you in Fuji.
- Yes.
And then you'll find out
you just made
the biggest mistake of your life!
Hey, kid.
- Ben Burns?
- Nice race.
I ain't seen moves like that
in a long time.
It didn't matter, I still lost.
Yeah. Tough break.
Well, good luck.
Mr. Burns, can I ask you something?
Sure, kid.
The 43 Prix.
Did you know you were gonna win?
You know, everybody thought that me
and Stickleton hated each other.
Funny, ain't it?
"Controversy surrounds Racer Motors,
now embroiled in IP litigation.
And while evidence
remains inconclusive
whether or not Speed
used an illegal device
the Fuji Helexicon seems destined
to become another mark of shame
added to the notorious
Racer family legacy
a legacy that has forever tainted
the integrity of this beloved sport."
Sparky.
Sorry, ma'am.
I'm gonna send that guy
some Chim Chim cookies.
- You'll do no such thing.
- We gotta do something, Pops.
This is exactly
what he said would happen
if I didn't drive for him.
He's just trying to scare you, son.
They tried the same thing with Rex.
If it's a fight they want,
it's a fight they'll get.
How? What can we do?
- How can we fight this?
- The truth will come out.
The truth? Don't be naive, Pops.
Speed?
Are you all right?
I don't know.
It's gonna be okay.
We'll work this out.
I don't know, Mom.
I may have really messed things up.
How?
By not joining Royalton.
Oh, don't be silly.
You never would have been happy
racing for that terrible man.
Maybe that's not the point.
Maybe Royalton's right
and racing's all about business
and anyone
who doesn't understand that
is just a chump.
Now you listen to me, young man.
What you do behind the wheel
of a racecar
has nothing to do with business.
Before you could even talk
you were making noises
that sounded like an engine.
We'd try to take you to the park
and you never wanted to get out
of the car.
I loved that old wagon.
And you remember when Rex
took you out to Thunderhead
and let you drive?
And I turned it over.
Oh, my heart starts pounding
just thinking about it.
Mom!
Yeah, you should've seen it! Yeah!
Rex told me
the only reason we survived
was because I was wearing red socks.
And I thought your father
would have a heart attack
when you came in
with that crazy smile.
Speed, when I watch you do
some of the things you do
I feel like I'm watching someone
paint or... or make music.
I go to the races
to watch you make art.
And it's beautiful and inspiring
and everything that art should be
even though there are times
when I have to close my eyes.
But then there are other times...
when you just take my breath away.
That is at those moments,
when I feel your father's chest swell
and I know that he's smiling
because he's pretending
that he doesn't have tears
in his eyes
that I just go to pieces.
Why?
Because I am so impossibly proud
to be your mom.
It's gonna be okay, honey.
You'll see.
We'll work this out.
We just have to stick together.
And something good will happen.
You'll see.
Racer Hex! The Harbinger of Boom!
Run for your lives!
What are you two squawking about?
Pops, whatever you do,
don't open that door.
This is a bad idea.
If it was any other driver,
you'd be here.
Inspector Detector.
Good morning, Mr. Racer.
I know it's been a long time.
Ten years.
We've been after Royalton for years
for dozens
of capital corporate crimes
including WRL fixing
but we haven't had
the evidence we needed
to convict him until now.
What's he doing here?
Racer X works closely with our WRL
corporate crimes division
helping us recruit drivers like you,
Speed.
Why does he always wear that mask?
If any of you actually knew
his identity
you'd become targets for his enemies
which include some
of the most vicious fixers
in the world.
What do you want with me?
Are you familiar
with the driver Taejo Togokahn?
- Of course.
- For years, he's been contracted
by a fixer named Cruncher Block.
Recently, Taejo has been forced
to lose races
and he began resisting
thinking that he could do it
on his own.
After Fuji,
he realized he needed help.
Why help him?
Because he has a file
with enough information
to connect Block to Royalton
which could put both of them
behind bars
for the rest of their lives.
The problem is,
he won't give us the file
unless we help him stop
the takeover of his family's company.
How?
There's an upcoming race
that Taejo believes if he can win,
it'll catapult Togokahn Motors
back into the spotlight
and double the cost of the buyout
which should kill it.
But there aren't any more races left
except for the Grand Prix
and we both failed to qualify.
There aren't any more track races.
- This is a cross country rally.
- Casa Cristo.
What?
I know it seems cruel of me to ask.
But Taejo made it clear that he had
to have Speed and X on his team
or there would be no deal.
Absolutely not!
You'll have the support
of the entire CIB.
No. Rally racing
is a back alley sport
filled with jackals,
headhunters, and thugs.
I'm sorry, Inspector
but I've already lost one son
to that deathtrap.
I won't lose another.
I understand.
- If you change your mind...
- Keep your card, Chief Inspector.
Thank you for your time.
But Pops will never let you go.
He won't if I ask him.
Speed Racer, what are you thinking?
You weren't in Royalton's office,
Trix.
You don't know what it was like.
Felt as though he had his hand
inside my chest
and he was trying to crush everything
in my life that mattered to me.
All right. Let's do it.
You're gonna need an alibi.
- We'll say we're going skiing.
- What? No way.
You're gonna need my help.
Casa Cristo is a rally.
I can spot from a 'copter.
Trixie, this isn't a game.
These people play rough.
I know.
That's why I'm going with you.
And if you even try to argue with me
I'll tell Pops and he'll never
let you out of his sight.
You would, wouldn't you?
Well...
I guess we're going skiing.
We're just minutes away
from the start
of the 82nd annual
Casa Cristo Classic
the grande dame of cross country
the second oldest rally race
in the world
spanning two continents,
three climate changes
and 5,000km of the most winding
and treacherous roads ever raced.
With me again is five-time
Casa Cristo champion
- Spritle!
- Johnny "Goodboy" Jones.
What are you two doing?
Just watching a little TV, Pops.
It's his favorite show.
- It's in German.
- Not the monkey parts.
Oh, no, you don't.
You are not watching that race.
Out you go. Outside!
Get some exercise.
You're too pale!
Speed. I want you to understand
how much the CIB appreciates
your help on this.
I'm not doing this to help the CIB.
I don't know anything
about corporate crimes
and honestly, if I did,
it wouldn't really matter.
I'm doing this because
someone's trying to hurt my family
and I'm gonna do everything I can
to hurt him back.
Safety has been a primary concern
for Casa Cristo officials
especially the last few years.
That's right, Colton.
There were a number
of fatalities several years ago.
It really had a bad reputation.
Fans started calling it,
"The Crucible."
These are some of the most dangerous
drivers in the world.
And we expect they'll do anything
they can to stop you.
Their cars will probably be equipped
with secret weapons
so we've modified the Mach Five
to try to counter their attacks.
The "A" button will operate
your normal jump jacks.
"B" will seal your cockpit
which we fortified
with bulletproof polymer.
Should someone go after your tires
with, say, a hidden shank or shredder
the "C" button
will activate your tire shields.
However, in the event of any blowout
"D" will inflate
a Hexadyno emergency spare.
"E" will activate
these zircon tipped saw blades.
They'll cut through almost anything.
Use with discretion.
"F" will project the tire crampons.
And finally, "G" will launch
a remote control homing bird
that is capable of transmitting
U-CAP footage anywhere you are.
Every race fan has heard
the rumors of spearhooks
tire shanks and battery boosters.
No... While it's true
there have been a few bad apples
on the whole, most teams stay
within legal rules.
Or at least try not to get caught.
This is wrong,
what you are trying to do.
Musha's price is an insult
to five generations of our family.
And if you die?
Then will the price be high enough?
- I have no choice.
- Why?
He is your father, too.
I finally understand it now, Trix.
I know why he left us.
He was trying to change
this rotten business
and they killed him for it.
I know a lot of drivers who believe
that the hardest part of Cristo
is the start.
- The Muqranna?
- Yeah, those archways are tricky.
And speaking of starts
here comes the Queen
of Casa Cristo now.
The moment the Queen sees the sun,
she'll signal the start.
No... This is supposed to be my race.
I'm supposed to win!
I got the green light.
They promised I would go
to the Grand Prix.
For eight years,
I've played by the rules!
This is supposed to be my race!
Enough!
I can't stand the whining.
Like a baby needing
its diaper changed.
It's simple.
We have a team of wild cards.
The problem is
these wild cards are better drivers
than you.
What? Like hell they are!
Prove it.
Take out Taejo,
and the other two will quit.
You just watch me.
Come on!
I got Racer.
From where we're sitting
this team Taejo Togokahn's
put together
looks like they mean business.
As they head out of the city
and into the Zunubian Desert
the team leading
the pack is Snake Oiler!
Let's pinch these turds off!
Come on! We are falling behind!
Speed! On your right, Flying Foxes!
Got them.
Headhunters.
They're not alone.
- Oh, no.
- Speed Racer has a blowout!
Move it, Speed.
It's getting ugly out there.
Okay, no more Mr. Nice Guy.
Hurry, Speed, they need you!
Where have you been?
Have any of these drivers
read the rulebook?
See? This race is full of cheaters.
It's tough to see what goes on
in those dust clouds.
It can get really nasty in there.
- Watch the backdraft.
- You want some?
Come on! Thor Axine, yeah!
Wing left.
Flying in.
- Lead them!
- Here you go.
What? Watch the blind side!
Broom Hilda!
Crom!
Taejo!
Oh, my God, did I just see that?
A rear single set jump
into a flying kick!
I know he blew up at Fuji,
but this kid is flat out magic!
I'm going into town for some parts.
I'll be back for lunch.
Sure thing, Pops.
Let's go!
The Togokahn team is fighting
- Game on.
- Their way back into the race
behind the electrifying driving
of Speed Racer.
The fans are getting
their money's worth today.
Honey! I can't find my wallet.
Spritle! You two are in big trouble!
Wait. Wait, before you get mad
at us, look!
- I'm not falling for that.
- It's Speed!
- Speed's skiing!
- Then who's driving the Mach Five?
The pace has been relentless
as the eight remaining teams slice
their way through the aqueducts
of Sassicaia.
Oh, no.
As we near the end of the first leg
of the Casa Cristo
one team has dominated the race.
And here they come,
through the streets
of Cortega heading for the finish.
Yeah!
If we drive tomorrow
like we drove today, we will lose!
You will get nothing.
- All of this will be meaningless!
- Relax.
Snake's weak on turns.
We'll catch him in the mountains.
We might, if you stop showing off.
Hey, all I was doing
was saving your ass.
Don't fall apart yet.
There's still a lot of race to run.
A CIB man will be posted
outside your door.
We got their attention today.
You and Trixie
should be very careful tonight.
Racer X.
I thought we made a good team today.
Felt like we'd been doing it
for a long time.
If you say so.
Ineptitude!
- Is this what I pay you for?
- They ain't checkered yet.
If they do, I assure you it'll be
a very costly mistake for everyone.
It was very weird, Trix.
I knew every move he was gonna make
and he knew mine.
It was so familiar.
Maybe I'm crazy,
but Racer X first showed up
two years after Rex's death.
- But, Speed, we buried Rex.
- A body was buried.
Remember, it had already been
badly burned in the crash.
Even if it was Rex,
no one could have recognized him.
So, you think he faked the crash
with a different body
in the driver's seat?
Somehow, the kwik save
was disconnected.
Inspector Detector
suspected foul play
but nothing could be proved.
Do you really think Rex
could put everyone through all that?
Maybe he felt
he didn't have any other choice.
I'm sorry to disturb you, sir,
but do you know these people?
Yeah.
Is this the kind of driver I have?
Someone who disobeys?
Someone who lies to me?
Is this the kind of son I've raised?
And you, Trixie.
You know what this race did
to this family.
Did either of you stop
and think about us?
That's all I've been thinking about,
Pops.
You, Mom, Spritle, Sparky.
Yeah, you, too, Chim Chim.
We're in serious trouble, Pops,
and it's all my fault.
This is not the place or the race
to do anything about that.
- Why not?
- Because it won't do any good!
You don't know that.
You think you can drive a car
and change the world?
It doesn't work like that!
Maybe not.
But it's the only thing I know
how to do
and I gotta do something.
That's unacceptable. This is over.
Pack your things. We're going home.
I can't.
- I'm sorry, Pops.
- What?
- I'm staying.
- So am I.
No, you're not.
- We're going home right now!
- I'm not a child, Pops.
You can't tell me
how to live my life.
If you wanna fire me
as your driver, then fine, do it.
But it won't change the fact
that I am going to finish this race.
God, you sound like Rex!
You wanna die like him too?
Will that make you happy?
Don't take it out on me
because you feel guilty
- for what happened to Rex!
- Okay, you two, that's enough.
Pops. If they're staying,
we're staying.
Room service!
And I suggest that we all find a way
to go home together.
Where's the Mach Five?
Logged with security.
You added something to it,
didn't you?
Some defensive modifications.
Whole thing's out of balance,
isn't it?
It pulls left, rides a little stiff.
Sparky!
I'm sorry, Mom.
- Your father loves you. It's just...
- I know.
It's gonna be okay.
You wouldn't lie to your mother,
would you?
Never again.
I got him, Speed!
I got him! I got him!
Still got him!
Speed!
Attack!
What's going on out there?
You attack my family.
You try to hurt my sons.
Here we go!
What's going...
Oh, my God. Was that a ninja?
More like a non-ja.
Terrible what passes
for a ninja these days.
Cool beans.
Oh, I'm sorry. I was looking
for Speed Racer.
- Horuko. Are you all right?
- No.
Something terrible has happened.
Narcolyte benzamine.
A highly effective
and debilitating drug.
Stays in the system for hours,
but leaves with no trace.
- I'll be fine by morning.
- No, you won't.
You can't drive a car.
You can barely stand up.
You do not tell me what I can do.
Taejo.
What are we gonna do?
The second leg
of the Casa Cristo is underway
and the stage is set
for what might be one
of the most ferocious rallies
we've seen in years.
This is my race!
She's leaving the hotel now.
Wicked sidewinder coming up.
Watch the inside out,
could get dicey.
Watch your line!
Watch it!
- This is abso...
- lutely crazy.
Yeah, boss. Signal's loud and clear.
Don't do it! On the ground! Now!
Got you.
What the...
You cheater!
If you're here, who's...
That's better.
I couldn't see a thing.
That's it. Nice line, Trix.
Top of the hill's coming up.
I'd say Snake's got about a quarter
of a mile on you.
All right. Let's go get him.
If you'd been a little more careful,
he wouldn't be ahead of us.
I told you I couldn't see a thing
out of this dang helmet!
I can't believe you talked us
into this ridiculous idea.
What's ridiculous about it?
You're the one who's always saying
I'm a better driver
than most of the WRL.
- Now's not the time to prove it!
- Why not?
It's too dangerous!
It's too dangerous for me,
but not for you, right?
Children, focus.
If we're going to have a chance,
we're going to have to pass Snake
before the rendezvous.
I'm ready. Let's roll.
Go get them, girl!
Here they come. Let's pick it up!
- Take him.
- With pleasure.
Bring it on!
Come on!
Now the gloves are off
and they're pounding one another
bumper to bumper, rail to rail.
Take that, Togokahn!
You're going down!
- Oh, yeah!
- That's my boy!
Oh, God! Speed!
Please... Oh, please! Please!
The Togokahn Team roars into the lead
behind some very aggressive driving
by Speed Racer!
Are you kidding me?
He just tore Snake a new tailpipe!
- Trix, you all right?
- 10-4.
- Ready for more.
- Then let's move it.
We've got some time to eat up.
- You're sure, no cameras here?
- No, I checked it this morning.
There's quite a few dead spots
in these mountains.
- What's he doing here?
- Stowaway.
We weren't sure what to do with him.
Do what he'd do.
Break his legs and let him walk back.
Thank you so much.
Oh, it was a blast.
The cell's reloaded.
Let's go!
Good luck.
Nobody move!
We're still waiting
for the Togokahn Team
to come out of the pass.
Those roads can really ice up.
Very dangerous.
What is this?
This is called a change of plan.
Yeah, that's right.
We're changing your plan
that changed our plan
to change your plan.
Right, boss?
- The new plan...
- What was it?
Break your legs
and make you walk back?
I like that.
But first, it's time to play
a little game
of peekaboo I see you.
Monkey cookie!
Nice shot!
Spritle?
Get that monkey!
Nobody messes with Spark...
Looks like another change of plan.
Take him away, boys.
Spritle!
Go...
Oh, no, you don't.
You're in big trouble.
First out of the pass is...
the Hydra Cell Team.
They better send
the emergency trailer.
Wait, is that?
Here we go again.
Whatever happened in that pass
has left Togokahn
back where they started
but now only one obstacle stands
between Snake Oiler and victory.
The Maltese Ice Caves.
This is where Rex...
Speed, what are you doing?
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
This next cave's a rattler.
We'll make our move in there.
Now.
Not this time, punk.
Speed!
Bye-bye, little turd.
He did not! He did not just do that!
Speed Racer is driving straight up
a cliff face!
- Are we getting this?
- (French)
- Come on!
- Go, Speed, go!
- Hi. Remember me?
- No way!
No... Not again! Not again!
- Gun!
- (Foreign language)
Snake Oiler completely going out
of his mind!
Could have been altitude sickness.
It gets crazy up there.
Whatever it was,
Speed handled it beautifully.
And with less than 250km to go,
nothing seems to stand
between Togokahn and victory.
Get me Tetsua Togokahn.
Thank you.
We make a good team.
We did our part.
Make sure you do yours.
Of course.
Congratulations, Mr. Togokahn.
- Very impressive race.
- Yes, thank you.
You're very generous, Mr. Royalton.
Here, Speed, does this mean
you've signed with Togokahn?
No, this was
a mutually beneficial opportunity.
- Yes. Well put.
- Taejo!
Will you be running
in the Grand Prix this weekend?
We'll see. Right now I'm just going
to enjoy this victory.
The price is 78 a share.
That's outrageous.
The price is barely above 50.
This is extortion, blackmail.
I'll sue you, tie up every asset
you own for the next 20 years.
As you wish, Mr. Royalton,
have a nice day.
Wait.
Seventy-eight a share.
I'll have the paperwork drawn up.
A pleasure doing business with you.
You have done very well for us,
my son.
I don't get it, Pops.
What just happened?
Togokahn's played us for chumps.
All he wanted was our help
to drive up the stock
in his family business.
Even if he had a file
he had no intention
of turning it over.
You mean the whole race
was for nothing?
X?
Racer X!
Jesus, kid, you can drive.
I haven't been thrown like that
in years.
What are you doing here?
The Inspector told me what happened.
I came looking for you.
Why would you care?
Because you're a fighter,
and a friend.
Why don't you just tell me the truth?
You're Rex, aren't you?
You mean your brother?
You first appeared
two years after Rex died.
You drive just like him.
You knew I'd be here
because this is where
he always used to take me.
Just tell me the truth.
- You're not Rex.
- No, Speed.
I'm sorry, but your brother is dead.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't be.
I'm sure if he was here
he'd be immensely proud of you.
For what?
- Making the same mistakes he did?
- For trying to make a difference.
From what I've read,
that's all he tried to do.
And what good did it do?
He got killed for nothing.
Racing hasn't changed
and it never will.
It doesn't matter
if racing never changes.
What matters is
if we let racing change us.
Every one of us has to find a reason
to do this.
You don't climb into a T-180
to be a driver.
You do it because you're driven.
If you know so much,
why don't you tell me
why I should keep driving?
Sorry. That's for you to figure out.
I just hope when you do
that I'm there to see it.
- What you doing?
- What's it look like?
- Where you going?
- I don't know.
I just gotta get away from here.
Can I come with you, Rex?
What?
Can we come with you?
- No.
- Why not?
You'll understand
when it's your turn.
Speed.
Before you go,
I'd like to say a few things.
Will you sit with your old man
for a minute?
- Don't try and stop me.
- I won't.
Speed, I want you to know
I acted rashly.
I said things I wish I hadn't.
Your mother usually protects me
from making an ass out of myself
but I was determined to do it
this time
and I guess I did
a pretty good job of it.
I just wanted to make sure
you understood how sorry I was.
Thanks.
The truth was I couldn't have been
more proud of you, son.
Not because you won,
but because you stood up.
You weren't afraid and you did
what you thought was right.
It didn't amount to anything.
It was completely meaningless.
How could it be meaningless?
I saw my son become a man.
I watched him act with courage
and integrity and drive the pants off
every other driver on that road.
This is not meaningless.
This is the reason
for a father's life.
I admit, I went to Cortega
because I was afraid
that what happened to Rex
was gonna happen to you,
and I just couldn't take that.
But what I realized at Cortega...
was I didn't lose Rex
when he crashed.
I lost him here.
I let him think that
a stupid motor company
meant more to me than he did.
He'll never know
how much I regret that mistake.
But it's enough
I'll never make it again.
Speed, I understand
that every child has to leave home
but I want you to know,
that door is always open.
You can always come back.
'Cause I love you.
I love you, Pops.
I'm just so confused right now.
I feel like I'm caught
in some kind of a tailspin
and no direction makes sense.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
When Rex died, I didn't even know
if I wanted salt on my eggs
let alone keep building cars.
But then, you remember
that night we sat together
we watched old Ben Burns
and Stickleton?
You remember that?
That night, something just clicked.
Like a light being switched on
inside of me.
After that,
I never had trouble remembering
how I liked my eggs.
Jeez, Pops, that's just it.
- That's part of my problem.
- What?
That race, the 43 Prix.
Burns and Stickleton? It was fixed.
Royalton told me the whole story.
It was all about
some DNF named Potts.
They've known the winner
of every Grand Prix
for the past 50 years.
It's always fixed.
I don't believe that.
Royalton's a crook.
- You can't believe a crook.
- I don't think he was lying, Pops.
The Grand Prix, a sham?
- Horuko.
- Forgive me for intruding.
But I had to come
before it was too late.
This is not a trick. I swear to you.
I'm not my brother.
Are you gonna ask the lovely lady in?
Yeah, sure. Come on in.
Can I get you something to drink?
No. My security man believes
I'm still at the opera
so I only have a moment.
I'm very sorry for what happened.
What my father and brother did
was not right
and I'm ashamed.
It's fine.
Just another lesson learned.
No. It is they
who are in need of a lesson.
This rightfully belongs to you.
An invitation to compete
in the 91st annual Grand Prix.
My brother was planning
to decline anyway.
But I studied the rules
very carefully.
And as a member
of the winning Togokahn team
if you present this invitation
on the day of the race
they must allow you to compete.
What do you think of that,
Mr. It's Always Fixed?
- I...
- You don't have to say anything.
I only hope you drive as you did
in Casa Cristo
and you wipe the smiles
from their faces.
We don't have a car. Sparky!
No. No. He'll yell at me!
- Yo, right here, Pops.
- What are you doing in the kitchen?
Same as everyone else.
I don't believe it.
You were listening the whole time?
- And I'm so glad I did.
- We were so worried about you.
Horuko. Thank you.
I would say, "Good luck Saturday,"
but you don't need it.
You're already very lucky
to have such a family.
Come on, we got work to do.
Pops, the race
is less than two days away.
How fast did Royalton say
he could build that tin can
with his fancy machines?
- Thirty-six hours.
- Then we'll do it in 32.
Come on, let's go.
Ladies and gentlemen,
behold the future!
Sparky? You ready?
Ready, Pops.
Pops,
that's a Bernoulli Convergenator.
Transponder schmonder.
You want real kick, you go Bernoulli.
Were you here last year?
- No.
- Yes, you were.
The Colosseum has begun to fill.
Final preparations are underway.
And we're expecting
the largest television audience
in Grand Prix history.
We've got an incredible lineup
this year
like the Gray Ghost Sonic
"Boom boom" Renaldi
Nitro Venderhoss,
and The Scarlet Valentine.
Not to mention C-ball.
Cannonball Taylor,
fastest Grand Prix seed in history
driving the new GRX
from Royalton Race Cars.
- Thanks, doll.
- You're welcome.
We've got an odd numbered field
this year
one shy of a full boat
as Taejo Togokahn declined
his automatic invitation
after winning the Casa Cristo.
All right, let's start her up.
Sounds beefy, Pops.
Yeah, I gave it
a little something extra.
Come on! Let's load it up!
Hold on.
Something's going on over there.
We're seeing some kind
of commotion down
at the trailer entrance.
Excuse me.
Is there a problem here, Officer?
Sir, we have a problem.
What madness is going on here?
Mr. Royalton,
this is a legitimate invitation.
We have verified it.
- Where did you get this?
- I won it fair and square.
This is preposterous.
He can't be allowed to race.
- It's too late.
- The ruling on this is quite clear.
Try to stop it
and you'll be in blatant violation
of the WRL charter,
leaving me no option
but to shut this year's Prix down
until a full investigation
can be completed.
What? Have you any idea
what that would cost?
- Are you insane?
- Try me.
Something big is going on,
because every race official has...
- Ladies and gentlemen
- Wait, wait, an announcement
- your attention, please.
- Is being made.
Now driving in the 40th
and final position...
Holy s♪♪t!
for Racer Motors in the Mach Six,
Speed Racer.
A million dollars to the driver
that takes out Racer.
He won't even get out of the blocks.
I'd prefer him to not even make it
out of the locker room.
We're installing a spearhook
in the GRX.
I don't need one to beat that punk.
A precaution.
As the cars take to the field,
you can feel
the anticipation mounting
in the audience.
Something is different.
There's an electricity in the air.
The presence of Speed Racer
has completely changed the equation.
How are you feeling?
It's big.
That cockpit is the exact same size
it was at Thunderhead.
Right.
I wanna say thank you
for what could be
the most exciting moment
in my whole life.
Couldn't have gotten here
without you.
I'm looking forward
to that cold milk.
Me too.
Ladies and gentlemen,
start your engines!
The final countdown has begun
and a stillness has fallen over
this stadium as all eyes turn
to one car.
Ten.
(Foreign language)
This ain't a race.
This is a showdown.
Trouble at the start.
A misfire traps Speed Racer,
causing a collision.
Look out.
That kid is wily!
I don't know how he got out
of that one, dude!
Nice, nice.
Speed Racer blows by Katsu
Toppledama
charging into the Moguls.
He's taking on all comers.
Kelly Kellencoff makes a move,
cuts him off!
- A big mistake!
- Speed fakes left, jumps right.
He slips in behind Gearbox.
Here comes over under.
I told you! I told you!
Speed Racer seems unstoppable,
moving up from dead last
nearing the leaders.
Go, Speed!
But look out,
as they approach the Big Drop
here comes Speed Racer.
Speed Racer is knocking on the door
of Cannonball Taylor!
Yoohoo, anybody home?
Okay, Mr. Two time Grand Prix,
Five time WRL Future Hall of Fame
teach me something.
You ready?
Let's go!
(Turkish)
Get that weak shit off my track!
Come on, that move is weak.
Cannonball Taylor's in trouble!
Tear him up, kid, tear him up.
(Foreign language)
Come on, is that all you got?
- (Turkish)
- (Spanish) It's the demon on wheels.
Lesson's over.
See you at the finish line.
Do it. Stop him. Stop him now.
- Oh, no!
- What is it?
Spearhook! He's got me!
Cannonball has Speed pinned
as they grind
through the butterfly turn.
That cheater! He's using a spearhook!
(Foreign language)
Spearhook!
Cannonball clearly using a spearhook.
That could cost him the Hall of Fame.
Not to mention what it might do
to Royalton Industries.
Shame on them.
Oh, no... don't do this!
The Triple Phase Conductor's fried.
Sparky, get me back in this race.
What is it? What's wrong?
The crash must've dislodged
the main conductor.
Starter's overloaded.
(Foreign language)
(Spanish) Both cars are dead.
The nickel hydride cells
are hemorrhaging.
I've got dendrite readings
everywhere.
- What do I do?
- Don't panic.
Just listen, Speed.
Just listen to her.
- If I could defibrillate the...
- Sparky.
Give me a second.
Is there anything he can do?
I ran a patch through the starter
to the Bernoulli Convergenator.
If he puts the car in fifth gear,
he could jumpstart the whole thing.
Will he know that?
Would Sparky?
What do you need?
He's back in it!
Come on, kid, move it!
He's gonna do it.
I don't know
why I'm doing it anymore.
You don't climb into a T-180
to be a driver.
You do it because you're driven.
Racing has nothing to do
with cars or drivers.
You ready to put away your toys
and grow up?
Are you ready to become
a real racecar driver?
Look at the split!
He's shattering the lap record.
If you know so much
why don't you tell me
why I should keep driving?
That's for you to figure out.
I just hope when you do
that I'm there to see it.
(Spanish) It's over!
When I watch you do some
of the things you do...
that you just take my breath away.
You remember that night?
We sat together
we watched old Ben Burns
and Stickleton.
That night, something just...
clicked.
Racing hasn't changed
and it never will.
(Foreign language)
It doesn't matter
if racing never changes.
What matters is
if we let racing change us.
When I'm in a T-180, I don't know,
everything just makes sense.
No hesitation, nothing fazes him.
No one seems capable of stopping him!
He's on a mission.
With a quarter lap to go,
Speed Racer is back.
- Two cars between him and destiny.
- Stop him!
Here we go again.
(Foreign language)
- No!
- (Spanish) Come on!
Yeah!
Speed Racer, whoo!
Yes!
Yeah!
It's pandemonium!
People here have gone
completely crazy!
In 14 years, we've never seen
anything like this.
It's a whole new world, baby.
It's a whole new world.
He did it.
Yes, he did.
This could change everything.
It already has.
My men are bringing the family down.
Do you want to go with them?
No.
Can I ask you a question?
Do you ever think you made a mistake,
hiding the truth from them?
If I did...
it's a mistake I have to live with.
Speed!
Come on!
Thank you, Speed.
I love you, sweetie.
That was so beautiful.
I'm proud of you, son.
Warning, the following image
may be unsuitable
for the uninoculated
or cootie sensitive viewers.
Okay, Chim Chim, go!
Speed, are you all right?
Never mind that, Trixie.
I've gotta get you out of here.
You're wonderful, Speed.
Why don't you try to win this race
fair and square?
You have beaten us, Speed Racer
but I solemnly swear,
you will pay for our defeat!
We will race you again!
Soon.
And we will beat you!
We'll be counting on you, Speed
and the future of world peace
will rest upon your shoulders.