That way, that way.
- Nothing here.
- That damn...
"Take up arms, Italians!"
Yeah, we sure will.
Let's wreck this place, come on.
I'll piss on that.
This'll teach them to leave
some valuables home next time.
Let's scram!
Why don't you try and rebel now?!
STREET LAW
A. MEROLA'S - FINE WATCHMAKING
Excuse me? I have to
collect a parcel on delivery.
- Desk number six.
- Thanks.
- Can you process this?
- Yeah.
One million two hundred
and fifty thousand lire.
Freeze! This is a hold-up!
Be quiet and still!
Don't move and
no funny business!
I'll kill whoever tries
to press the alarm!
I'll take this.
Open the safe and
fill this up, quick!
Everybody face the wall! Now!
Where do you think you're
going?! Against the wall!
You too!
To the wall, move it!
No, young man, don't...
Shut her up!
Shut your trap or I'll kill you!
Fuck! Outta the way!
Can it! Shut up!
Get a move on and
empty the register!
Fill them up! Move
it and hurry up!
You keep still and
don't move an inch!
Hurry up! Get a move on!
Hurry up, hand
over all the money!
Stand up! Stand up, dammit!
Face the wall! Move
it! Move it, I said!
- Stop her!
- Hold it right there!
Shut up or I'll empty the whole
magazine into your mouths!
What are you trying to do?!
Run for it!
- Quick, we gotta go!
- Don't you try to move!
On your feet! You're
coming with us!
Move it!
The money! Hand it over!
Go!
Hurry up and run!
Keep going!
- Get in the car, quick!
- Let's move!
We must do better if we want to
carry out our hat-trick of robberies!
Only this jerk is to blame!
You tried playing the hero, huh?
Assholes like you
gotta learn the way it is!
I swear, if things go sour for
us, you'll be getting it worse!
Step on it!
Look out!
Here they come!
Step on it! Faster!
Car 2 calling HQ, they're on
the road near the waterfront.
They're heading south.
Hear you loud and clear.
White car, four robbers inside.
The vehicle is heading
towards Corso Italia.
Exercise extreme caution,
the robbers are armed.
- Calling Car 12, over.
- Car 12 speaking, over.
They have a hostage,
presumably wounded.
Be careful, they are armed.
Copy that, over.
We'd better head back towards the city
centre if we want to lose them, turn left!
Calling Car 7, requesting
their current status, over.
City centre, on Via
Venti Settembre!
Go! Go!
White car, Alfa Giulia model,
license plate Genoa 446719,
they are leaving Corso Italia
and entering Via Venti Settembre.
Heavy traffic.
They're done for!
Blast it! There's another one!
Watch it, they're firing.
Don't get too close.
They're on Corso Italia and
headed towards Ponte Assereto.
- Copu that. Go.
- Calling all cars.
Calling Car 6, 9 and 12 to
converge on the robbers' vehicle.
Keep going!
Go, come on!
Car 7 calling HQ.
We had an accident and lost
contact with the robbers' car.
We're heading
back to Corso Italia.
- Awaiting orders.
- Car 7, we're in Via Felice Cavallotti.
Car 73 to Car 7, white Alfa headed
towards the docks area on Via Gramsci.
To all cars patrolling Ponte San Giorgio,
Ponte Etiopia, Ponte Resea and Ponte Libia,
the robbers' white Alfa is
headed towards the docks.
Car 18 to Car 73, we're
reaching Ponte Assereto.
Car 73 to Car 19, converge to the
shipping containers section of the docks.
The post office robbers' car has been
reported in the Ponte Assereto area.
The post office robbers' white car has
been reported in the Ponte Assereto area.
Car 19, copy that. We're
heading to Ponte Assereto.
Calling Car 16. Robbers'
car located in Ponte Assereto.
Converge to the shipping
containers section in Ponte Assereto.
Car 19 to Car 73, we're
reaching Ponte Assereto.
We have reached the white Alfa.
Car 73 to Car 12 and 16, robbers' car
located in shipping containers section.
Car 19 to Car 73, we
found the robbers' car,
only the wounded hostage is
on board, we need an ambulance.
Don't worry, everything's fine.
You're lucky, nothing's broken.
An ambulance is on its way.
Stay back, everyone.
Nothing to see here.
I... I'll kill them!
I swear I'll kill them!
They're dead if I get
my hands on them!
- This one?
- No.
You recognise this one?
No.
- This one?
- No.
Are you positive?
Yes.
I'll never forget those faces.
Amateurs, probably, considering you
couldn't identify these slides you've seen.
They were professionals.
They only pretended to
be on edge, to scare us.
Ah, I see.
You're one of those individuals
who'd like to teach us our trade.
I'm not trying to
teach you anything!
I just want you to
catch those criminals!
And yet, here I am feeling like I'm the
crook being grilled by you people!
Are you going to
cooperate or not?
Plenty of robberies every day, we can't
post a policeman on every corner.
This kind of criminals are armed
and dangerous, not to be provoked.
Even bank tellers are
instructed to comply with robbers.
Very unwise of you to resist.
Resist? I wasn't resisting!
I... I only tried to
get my money back!
It was hard-earned,
you understand?
They hit me! What
was I supposed to do?!
Thank them and say I was sorry?
"Please, go ahead
and destroy my face!"
"The police won't let
you get away with this."
Police, right...
You wouldn't catch a criminal
if he landed on your hands.
Please, Carlo, calm down now.
Forgive him, it's the reaction
of a man with a broken head.
Broken but thick.
You're one lucky individual.
You got off easy.
Right. Nothing really happened.
You don't care about
citizens like myself.
Do you feel better after
lashing out at the police?
You could have gotten arrested
for insulting a public official.
Stop thinking about
what happened.
I was scared and
they humiliated me!
You cannot even
imagine how scared I was!
It wasn't because they had guns.
I just can't lose
my self-respect!
I'll kill them if I
find them again.
Don't talk nonsense.
- Be reasonable.
- Are you asking me to be a coward?
Better to be cowardly
than reckless.
Sure, right, you're suggesting me to
keep feeling scared and humiliated?
And only because there's
nobody willing to protect us!
ITALIANS, REBEL!
NOW IS THE TIME!
I'm sick of being kicked around!
What did the police do
when they got here? Nothing!
They didn't lift a finger after crooks
robbed and almost torched down my home!
They only asked if I'm insured!
Like I'm in cahoots with the thieves
to cheat the insurance company!
Of course crimes
are on the rise!
Criminals wouldn't go around
killing people if they kept them in jail!
If I died I'd save them the
trouble of arresting the culprits!
You've got to stand up for yourself,
no one else would protect you.
What could you do
on your own, Carlo?
If you're so keen to play the hero,
why don't you marry me first?
- So I'd have your pension and insurance.
- Knock it off, Barbara.
Becoming a wealthy widow
doesn't sound too bad.
Don't you understand that one's gotta
fight their fears to overcome them?
My only fear is for your sanity, after
taking so many blows to your head.
You're not special, you know?
You think this is the wild west?
Bandits ride into town and you put
your star on before blazing them away?
Quit complaining and playing the
victim! You're acting like a pathetic wuss!
- Excuse me, I'm looking for some people...
- Scram, fool.
Is there a tall, blond man who speaks
the Veneto dialect among your customers?
I get people of all races.
Yeah, it's three young men,
with lots of money to splash.
I wish, I only find
deadbeats around here.
Excuse me, I'm
looking for three...
I dunno, try the hotel
'round the corner.
You a cop? Only clean customers
here. Check the guestbook if you fancy
Try the docks.
Who are you anyway?
Who knows you?
- Listen, where can I find...
- You lookin' for trouble?
Look for Armando, tell him
the Parisian girl sent you.
You staying or what? Gonna
cost you more if you rent a room.
I need to contact some people.
You dealing with
hot stuff? Take a hike.
- I'm looking for a guy from Veneto who...
- We don't know nobody
- I'm looking for...
- Put an ad in the papers!
You again?! What the
hell do you want from me?
I only need some names.
Looking for weed? Gino
from the alley's your guy.
- Hello, Ma'am.
- What is it?
Is Gino home? I
need to talk to him.
- Who are you?
- A friend of his.
No, he's not here.
He went on vacation.
When will he be back?
Who knows? Maybe with the
next amnesty, if he's eligible.
Really? I heard he got paroled.
Well, he missed the friends
he made in the slammer.
He got right back to prison.
Where can I find
some of his friends?
Bar Italia, behind the
Shanghai street market.
Get your American
jeans right here.
Transistor radios, gas
appliances, I got everything.
Tell the man I'm
looking for him.
There will be blood if he
doesn't cough up my money. See you.
- Take it easy, tough guy.
- Oh boy, indeed.
- Here's your aperitifs.
- Gee, it was about time.
Say, what happened last night?
Did they try to attack the party HQ?
Tried's the word, it was six of
them putting posters on the wall.
They skedaddled as soon as
they saw us, same old story.
Managed to grab one by the
collar, you know what I told the guy?
What will it be?
"I know you're a red, pal, but
I'm gonna beat it outta you!"
So I throw the guy against the wall
and do a number on him with a chain.
Damn coppers appeared
out of the blue, such a shame!
I am looking for
some information.
Why, you're carrying my
favourite business card!
- I'm looking for somebody.
- I'm sorry?
Mind saying that again?
I'm a bit hard of hearing.
Lean closer.
Get bent, mate!
You fellas took this place
for an info point or something?
- Why?
- This guy here's seeking information.
And you came to this place?
You better check the yellow pages
instead of busting our balls, pal!
Wait, let's see what he's looking for.
we're all for helping our fellow citizens.
We're all here, spill it.
We're eager to help you out.
What the fuck are you
looking for anyway?
Well? Cat got your
tongue? Speak.
You came here
for a reason, right?
What do you want?
- I have a car for sale.
- A car? A stolen one, I presume?
Ah, it's a piece of cake.
Look. Go over there, take a
left and then turn right.
When you reach the loo, jump
in and flush, understand?
Watch it! What's
biting you, mate!?
Played you like fools!
Made you look like a chump!
Let's get him, hurry!
Now you can sell it
to the junkyard, fool!
Don't show your face around
here again, understand?
Let's go!
Are you crazy? You wanted to
get in touch with the underworld?
They can smell
you're not one of them.
Carlo, those people are a
different breed, don't you get it?
They have stricter
laws than ours.
You've defended some of them
in court, put me in contact with one.
Are you crazy? I'll never
do something like that!
I don't want you
on my conscience.
You do not realise the kind of people
you are trying to get in contact with.
Robbers and ruthless criminals
who kill people without thinking twice.
No way I'm putting you
in touch with any of them.
Forget about this,
Carlo, trust me.
Be grateful you're still alive.
Even you tell me to let it go
and forget what happened!
What do you want me to tell you?
At my age, I realised that this
world is like a theatre of sorts.
I have entered, watched the
show and soon I will exit the stage.
It is something I have come
to accept, with no regrets.
- You know what I mean?
- Yeah, yeah, sure.
I guess my father
just died for nothing.
You were with him when
he wrote the manifesto...
... calling on Italians to
rise up against the Germans.
You shared the same ideals then.
And now you just keep your mouth
shut and suck it up like everyone else.
You know what my father
wrote before they shot him?
"Remember, you must learn
to resist if you want to be free.
If the laws are unjust, it is not only
your right to disobey them, but your duty."
The law is like a spider's
web, you can catch flies with it.
Too bad the bigger
flies break through.
Our web is so broken that
it doesn't even catch gnats.
Too much work to keep track of them, they
stay in jail three months and then get out.
Back and forth like commuters.
Here's the dossiers you wanted.
What are you looking for?
Car stealing? Armed robberies?
There's no shortage of choices,
and the culprits are all out there.
You know why judges wear black?
They're in mourning.
I wouldn't know what
to choose between...
... falling into the hands
of a doctor or a lawyer.
It's like choosing between
a hammer and a hard place.
THE ROBBERS OF THE PETROL STATION ATTENDANT
IN VIA NOVARA HAVE BEEN IDENTIFIED
THE MUGGING OF AN ELDERLY LADY
THEY SMASHED THE SHOP WINDOW AND STOLE
THREE MILLION LIRE WORTH OF JEWELLERY.
Seems like ages since we've seen
each other, you could have given me a call.
Hi.
Hey.
Found anything?
Not even the police were
able to get to those three,
but criminals all
know each other.
That's why I'm after
some small-time crooks.
I'm getting more knowledgeable,
and I'm beginning to recognise the
techniques of the various gangs.
You must also take care
of your work at the lab.
Leone is dealing with that.
- Any luck concerning your gang?
- My gang?
I found out a lot of things, even that
they take hostages when things go wrong.
They usually rob
three banks in a row.
While the police
rush to the first bank,
they are already robbing
the second, and then the third.
They specialise in hat-tricks.
They steal about thirty million
lire each time and then disappear,
going on vacation
for a few months.
This is our newest
comic book hero.
Here, keep it for luck.
It's a hunting dog, like you.
Be careful, Carlo. Please.
Don't worry.
I'm sorry about the other day.
Forget it.
Hello? Yeah, I'm working
on it, like I told you.
At last, Carlo! What
happened to you?
That company has been
waiting for your report for a week.
- Take care of it and send it off, please.
- I knew it.
- Good morning, Engineer.
- Good morning.
You leaving already?
Yes, I'll be away for a few
days, you take care of the lab.
Heh, like I haven't already...
I wonder what the guy is
cooking, hope it's not trouble.
HE LEAVES THE HOUSE
AT 3:30 P.M. AND GOES TO...
Got a light?
Looking for me?
Why have you been
following me all day?
I dunno who you
are and I don't care.
Anyway, it's gonna be trouble
if I see you around again.
Got that clear?
I'm an imbecile, dammit!
... And this in the
case of a ferrous alloy,
most notably stainless steel.
The diagram is divided into
two parts, as you can see.
The first, less anodic,
is the activity area.
which ceases at the
passivation curve.
This yelds an average
value which is basically zero,
reaching the passivity area.
Therefore, if we...
Hey, but...
Oh, sh...
Good grief, mate.
I'm gonna smash the bastard
who took these pictures to bits.
- This is no joke.
- How do you call it?
Casting call pictures
or something?
- This guy's out to get you.
- Both of us.
Well, then he would have also
chosen some pictures with me.
What, you jealous?
You reckon the cops
are involved in this?
Someone trying to blackmail
you, that's my guess.
Who am l, Paul Getty?
Boy, do I look like a million.
I WILL CALL YOU AT THE PHONE
BOOTH IN CORSO PODESTA' AT 3:30 P.M.
Hello? Who the hell are you?
What do you want from me?
Listen up, scoundrel.
If you want those negatives,
get me a sawed-off shotgun, two machine
guns, two pistols and a hundred bullets.
Sure, lemme go to the nearest grocery shop
and fix them up! You need cigarettes, too?
You realise how much
that stuff would cost?
One hundred thousand lire per
gun and two thousand per bullet.
Where am I supposed
to get that kind of dough?
Wait a second!
I don't know anything!
I was just talking
for the hell of it!
I'm gonna behave
from now on, yes sir.
- It's the truth, I swear.
- Cut it out, you idiot.
If I were a cop, I could throw you
in the slammer with those photos.
Hurry up and get that stuff, you'll have
the money tomorrow night at ten o'clock.
Still playing
soldiers at your age?
This? No' just preparing
a prank on a friend.
You brought the stuff?
Everything's fine. It's all
clean, no serial numbers.
- Where's the dough?
- How much?
Five hundred thousand lire.
Prices have gone up, blame
it on the currency devaluation.
You'll find three hundred
thousand lire in the bin behind you.
You'll get the rest
tomorrow night at ten.
Hold it! What about
the negatives?
Son of a bitch...
Hello?
I knew you'd try to play
a trick on me, dummy.
If you don't bring me the
stuff I asked for tomorrow night,
your next robbery will be in five or
six years, when you get out of jail.
There's two hundred thousand
lire in the phone book, take it.
If you try to get smart with me
one more time, you're finished.
Place your bets.
That's it, no more bets.
- Red. Eleven wins.
- The house loses.
- Eleven wins.
I'd quit if I were you, Peppe.
The house wins.
Nice going, luck's
on your side tonight.
The cops! It's the cops!
Freeze, everyone!
Good evening, Inspector.
I'm so glad to see you.
Care for a little pool game?
You sure you're
not up for a game?
- Another time.
- Whenever you wish.
Let's go.
See you, boys.
Come again soon.
Hey, Gambino!
Scipione sent
me, he says that...
He says you can get
me some hardware.
Didn't he tell you my
name's Mr. Gambino?
- Sorry.
- What do you need?
One sawed-off, two
machine guns, two pistols.
- For you?
- No.
Who wants it?
Some independent professionals from
out of town who'd prefer to stay anonymous.
- Who are they?
- I can't name names.
- Price goes up, then.
- That isn't a problem.
These folks are
rolling in dough.
- How much you got now?
- Two hundred thousand. A little advance.
Good enough for
a three-days rent.
Ammo paid separately
- When do you need the stuff?
- Tomorrow night.
Contact Scipione, he'll
give you the location.
Listen, pal, you are acting
too much like a smart-ass.
Sure, you're blackmailing me with
those pictures, but I've had enough!
It's all getting too confusing
and I've had enough!
What else do you
want from me, dammit?!
Calm down.
I have one last request,
then you get those pictures
and we go our separate ways.
I need the best
robbers in business.
Determined men, who know how to use
machine guns and sawed-off shotguns,
with an expertise
in bank robberies.
Tell them to stand
by, I'll be in touch.
It's them! It's them!
I knew I'd find those
sons of bitches again!
Police? Get to the Nautilus
Shipyards at the harbour at once!
There's a warehouse full of weapons,
along with the three post office robbers!
- How do you know that?
- Who cares?! Just hurry up!
- Who are you?
- Move it, for christ's sake!
Repeat the address.
Nautilus Shipyards!
Send somebody!
You're in there, you bastards!
I got you good this time!
Where's the police? What
the hell are they waiting for?!
Christ, no!
They're getting away!
What the hell are
the police doing?
the police doing?!
Emergency service my ass! Why
did it take you so long to get there?!
Mobile Unit! What a joke!
- Could you please stop shouting?
- No!
I'm going to kick
up a stink here!
I want everybody to know
you let them get away!
Either you're incompetent
or in cahoots with them.
- What?
- Somebody warned them!
Who could have done
it? I've been on my own!
I acted on my own!
The tip-off must
have come from here.
You better watch your mouth.
You people know who the
fences and arms dealers are!
All you have to do
is put them in jail,
but you hold on to them instead.
Because when there's dead bodies involved,
they're the ones you seek information from.
That's enough!
Do you realise that you are in this
room to cooperate with the police?
Know your place and don't
forget who you are talking to.
I can lock you up for
insulting public order,
and it is not inconceivable
that I will do so sooner or later.
You must understand that the
underworld is well organised.
They have both money and means.
And they may be able to intercept
our radio messages to the patrol cars.
What are you going to do to
the owner of the warehouse?
We can't arrest people
without evidence.
Evidence?
I saw them delivering those
weapons with my own eyes!
There must be
an arsenal in there!
I recognised the three
who robbed the post office!
But sure, you probably think they were
fooling around, playing cops and robbers!
What I say doesn't count, huh?
You cannot take justice
into your own hands!
You'll end up hurting
yourself or others!
I'm tired of entrusting my life to
people who don't give a damn about me!
Tired of continuing to suffer and being
a good, meek and compliant citizen!
The state is like a deity.
We owe it everything, and
it gives us nothing in return!
No use playing the
victim, the blame is on us!
Every nation has the
government it deserves!
What do you think you
are solving with a gun?
What do you think you are
going to solve by doing nothing?
You are deluded if you
think you are going...
... to change anything by
playing the lone vigilante!
Carlo! You better
put on a wool jumper,
the marble slabs at the
morgue are rather chilly!
Hey! Who are you?!
Get out! Out!
Hey, this is a misunderstanding.
I'm serious about that girl.
I mean, it's not
like she's underage.
Besides, she started it.
Who the hell are you?!
Her father? Brother?
Husband?
Why are you so pissed off?
I get it, you're
a police officer.
This stuff ain't mine,
it belongs to... Damn!
Get dressed, you're
coming with me.
Do it again and the police will
get your pictures tonight.
So you're the
scummy blackmailer!
Dammit...
I should have known.
You've been tormenting me
with those phone calls for a week.
I got those guns for you, and even
put in touch with those three folks.
What the hell you
need more, I ask?
- The names.
- What?
Give me the names and whereabouts of those
three, and you'll have the negatives.
You're nuts.
Rat them out and you'll end up at the bottom
of the sea with a rock 'round your neck.
- Give me their identities.
- I don't know them.
It's the truth, l
never met them!
All right, we'll
find them together.
Get dressed and let's go.
Absolutely no way.
So, what you want me to do?
I want those three, get some
ideas and do it pronto.
I had my last idea so long ago I can't
even remember what it was about.
Stop talking like a jackass.
at least I'm not planning to
act like one, like you are.
Shut up and think of the quickest
way to get in touch with them.
Boy, thinking sure
gives me a headache...
I'll give you a right one if
you don't start cooperating.
Here we are. Come with me.
Hey, where are we going?
To see Mrs. Cavallo.
- Who's Mrs. Cavallo?
- Gino Cavallo's wife, ever heard of him?
Gino Cavallo is the
best robber in all of Italy.
She became a
snitch after his arrest.
A real lady, she
knows everybody.
She's always willing
to help a friend in need.
Behave accordingly, huh?
Good morning,
Ma'am! Remember me?
I'm Tommy.
Yeah, I do remember you.
So...
What will it be, handsome?
What can I do for you?
You see, Ma'am, this friend
of mine is in a bit of a pickle.
- We could use your assistance.
- Something special?
Well, in a way...
It's something we'd
like to keep quiet.
Follow me.
Go on.
She doesn't want to snitch in
front of too many people, you know.
So, what's the matter?
- I'm looking for somebody.
- Oh, well...
I guess you just found the
person you were looking for.
Take off your
clothes, pretty boy.
Now listen, I'm looking for somebody
else and I don't have time for this.
- Tommy said that...
- What's wrong with you?
- That rotten bastard!
- Where are you going?!
I'm a professional,
you stupid idiot!
The steering wheel lock!
Right.
What have those guys done to
you? Why are you trying to find them?
- Mind your business.
- Oh, it's my business alright!
They'll kill me if
I swindle them.
Stop the car.
Use that phone
booth to call them.
Your change.
It's Tommy. I need an answer.
All right.
They're suspicious. They want to
know who you are before doing anything.
Yeah, I bet they do.
They said to wait for
them at the gasometer.
I told you, they won't show up!
They're too suspicious!
Come on, let's get out of here.
Why do you want to
go through with this?!
keep being a criminal?
You think I got a
calling or something?
There wasn't enough
to eat in my house.
Sure, I stole, but in my
situation you would have too.
You could have found a job.
And who would want to hire a kid
who entered juvenile detention at 13?
That was the only
school I went to.
First year: car theft.
Second: house breaking.
Third: lockpicking
and breaking windows.
Next time I'll go to prison I'll
prepare a thesis on armed robbery.
All paid for by the state.
No graduation if they
keep you locked up for life.
Nope, they won't get me.
You see, I just need
a couple more jobs.
Nothing too serious on a felony level,
but that would make me a lot of money.
Then I'll open a nice car
repair shop and retire for good.
How much did you manage to save?
Not a single dime.
I only have a single regret, you
know: not being somebody else.
What's that? An
advance for the shop?
In a way.
Hey...
You're a friend.
Now mark my words: forget about
those guys, stop looking for them.
Why are you so eager to die?
Come on, I'll take you home.
Take me to your friends.
You just don't get it, do you?
Let's go.
All right, whatever!
It's your choice!
Why don't you reconsider?
Hey! Watch out!
- What's wrong?
- I think I got a flat tyre.
Where are you going?
Get out!
Step out of the car, let's
have a look at your mug!
Look who's here, what
a nice surprise.
The hero from the post office.
Found us at last, heh?
Must be the kind of guy
who's never satisfied.
He's back for another beating.
All right, we'll deal with
you for good this time.
Bastard!
Now mark my words: forget about
those guys, stop looking for them.
Why are you so eager to die?
You think this is the wild west?
Bandits ride into town and you put
your star on before blazing them away?
This kind of criminals are armed
and dangerous, not to be provoked.
Very unwise of you to resist.
Relax, it's me.
I know, you're right, but I didn't
think they'd beat you to a pulp.
Come on, time to
get away from here.
Let's go, come on!
What are you
waiting for? Hurry up!
Come on.
Good, like this.
They've really done
a number on you.
Come on, let's move.
Don't worry, I'm holding you.
Crap!
Get up! If they find
out we're done for!
Get moving or I'm
leavin' you here, mate.
They mustn't
know I set you free.
Why are you helping me?
Because I've never killed anyone
and I don't want you on my conscience.
Move your ass now.
Let's go.
Come on, you can do it.
No! No! No! Don't!
Stop!
Damn...
What are we gonna
do if he's dead?
I told you things
would end ugly!
Look at what you've done!
Well, talk about an
upstanding citizen.
Go fuck yourself, mate.
To say I almost
believed your crap.
If all honest people are like
you, give me prison any day!
Now what? You thinking
of goin' to the cops?
"Good morning, gentlemen, I just
offed one of the post office robbers!"
That's gonna be your next move?
How you goin' to prove it's one
of the guys who took you hostage?
You got nothing to show!
You're in deep shit, mate.
- Both of us.
- No way!
If you're thinking of using me as a
witness I'm gonna vanish into thin air!
You don't have those negatives
anymore, so good luck blackmailing me!
Nice way of showing me your
gratitude for saving your skin, by the way!
You're going to prison if the guy's
dead, but the others will remain free!
Wanna know what'll happen next?
They'll bribe some inmate
to ice you in the slammer!
You'll end up
like a proper twat!
GALLIERA HOSPITAL
Zilch! He's nowhere to be found.
I even asked a mate who works at the
morgue: no new arrivals, nothing at all.
That son of a bitch's gone.
- Maybe his friends hid the body.
- For the nice memories? It'd be nonsense!
The body's hot evidence,
they'd ditch it right away.
They would have had it found immediately,
perhaps disfigured and unidentifiable.
The guy's still alive,
mark my words.
He ain't six feet under yet.
Hey, stop making that
face. I told you, he's alive!
Have a laugh!
Here, have a smoke.
You serious about that
advance to buy the shop?
I know my way around cars.
One whiff of an engine and I
can tell what's wrong with it.
And one look's enough
for a full check-up!
Hey, I'm serious. We'd
be great business partners.
- Hey, isn't that your house?
- Yes!
What's up with all those
firefighters and cops in front of it?
Wait, stay here. I'll go.
- What happened?
- It was them!
They found out where you live!
Keep your head down!
Those sons of bitches...
They wanted to make
another number on you.
They wanted it to
hurt, the bastards.
Pouring a petrol tin
under your door...
You'd be done for
if you stayed home.
Those guys are gonna
hunt you down now.
Damn cops being useless.
They should nail those bastards!
What's their names? Tell me!
I swear, I dunno.
I only saw them when
they beat you up.
I reckon you should
turn yourself in.
That's the only way you can get
some protection and stay alive.
They'll find me everywhere
if they really want me dead!
You said so yourself,
didn't you?
Anyway, it's a matter
between me and them.
It's not fair for you to get
involved because of me.
- You better disappear.
- And you're suggesting that now?!
You should have said it before
getting me into this mess!
- What are you going to do?
- Let's stick together.
- All the way?
- Heh.
Come with me, you need a shower
and a change of clothes.
You reek.
I recorded five sequentially
numbered tapes.
The information they contain is to be
released to the press in case I am killed.
- All right, change reels.
- Sure, what title you want on it?
Third reel: "organization
of the underworld."
I'd like to see their faces when they
can't find the reels we didn't record.
They'll find the tapes, but
they'll be completely destroyed.
Ready.
As the police know, the
underworld is built on many levels.
Reel four: "connections between
the police and the underworld."
You're gonna unleash pure chaos.
Ready.
I discovered that the
criminal Michele Gambino,
owner of an illegal gambling den, has been
meeting with the three post office robbers.
Their last meeting took place
at the Nautilus Shipyards.
I called the police,
and soon afterwards...
... I saw Gambino and
the others fleeing in a car.
They could only have been informed of the
police's arrival by the police themselves.
The names of the policemen involved with
the underworld can be found in reel five.
Where do we hide these
for the police to find them?
Here.
Poor Leone! He's in for a shock
when he gets back from the weekend!
You're pretty sly, Engineer!
You're going to
cause quite a mess!
I hope so! What would
you do in the police's shoes?
You'd think there were who knows
what revelations on those tapes,
and you'd do your
damnedest to find them!
If you say so.
Shame to leave all this
stuff here, it cost a fortune.
It's a present for the police.
Except this one.
Well? Are they tapes?
Yes, Inspector. They
look like magnetic tapes.
We'd better wait until the
lab confirms this theory.
Hey, who's this guy
that got kidnapped?
It must be someone very important,
considering how worked up everyone is.
Borelli, come here. I've
found two tapes here.
They've burned a
few others over here.
They probably
didn't find these ones.
Perhaps the most compromising
things were on the burned tapes.
I told you, Inspector, last
night everything was in order!
I came in this morning and called
you immediately after finding this chaos!
Did you try to get in
touch with the engineer?
I would have, but
I cannot find him!
He's not home and I
haven't seen him for days!
I mean, he used to call every
now and then, but lately nothing.
Look at this mess, how
am I supposed to work now?
Be careful with the press.
Let's be cautious.
The less we tell
them, the better.
They just can't
wait to stick it to us.
When they find
out it's Antonelli,
they'll connect everything
to the post office robbery.
You know journalists
better than I do.
We do our job, but they
always seem to know everything.
- Who's this?
- Engineer's girlfriend.
What happened?
Tell me, did they...
No, we're convinced he's alive.
- Try to calm down, please.
- Calm down?!
I won't calm down
and I'll shout if I want to!
It's your fault! You
didn't give a damn!
Carlo told you, but
you wouldn't even listen!
It's your fault.
Borelli, you stay here.
See you at the office
when forensics are done.
I want the staff
in for questioning.
- Tommy?
- Yeah, it's me.
- Did anyone see you?
- Mate, I'm not that dumb.
Look! Will you
take a look at this!
- We did it!
- Boy, we sure dropped a bomb!
There's even a
picture of the lab.
Read the title! "Engineer Carlo
Antonelli has been kidnapped!"
- This one?
- No.
Another dummy, huh?
"Is the mysterious disappearance
of Engineer Antonelli...
... caused by murder or kidnap?"
- You read this one?
- Yes.
"Antonelli was collecting
evidence of complicity...
... between the police
and the underworld."
- Well, talk about good news.
- Yes, yes.
Lippi's asking if he can send out
the men for that operation we planned.
Yeah.
We must search
every inch of the city.
Find dealers, pimps, gambling
den owners and fencers.
Scare up bail jumpers, sooner or
later somebody will give us a lead.
Tell Lippi permits
are suspended.
I want every available officer. 24/7.
The police have gone wild!
Everyone's gone crazy!
People are under pressure, you
wouldn't believe the chaos out there.
Things aren't getting
nice for those three.
Word has spread that
it's pivotal to nail them.
- Did the police identify them?
- Police? The underworld!
They've decided those three are too hot,
so it's time to throw them at the cops.
It's a way to quiet things down.
You bastard, you
gotta help me out.
That so? But I helped you
out when you needed me!
It's your turn now!
What? What?!
I'll make you pay for this!
Hello? Hello?
Son of a whore...
Why did you come to me?
- Bourbon?
- No, thanks.
Some friends suggested
me to come here and, well...
Friends? What friends?
You don't have any.
Hey, I'm staying
here, understand?
Until you do something
to help me out.
Oh, swell...
Miss? Call the police.
This ain't over, I'll show you!
Desolated, nothing I can
do. You're a marked man.
- But I...
- Friends and foes, all looking for you.
I don't want to end up in the
river with a rock around my neck.
I'm sorry, but you'll have to ask somebody
else to take your nuts outta the fire.
Now listen' if I make it you and those
other assholes won't get away with this.
Yeah, yeah, you'll show me.
But if the other fellows find you first,
you know what they gonna do with this gun?
They'll shove it right
up your butthole!
Freeze! Don't move and
don't touch those tables!
Over there, block those exits!
You finally up for
that pool game?
The time for games is over. Put on your
coat and move it, you're coming with us!
- There he is!
- Look over here, Mr. Gambino!
- Back off.
- Peace and goodwill, boys!
Don't you worry,
it's just a false alarm.
- Make way.
- One more photo!
Keep snapping! Look
over here, Mr. Gambino!
Look over here!
One more picture!
Who are you? What do you want?
- Relax, I'm a friend of Carlo's.
- Carlo's?
I couldn't let you know or
you'd have been in danger too.
All right, but now
that I know everything,
don't expect me to help
you in this madness.
I had no choice, and it was the
only way to get the police moving.
It'll be over for me if
they don't catch them.
- No turning back now.
- And if the police catch you?
They could jail you
for simulating a crime.
It's a risk I have to take.
The police wouldn't act
unless it's a noisy case.
I can't believe you don't understand
how absurd this situation is!
Look at what they've
done to you, Carlo.
You must forget about all this.
Let's move to another city.
I beg you, Carlo.
Do it for me.
It's no use, Barbara.
It's not just a personal
matter anymore.
I must go all the way now or I wouldn't
be able to live in peace with myself.
I'd be ashamed of myself.
I love you.
Of course you do.
You love me yet you're doing
everything to get yourself killed.
That's how it'll end, Carlo, and
you want me to sit down and wait.
Help me.
I put myself in this, but I need
a reason to come out of it alive.
The disappearance of Engineer Antonelli
is still shrouded in complete mystery.
During their operation, the police have
discovered many warehouses of stolen goods,
as well as arresting
some fencers.
Roadblocks led to the arrest
of several convicted criminals.
However, there seems
to be no real lead so far.
Does your car repair
shop offer still stand?
Of course.
Prick up your ears, then.
I'm on the right track now.
I can get you the names
and addresses of those three.
Their fathers' details don't matter,
considering they're sons of bitches.
Who's going to give
you the information?
Somebody who
was in the business.
- When?
- Later.
I'll be meeting him
in a couple hours.
- I'm coming with you.
- No, Engineer.
I have to go alone, otherwise
this guy won't spill the beans.
All right, but be careful.
You be careful, otherwise
who will I open the shop with?
- Tommy, is that you?
- Yeah, it's me.
- You alone?
- Yes.
Yeah, I'm alone.
No, I don't believe you!
You have my word.
I'm alone, I swear!
You're with them!
You brought them here!
Why do you keep
trying to screw me?
You're not a friend,
you're just a...
Tommy!
Come on out, you bastard!
No! No!
We'll send him in
one piece at a time!
Carlo! Carlo!
Help me!
I didn't... I didn't...
Carlo, I didn't set you up!
I swear I didn't! Help me!
Come on out, you filthy bastard!
Carlo!
Carlo, kill them!
Blast them away!
Blast these sons
of bitches to hell!
Lookin' for us?
The rat's here, now
the cats can play!
Hold it! Where do
you think you're going?
Stop squirming, you bastard!
Move it!
Tommy...
Come on out, bastard, or
we'll kill him one bullet at a time!
Come on out already!
Save your friend!
Come out, you're not
getting out of here alive!
Come on out, asshole!
Hey! Come on out!
You heard them! Come on out!
They'll kill me if you
don't do something!
Run, Tommy! Run!
Please! Mum!
Mum...
No...
No!
Tommy!
You bastard!
You see? We showed them...
You really did.
Do I deserve a shop or not?
You bet.
We are going to open the
biggest car repair that ever existed!
We'll put in lots of sports cars,
and you'll always be
there to test and fix them!
We'll have so many clients!
Everybody will want
Tommy to fix their car!
Damn...
You found me a
fine looking shop.
It looks swell...
Just the way I wanted it.
It feels like a dream...
Yeah, and we'll fill
it with luxury cars!
So many that we won't
know where to put them!
We'll put the sports
cars over there.
The luxury ones will go there!
We'll have a lift
to the upper floors!
And an office with a big staff!
At night the shop
will be floodlit!
And it will always be
packed with pretty girls!
Do you like it, Tommy?
Christ!
The police intervention
saved your life.
The officers killed your
captors during a shootout.
That's going to be
the official story?
It depends on you.
Sign this paper
and you're free to go.
- No charges, no arrests.
- You feeling generous?
- Aiming for a promotion, maybe?
- No.
I'm doing what I've
been instructed to do.
We can't risk other hotshots
to follow your footsteps.
If citizens start taking the
law into their own hands,
who will distinguish honest
people from dishonest ones?
This is the best
solution, believe me.
I hope you'll finally
understand it.
At the bottom of the
statement there's a declaration...
... that the captors forced you to
make those statements against police.
Sign.
And don't forget we can gather new
evidence at any time to re-open the case.
Against you.
I'm insured! But they cover damages,
they're not the ones who have to defend me!
Police are supposed to do
it, even your posters say so!
You even dared ask me if l
have a permit to carry a gun!
Why don't you ask the same
question to the people who robbed me?
Four times I've been robbed! But you better
pray the lord it doesn't happen anymore!
Next time I'll open fire first,
I don't care against who!
Don't you realise citizens are fed up of
risking their lives every time they go out?
They've had enough
of this! Enough!
Subtitled by Francesco Massaccesi
THE END