( rock music playing )
( birds chirping )
- ( alarm buzzing )
- ♪ Sometimes ♪
♪ I can't help
the feeling that I'm ♪
♪ Living a life
of illusion ♪
♪ And oh, why can't
we let it be ♪
♪ And see
through the hole ♪
♪ In this wall
of confusion? ♪
( splashes )
- ( groans )
- ( splatters )
( groans )
...29, 30, 31,
32, 33, 34...
( squeaks )
♪ Pow... ♪
♪ Right between the eyes ♪
♪ Oh, how nature loves
her little surprises ♪
♪ Wow, it all seems
so logical now ♪
♪ It's just one
of her better disguises ♪
♪ And it comes
with no warning... ♪
- Hey, Andy!
What's up, Dude?
- Hey hey, Joe.
- Hey, Sarah.
How are you doing?
- When you gonna get a car?
- Hey hey--
Why don't you get a car?
- I can't afford it.
( both laugh )
Hey, so, uh--
"Survivor" tomorrow night,
are we on?
- See you then.
- I'll bring the soda.
- Hey, enjoy your orange.
- Okay. Take care.
See you, bye-bye.
That guy needs
to get laid.
- ( both laugh )
- Tell me something
I don't know.
Good morning.
Hello.
Excuse me.
- Pardon me.
- ( cars honking )
Sorry.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
- Good morning.
- Hey.
- Good morning, Paula.
- Andy.
Excuse me,
I have a question.
What is the difference
between Hi8
and digital
video tapes?
Um, I'm not a salesman,
so I could proba--
Welcome to Smart Tech.
How can I be of service
to you?
Um... well,
I was just wondering
what is the difference
between these.
Salesman:
Well, if I'm
photographing someone
as fine as yourself,
probably the digital.
♪ Hey, don't worry,
I've been lied to ♪
♪ I've been here
many times before ♪
♪ Girl,
don't you worry... ♪
My God.
Sorry I'm late, man.
Oh, no problem.
Oh, man.
- I had a weekend.
- Yeah?
We went
to Tijuana, Mexico...
- Mm-hmm.
- ...you know, and we--
we-we thought
it'd be fun, you know,
to go to this show.
"You gotta check out
one of these shows,"
and you know,
it's-- it's a woman
fucking a horse.
We get there and, you know,
we think it's gonna
be awesome, and...
it is not
as cool as it sounds
it would be, man.
It is-- it's--
it's kind of gross.
- Yeah.
- You think "A woman
fucking a horse,"
and you get there,
and it's--
it's a woman
fucking a horse.
- Yep.
- It was really
giving it to her.
And you know what?
To be honest, I felt
bad for her.
- We all just felt
- Yeah.
- Kind of felt bad
for the horse.
- Wow.
- That's something.
- So did you, uh...
- what did you
get up to?
- Um...
uh, you know,
I just kind of hung out.
I was-- God, Friday,
when I went home,
I really wanted
an egg salad sandwich,
and I was just obsessing
about it, I was like,
"Man, I'm gonna make
one of those," so--
so Saturday I went out
and I got...
like a dozen eggs,
I boiled them all,
and then I just...
I-- I spent-- I don't know,
probably three hours...
like three
and a half hours making...
you know, the mayonnaise
and the onions
and paprika--
you know,
all the accoutrements,
and then by the time
I was done, I just really
didn't feel like eating it.
- I can imagine.
- And I didn't have
any bread.
So... you know,
it was pretty good.
- It was a good weekend.
- Sounds pretty awesome.
- Yeah, it--
it was fine.
- Sounds really fun.
- Cool.
Cool cool.
- Hey, Paula.
- Yeah?
I gotta tell you
something. I'm really
excited about it.
Uh, for the first time,
today...
I woke up, I came
to the store,
and I-- I feel confident
to say to you
that if you don't take
this Michael McDonald DVD
that you've been playing
for two years straight off,
I'm going to kill everyone
in the store and put
a bullet in my brain.
David, what do you
suggest we play?
I don't care. Anything.
I would rather--
I would rather watch
"Beautician and the Beast."
I would rather listen
to Fran Drescher
for eight hours
than have to listen
to Michael McDonald.
Nothing against him,
but if I hear
"Yah Mo B There"
one more time,
I'm going to yah mo burn
this place to the ground.
You're such a smart ass!
Get back on the floor.
♪ I'll be holding on... ♪
( fakes sneeze )
Fuck you. Oh.
- How about Andy?
- No.
Come on, man.
We need-- what?
--five guys to play
a decent poker game, right?
- Yeah.
- If we cancel, I might have
to go to some stupid-ass
birthday party with Jill,
and that ain't happening.
- No.
- Man: Why not?
He's a really
nice guy and all,
but I'm pretty sure
that he is
a serial murderer.
Who cares, man?
He's a nice guy.
I just wanna get drunk,
- fucked up,
and play some cards.
- That's great.
Look, I don't wanna end up
a lamp shade in some
creepy apartment,
- that's what I'm saying.
- I don't really see
any other options.
Andy!
My man!
- You got any plans
later on tonight?
- Why?
- Do we have to unload
the Sony truck?
- No.
No, the guys are
getting together,
we're playing some poker,
thought, you know,
you'd wanna play.
With you guys?
Yeah yeah, sure.
That'd be cool.
- You know how
to play, right?
- Yeah.
- I play online sometimes.
- We're gonna play
in the store.
Great. Are we
allowed to do that?
- Absolutely not.
- Yeah.
Oh. Oh, well,
so I'm gonna go
tell Paula.
I'm just kidding.
I'm kidding,
that sounds great.
Well, cool. I'll see
you guys tonight.
- Okay.
- All right.
- ( clangs )
- Oops.
- I almost feel guilty.
- No, you don't.
I'm hot tonight.
You're going down!
- Going down!
- You dumb ass.
- And a full house.
- ( man laughs )
Oh my God.
How much online poker
do you play, dawg?
An hour or two a night
when I'm not playing Halo.
Where did
you get this guy?
He's a fucking ringer, man.
This is hogshit!
You! You're a fucking asshole
to tell me come here,
tell me he was
a nice guy, didn't you?
Motherfucker, you been playing!
Fuck you, you and you.
Fuck and kiss my big, round
fucking ass, okay?
- I'm gonna
see you tomorrow.
- Peace.
- All right, man.
- Fuck a goat!
- ( all laughing )
- Good night.
- I love that guy.
- Dude, you totally fu--
Oh, shit,
I gotta go. Damn!
- About to go see
Ellen in a little bit.
- Going now?
- Late night action, huh?
- Dude, you know
how it goes.
Your girlfriend
know about all these
late-night visits?
It's like an unspoken
agreement, yeah.
It's like
a completely and utterly
unspoken agreement.
- ( laughs )
- If you knew her--
if you knew who I was
dealing with, you wouldn't
be saying shit.
There's nothing you
can't do with this woman,
straight up and down.
I literally sit at home
trying to think of things
to do to her.
I'm dead serious.
Sometimes, I just
sit for hours
just staring
at the sky trying to come up
with something to do.
I even don't know
if she can walk. I've never
seen her standing up.
I've only seen her
on her back.
- Wow!
- Yeah, that's sick, man.
- Wow.
- That is not sick.
- I will give you sick.
- Oh, shit.
I was sleeping
with a woman recently.
She had-- her tits
were unbelievable.
Oh, man.
I love titties, so...
And, uh...
so we're doing it,
we're about to finish
and her dog starts
licking my ass.
- ( all laugh )
- I-I-I have to decide,
- "Do I finish,
or do I stop the dog?"
- I know your nasty ass.
- He finished.
- I finished!
And then I stole
the dog.
No, I didn't, but--
You know, sometimes
Amy and I would make love--
it was almost like
we weren't two people,
but we were two...
spirits or something.
Our-- our souls were
connected in this way--
I can't describe it.
Time stood still.
It was like we were
sharing the same heart.
Stop! Man, why do you always
come and kill the vibe
with those things?
"Sharing the same heart?"
That's like some...
Britney Spears shit, man.
This is three grown ass--
don't nobody wanna
hear that shit!
Yeah, man, come on!
Nobody wants to
hear that shit.
Thank you, Andy.
Dude, you-- you broke up
two years ago.
- You like get over it
at some point.
- Two years, man.
You need
to get past that
because no ass is worth
thinking that much about...
- I always say.
- Andy, do me a favor?
Will you please help him
redeem himself,
- by telling him
a real sex story?
- Yes.
Uh... I don't--
you know what?
I'm-I'm a gentleman
and I don't--
you know?
I don't kiss and tell.
Fuck it. I raise you--
nastiest shit you've
ever done.
- I'm talking
about nasty.
- Uh...
Wow. So many stories
are running through
my head right now.
I dated this girl...
for a while,
and she was really
a nasty freak.
She just loved
to get down
with sex all the time.
She was like--
any time of day,
she was like, "Yeah,
let's go!
- I'm so nasty!"
And I'd be nailing her...
- Oh, shit.
...she'd be like,
"Ah, you're nailing me!
- Cool!"
- She talk dirty to you?
Oh, she loved
to dirty-talk.
Totally into it.
She'd be like,
"Yeah, let's screw,
let's--
I wanna fuck."
God, it was so dirty.
She'd be like,
( high-pitched voice )
"Oh, me so horny.
Me love you long time."
- So...
- Man #2: So, what are
the titties like?
- Yeah, describe her, uh--
- Man #2: Yeah.
Oh, yeah, she had
great tits.
Oh, no no no.
I mean like detail her.
Did she have like--
- you know them little
pink teeny nipples...
- Oh, yeah.
- ...or the long "National
Geographic" nipples?
- Long.
Did you have
the bumpy brown nipple--
- the Stevie Wonders?
- Andy: Yeah, they
were nice.
You know, when you--
you grab a woman's breast
and it's--
and you--
you feel it, and--
it feels like
a bag of sand...
when you're touching it.
A bag of sand?
You know what I mean.
Why don't we just play?
- Why don't you just
deal the cards?
- Nuh-uh.
- What are you talking about?
- Have you ever felt a breast
before, man?
- Yes.
- Dude, are you gay?
No, I'm not gay.
I've been with
tons of women.
I touched a guy's balls
at Hebrew school once.
Dude, it's not a big deal
if you like to fuck guys.
I'm cool.
I got friends
that fuck guys...
- in jail.
- No, I'm not gay.
No, I've borked
a lot of women in my day.
- You've "borked"?
- Hold on, hold on,
hold on.
Yo, answer this question.
Are you a virgin?
Y-yeah, li--
not since I was 10.
It all makes sense!
You're a virgin!
I am n-- shut up.
- How does that happen?
- He's a fucking virgin.
Oh, knew it! That makes
so much sense, man!
- He's a virgin!
- You guys are hilarious.
All right, guys.
Come on, don't be mean.
I'm not being mean.
I'm trying to help the--
I'm trying to say
I wanna get you laid, dude.
- I understand what's
going on with you.
- You guys are so...
- up your asses.
- From now on, your dick
is my dick!
- I'm getting you some pussy.
- ( men laughing )
( laughing echoing )
"A bag of sand"?
Come on, man!
You can do better
than that!
God, "me so horny."
No, me so stupid!
( screaming )
Oh, come on!
( laughing )
It's gonna be fine.
They don't even remember.
Those guys are cool.
( alarm buzzing )
This is gonna be bad.
Come on!
- Hey, David.
- Hey, Andy.
- What's up?
- Cal, good morning.
Yeah, man.
- Man: Hey, Andy.
- Hey.
We're gonna have
to get you some punani.
Andy!
It's going down, partner!
We're gonna be--
( grunting )
This for you, partner!
This for you!
Waves of it coming
at you on Friday,
Saturday.
By Sunday your nuts
going to be drained!
Andy, don't let them
bother you. It's okay
not to have sex.
Not everybody
is a pussy magnet.
You, uh--
what are you?
- 25?
- I'm 40.
Holy shit, man,
you've got to get on that.
Life isn't about sex.
Life is about children
- and passion.
- Yeah.
- And spirit.
- Yeah, life's about passion.
It's not about fucking
and balls and pussy.
It's about love.
It's about people.
It's about connection.
- It's all about connections.
- It's not about cock
and ass and tits...
- Mm-hmm.
- ...and butthole pleasures.
It's not about butthole
pleasures at all.
It's not about
this rusty trombone
and the dirty Sanchez...
- Please stop.
- ...the Cincinnati bowtie...
- Mooj.
- ...and your
pussy-juice caulking
- and the shit-stained balls.
- Mooj, just please stop.
- It's relax--
- All right, that's enough.
Party's over.
Let the virgin
get back to work.
Andy!
Andy, come on!
We were just kidding!
- Sorry.
- Andy, nobody cares
that you're a virgin!
Don't be such a baby!
They were just having fun!
They didn't mean anything!
- Get away from me, David.
- Wait a minute!
- Stop following me!
- Hold up.
Andy:
Shit.
- Whoa.
- I'm gonna have
to quit my job now.
- You don't have to quit.
- I don't wanna go out
with you guys!
- Fine. Okay.
- I don't need
your help!
All right. You don't
have to go out with us
if you don't want.
I respect women,
I love women.
I respect them
so much that I completely
stay away from them.
- Okay.
- I have a very
fulfilling life.
( tooting )
- ( playing continues )
- And now, I am making your
silver pants blue.
Get some road burn,
come on!
Come on, sucker!
♪ Yo, pretty ladies
around the world ♪
♪ Got a weird thing
to show you... ♪
( laughs )
Oh my God.
( tooting )
- So how could this
not have happened?
- It just never happened.
When I was young...
uh, I tried,
and it didn't happen.
And uh...
then, I got older,
and I got more and
more nervous
because it hadn't
happened yet,
and I got--
kind of--
weirded out about it.
Then it really
didn't happen, and--
then, I don't know. I just
kind of stopped trying.
Do you wanna
give it another shot?
Maybe it's too late.
Bec-- I-- sometimes
I feel that it is just
too late for me.
Oh... no, that's cra--
that's crazy.
You're 40 years old.
You know, 40's the new 20.
You wanna spend
the next 60 years
of your life
never experiencing sex?
And not just sex,
but-- but love,
and a relationship,
and laughing, and--
and cuddling
and all that shit.
I don't know, I--
- I wouldn't know what to do.
- Look, you gotta take a risk.
You gotta risk it.
Look at me, I went out
with this girl for four months,
and it was the greatest--
greatest thing in my life.
Until she went
down on this guy in
an Escalade, I think.
And you know,
instead of like saying,
"Okay, what I am doing
that caused this behavior?"
I dumped her.
Stupid decision--
I spent the last two years
of my life regretting it.
Then, why don't you
get her back right now?
Oh, 'cause she's
dating this pot dealer.
It's a stupid,
horrible decision.
But hey, that's
her journey, you know?
I gotta respect that.
I gotta give her the space.
If she wants to be some
immature, little bitch
and blow everybody,
that's--
that's love, man.
- That sounds horrible.
- Of course it's horrible.
It's suffering,
it's pain, and it's--
you know, you lose weight,
and you put back on weight,
and then you call 'em
a bunch of times,
and you're
trying to e-mail her,
and then they move,
they change their e-mail,
but that's just love.
Do you realize that
this is the first time
we've spoken
- for more than,
like, 30 seconds?
- Uh-huh.
- God, it's kind of nice.
- Come out with us
this weekend.
No pressure,
we'll just have
a good time.
Okay, yeah,
I will.
- I'll give it a shot.
- Great.
But I am not
going to have sex
with anybody.
Good, sex should be
the last thing
on your mind.
( funk music playing )
♪ Hey, but what
you gonna do ♪
♪ About that?
Yeah, but what you gonna do ♪
♪ Eow, about that? ♪
♪ I got ants in my pants
and I need to dance ♪
♪ Come on! ♪
Okay, that's not right.
♪ Hey hey hey... ♪
Oh, come on, bus!
♪ Hit me ♪
♪ Uh! Hit me ♪
♪ Eow! Hit me,
hey! Hit me...♪
Oh, come on, dogs!
Shit, you gotta
be kidding me.
I mean,
I'm kind of nervous.
I never had
oral sex before.
Jennifer told me
how to do it.
It's gonna kick ass.
- ( zipper opens )
- ( screams )
- You know what else
is sexy?
- What?
- Me...
- Yeah?
- ...sucking...
- ( chuckles )
...on your...
- toe.
- Oh, that's what
you wanna suck on?
- Yeah, it's just
so big and...
- ( laughs )
- ...thick.
- Okay.
Yeah.
( chuckles )
- ( laughs )
- It tickles.
- ( screams )
- I'm sorry.
Oh, no no no--
I'm-- your nose
is bleeding.
- You think?
- I'm sorry.
You are terrible
at this!
You should just
give up forever!
( echoing )
Oh God! Oh...
G-- oh.
- ♪ 'Cause, baby, there... ♪
- ♪ Ain't no mountain... ♪
- Cal, what do you think?
Is this too yellow?
- No.
- What's Curious George
like in real life?
- Come on, man.
♪ Now to the beat,
jump-jump on the dick ♪
♪ Don't eat,
suck-suck on the clit ♪
♪ That's right,
jump-jump on the dick ♪
♪ All night,
suck-suck on the clit... ♪
Wow, this is, uh,
pretty crowded.
Yeah, well,
it's nine dollar
beer night.
Okay, look here.
So this is what's about
to happen, a'ight?
You're about to go run down
some drunk chicks, a'ight?
Don't confuse that with tipsy.
We're talking about drunk.
I want vomit in the hair,
bruised-up knees--
a broken heel is a plus.
That's what you wanna
find, okay?
- If things--
- No, Dave already
told me
I didn't have
to have sex tonight.
And now he's gone, so...
Dude, stop thinking
for a minute, a'ight?
- You ain't got
the think on this one.
- Yeah?
All you got to do
is use your instinct.
How do you think
a lion knows to tackle
a gazelle?
It's written.
It's a code written
in his DNA.
- It says "Tackle
the gazelle."
- Okay.
And believe it or not,
in every man there's
a code written
that says
"Tackle drunk bitches."
N-- oh God,
you know what?
- I don't feel
comfortable...
- ( blows raspberry )
...hitting on drunk bitches.
You know, I don't think
that's right.
Okay. Hold on,
hold on, hold on.
Now, first of all,
you making it up to be
some kind of bad thing.
I didn't use "bitches"
in the derogatory
sense you did.
It just doesn't--
this doesn't feel right.
Of course, it don't
feel right. What has felt
right for you doesn't work.
You need to try
some wrong, dawg.
Okay, how do... I tell
which ones are drunk?
So we just decided--
because this is
my last night
as a free woman
before I marry Dan--
that we would
just wig out!
We're wigging out!
You guys are hilarious.
Whoa whoa whoa!
Wait a minute.
Yes yes, Mr. President?
Yes yes, the election
results are in.
Hey, guys, look.
It's Dr. Seuss' penis.
I really mean this.
Hey, everybody,
who wants penis cake?
- I do.
- She does.
Hey, you guys,
Betty "Cocker."
( all laugh )
What a good guy.
What a-- Dan,
the guy Robin's marrying,
is such a good guy.
- He sounds
like a good guy.
- Oh.
I hated him
like for two years
'cause he cheated on me.
- Oh.
- But...
( moans )
he's really changed now.
He's a really good guy now.
- Your friend seemed nice.
- You have really kind eyes,
you know that?
Thanks, um...
your hat has sequins.
( both moan )
Mmm. Whoo.
- You have your hands
on my belt.
- What?
- Your hands
are on my belt.
- I'm sorry.
- No, that's good.
- You're cute.
This is kind of lame.
You wanna get out of here?
- Okay, yeah, so... ahem.
- ( giggles )
Mmm.
- Mmm. Man! Fuck!
- Yeah.
- Come on.
- Okay.
♪ I said it before,
I'll tell you again ♪
♪ Have you wishing
I was your girlfriend... ♪
- You wanna drive?
- I don't-- um...
- have a car
with me here, so...
- Oh, that's cool,
I'll just suck it up!
- I'm driving.
- ( beeps )
- Are you drunk?
- No, I didn't have
anything to drink.
- Blow into this?
- Oh, okay.
( laughs )
( beeps )
- What is this?
- Oh, the judge
recommended I get one.
- ( engine starts )
- ( hip-hop music playing )
Whoa, okay!
Wow, that's fast.
- ♪ Gimme some new shit... ♪
- Okay.
Com on,
you're on the lasso!
( tires screeching )
♪ Missy be putting it down,
I'm the hottest around ♪
♪ I told y'all mother-- ah!
Y'all can't stop me now ♪
♪ Listen to me now,
I'm lasting 20 rounds ♪
♪ And if you
want me, nigga ♪
♪ Then come on, get me now,
is you with me now? ♪
And Pam's like, "You are
such a b-i-t-c-h--
- bitch!"
- ( tires screeching )
And I'm like,
"You're the bitch, bitch!"
- You know?
- Uh-huh, yeah.
What was your name again?
- Andy.
Let me tell you
something, Andy.
Don't ever
be named "Dan."
Dan rhymes with man,
and men jerk off,
and he was a jerk-off.
- Do you know what I mean?
- Yo, look out!
- Andy: God!
- ( tires screech )
- Andy: Wow, um...
- I like you.
I like you.
You're not a jac--
Ooh, ah. Ech.
I think I ate some
bad shellfish sandwich
or something.
- ♪ What da dilly yo,
now what da drilly yo... ♪
- You're cute.
- No!
- ( tires screeching )
♪ Let me know ♪
♪ Got to feel it, son,
I know you feel me now... ♪
- ( gasps )
- Hmm, that tasted good.
Oh, that tasted
like shellfish.
Look out!
Oh! Sorry!
- Oh! Watch it!
- ( cars honking )
- Am I gonna die?
- ( tires screeching )
- Do you think
I'm pretty?
- Oh, yes.
Yo, a car!
Yes, a car!
- Oh!
- You're not
looking at me.
- Yes, you're pretty.
- You're not looking at me.
- Do you think I'm pretty?
- Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
- Look at me. Look at me!
- ( yelling )
Look at me!
- I'm looking.
You're pretty!
you're pretty!
( hysterically )
God, I just wanna live!
God, I hope I get
my period soon.
I am in a bad mood.
- Okay.
- I'm so tired.
Hey. Hey!
Whoa! No! No!
Oh God! Out of the way!
- Oh!
- Hey!
Get off the wheel.
Jeez.
You're not gonna
get in my pants
acting like that.
I'm starving!
Let's get some
fucking French toast!
( screeching )
Okay, here we are.
Oh God, we made it!
- Woman: Home sweet home.
- Yay.
- Oh! Mommy!
- ( screams )
( pants )
Are you okay?
- That fucker came
out of nowhere!
- Oh.
- Okay. Okay.
- ( laughing )
Are you--
are you okay?
- ( sobs )
- Whoa-- are you--
what's the matter?
- I'm sorry.
- Oh, that's okay.
I think I kind of
had that coming.
I'll still have
sex with you,
if you want.
You know what? I think
I'm gonna pass on the sex,
if you don't mind.
At least I don't have to
work out tomorrow.
Did you have
a daiquiri tonight?
- Yeah.
- I thought you might.
It was a very bad night.
- Whoo-ah!
- Yeah, laugh.
You know what?
You guys wouldn't be
laughing right now
if some girl had
just vomited shellfish
sandwich into your mouth!
- ( grunts )
- You know what?
You're right, it's my bad.
Let me apologize
to you first of all
for not mentioning
in detail
that when you pick up
a drunk woman
who's falling down
on her way out of the bar
that you should
probably drive.
I drive a bike.
Okay, Mr. Schwinn-
fucking-Armstrong,
who asked you
to drive a bike?
You know what?
I'm not the only person in
the world who rides a bike.
Yeah, everyone rides a bike--
when they're fucking six.
Why don't you
kiss something?
Because this-- this is over
you guys, okay?
Can I just interject
for a second?
Let me just say, you are--
you are putting the pussy
up on this pedestal.
You're just building
the pussy up.
What are even talking about?
"Building the pussy up."
What does that mean?
You're making the pussy
into this great big
Greek goddess
named Pussalia,
and what you're doing is,
you're psyching yourself
into thinking it's
some impossible feat.
Yeah, I think you're right.
I'm putting the pussy
up on a pedestal.
- Right.
- That's it.
It's Pussalia, right?
- Look where you going.
- I don't want to say
the word anymore.
- Say what word?
- Pussy. I don't want
to say it.
Pussy is
a scientific word.
Dude!
New pants, man!
You know what, Dave?
You said there wasn't
going to be any pressure.
- We're not pressuring you.
- Excuse me.
Can one of you guys
help me please?
- No hablo English, lady.
- Oh.
I actually am helping
a customer right now.
- Okay, well, um...
- I'm on break,
but our stock supervisor
is very knowledgeable.
He can answer all
your questions and he'd
love to help you.
- Oh, thank you.
You too.
- Have a nice day.
Uh, great, okay.
Hi, I'm Trish.
Hi. Andy...is my name.
This one looks pretty good.
- You don't want
to buy that VCR.
- I don't?
No, actually to be
totally honest with you,
you don't want to buy any VCR.
It's a dead technology.
- It's, you know,
like getting...
- What the hell?
- ...an 8-track player...
- Yeah.
or a beta-max.
Actually I'd recommend
this one.
This is a dual.
You've got the VCR
and DVD combo.
So, you know,
that technology will probably
be pretty good for--
- Six months or so?
That's good.
- Yeah.
At best.
Sorry.
- No no no.
- This is as good
as it gets.
- Okay, that sounds
good then.
- Okay.
- Excusa, por favor.
- Oh, sorry.
Coming through.
Muchas gracias.
God, you know,
it's so funny. I work
right across the street,
- and I've never
been in this place.
- Oh, really? Where at?
The We Sell Your Stuff
On eBay store.
Oh, that's the name?
Yeah. Yeah, I was looking
for something...
you know, obvious,
so I chose that.
I don't understand.
So what-- you do what?
I take the stuff
that you don't want,
and then I "sell it"
on eBay.
But you don't actually sell
anything in the store?
No no, I don't.
So why do you
have a store?
( laughs )
I don't know.
No, I think it's because,
you know, I wanna maybe
look professional
and not like a crazy person
who's just going to steal
all your shit.
Sure. I didn't mean
anything by that.
No no, it's okay.
You know what?
You should come by sometime
if you want, you know?
- All right, I'll--
- See for yourself.
Check it out.
I'll check out
your empty store.
Yeah, it's the one across
the street that's not empty.
( laughs )
- Here's my number, so...
- All right.
So just any time.
Why do I need your number
if you're across the street?
Um...
I don't really
have a good answer
for that, Andy.
- Sorry.
- I'm just
giving it to you.
So I'll write you up and meet
you over at the register.
- Okay.
- Check you out--
check out.
- See you over there, okay.
- Okay.
- Awful chatty.
- Hey, that-- I--
look, I think she
gave me her number.
I mean, she wrote down
her number, but I think
she gave me her number.
Oh no, she gave you--
dude, see?
- You still mad at me?
- I was never mad.
See what I mean?
We gonna celebrate, man!
- This is pretty cool.
- Yeah!
Give him some credit, man.
The man pulled a number.
It's just, I was--
I can't believe
that happened.
- What you did
was you zoned in.
- She just gave me her number.
That's great, man.
I'm telling you
- love is
a mysterious fig.
- It is.
Okay, here's a question.
When should I call her?
You like her?
Yeah, you definitely
don't want to call her.
When is
the next Olympics?
What you just got to do
is just get you a bunch
of these hood rats,
run through them.
Just knock them out--
boom boom boom.
And once you've done slayed
like 20-30 of them hood rats,
now you're ready to go up
to the upper-echelon-type ho.
- You know what I mean?
- I'm not a big ho runner.
My uncle used to drive
a ho runner.
Screw these analogies.
What he's saying is
you are going to be so bad
at sex the first time
you don't want to have sex
with someone you like,
because they'll think
you're a weirdo for being
so lame at it.
You want to have sex
with "hood rats" first
so that by the time you
get to the girl you do like,
you're not terrible at sex,
you'll be mediocre at it.
Probably still
pretty bad, though.
Put it up for my man
for pulling that number.
- Way to go, man.
- Politicked his ass off.
- He did politick.
- Thanks a lot.
Like a train,
around the bend.
You ready?
( coughs )
Yeah!
- I can't.
- Do it.
- I can't pee in public!
- Gotta do it.
- I've got
a mental block about it.
- Come on, do it.
( yells )
I'm shy!
( screams )
I'm peeing in public!
- Let me out!
- I can't hear what
you're saying.
- I don't want to be in here!
- It's a sound-proof room.
- Learn his techniques.
- Right on, man.
You guys,
this is not funny!
( sighs )
( phone ringing )
- Hello.
- ( groans )
- Hey, what you watching?
- "Dawn of the Dead," man.
- Great.
- Store is slow,
Paula's gone.
- Is Paula back?
- No no, she's not here.
She said we can't
watch this in here.
You sure?
Can I ask you something
in confidence?
I know this is gonna
sound weird, um...
am I good looking?
Do you think a woman would
find me attractive?
Oh my God!
Oh my God,
the blood just squ--
- Okay, never mind.
- Whoa, wait wait, Andy.
Andy, hold up.
This is embarrassing for me.
This is hard to talk about.
- Are you ready
for my honest answer?
- Yes.
Yeah. I think you're
a good-looking cat.
I don't think that anybody
knows it, and I don't think
anybody can see it.
That's why I'm asking you.
You seem really well groomed
and really put together.
I mean, look dude,
you think this was an accident?
- ( chuckles )
- All of this right here?
Premeditated, partner.
You got to highlight your
attributes. You're like
a diamond in the rough.
- You willing to make
some sacrifices?
- Absolutely.
See that whole "Teen Wolf"
thing you got going
right there?
Just need to wax
that right out, boom.
- Does it hurt?
- No, waxing don't hurt.
I mean, not unless you're
a bitch, you know what I mean?
Didn't hurt me.
I get it done all the time.
What the fuck?!
Oh!
( laughs )
Fuck that nigga up!
Bitch, get out the room!
No, it's gonna be good.
It's gonna be good.
- This is the one right here.
- Hi, how are you?
So this is your first time
getting body wax?
- Yes yes, it is.
- Take off your shirt.
Okay.
Oh, we're gonna
need more wax!
I'm staying.
This is gonna be good.
And clear
all my appointments
in the afternoon!
Here we go.
Oh, that feels warm.
Dave:
I like your sweater.
Does that come in a V-neck?
Cal:
If she starts doing
his pubes, I'm out of here.
Jay:
You're gonna look good
after this, man.
- Thanks, man.
- So, ready?
Yeah.
Ich, ni, san.
( groans )
You fucker!
Oh! I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
That's just your job.
- Do you want
to stop now?
- No no no no.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
( whimpers )
Let's do another.
That one little patch
looks sexy, though.
- Does it look good?
- Cal: Yeah, it looks
really good.
- ( groaning )
- Dave: It looks man-tastic.
Andy: Okay.
Whoo, wow. I didn't
expect that at all.
I really
didn't expect that.
Jay: You got it.
The first one's the only
one that hurts.
Yeah, well those hairs
are pretty deep.
- Okay.
- You ready?
- Yup.
- Ich, ni, san.
( yelling )
Cocksucker motherfucker!
You shithead!
Oh, I hate you!
I hate you so much!
That one hurt.
That one hurt just as much
as the first one.
- That's great, man.
- Andy: Man!
( breathing heavily )
One, two, three.
( screaming )
Fuck me
in the asshole!
- Wow-wee!
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I really
don't swear this much.
You know what?
I got a weak stomach,
that's all I can take.
- I'll se y'all.
- Jay? Jay?
Be tough, Andy!
You got it!
- Where did Jay go?
- Dave: He went to throw up.
- Ready?
- Yup.
- One, two...
- ( all gasp )
Cocksucker
Motherfucker!
You pulled on two!
Why didn't you
pull on three?
Sweaty pie-hole!
Cómo se llama?
Oh, Kelly Clarkson!
And three!
- Y'all done?
- ( Andy screams )
- That's fucked up.
Oh, that's fucked up.
- Andy: Shit! balls!
- Two.
- ( screams )
I hate you!
Stop smiling, you jerk!
- You pussy.
- Oh God!
What's next?
Oh, you're doing the nipple.
- Oh, not the nipple.
- Not the nipple.
Please, Cal,
hold my hand.
- You kidding me, man?
- Hold my goddamn hand, man!
Do it!
Just hol-- okay,
here we go.
- ( grunting )
- Ready?
Oh no.
Yup. Yup.
One, two, three.
( screams )
Oh nipple fuck!
Oh, Mika, you should
burn in hell!
Okay, all right.
No seriously, I think I'm done.
I think we're done.
I think that's good.
( pants )
You know what, guys?
This is not
a good look for me!
You look like
a man-o-lantern.
- Thank you very much.
I appreciate it.
- Thank you.
( yells )
- Can you get--
thank you very much.
- Woman: Thank you.
Andy, I owe you
an apology, man.
I wasn't very nice
to you for the past
- like two and a half years.
- You were nice to me.
No, I wasn't.
I thought you were
really boring
and I kind of thought
you were a serial killer.
- ( laughs )
- I'm not joking.
Look, you shouldn't listen
to Dave and Jay, okay?
Those guys are crazy.
You should listen to me.
Okay, look,
there's a hot-ass girl
who works right there.
There she is, in the bookstore.
You should ask
her out, man.
There's something wrong
with her underpants.
- Cal: Yeah,
they're not in my mouth.
- You know, I kind of...
like the woman
from the eBay store.
That's great, but you're
not gonna get with anyone
unless you play
the odds on this, man.
You need to plant
a lot of seeds.
It's like this,
when I was growing pot
- I realized
that the more...
- Thank you.
...seeds I planted
the more pot I could
ultimately smoke.
I think I have all the advice
that I can handle right now.
- Don't get bitter.
- I'm not bitter!
I almost lost
a nipple, okay?
The problem
most men have is
they just plain,
straight-up have no clue
how to talk to women.
You just ask questions,
okay? That's it.
Because women do not care
about what you have
to say at all anyway,
you know?
And all they want to do
is talk about themselves.
So you're just gonna
let them do that, okay?
So remember:
Questions, be cool
and be kind of a dick.
Here, be David Caruso
in "Jade."
Okay, I know exactly
what you're talking about.
You do?
That's good.
Cal:
Oh, there she is.
Go plant that seed, man.
Plant it
with your finger.
Can I help you?
I don't know,
can you?
Are you looking
for something?
Is there something
I should be looking for?
( laughs )
Um...
well, we have
a lot of books,
so maybe it depends
on what you like.
What--
what do you like?
We have a great,
um, section
of do-it-yourself.
Do you like
to do-it-yourself?
Sometimes.
( giggles )
I mean, if the...
mood strikes.
How is the mood
striking you now?
( both laughing )
What's your name?
I'm, uh, Beth.
Andy.
Andy?
Don't tell on me,
okay, Andy?
I won't.
Unless you want
to be told on...
Beth.
( giggles )
Wow, that totally worked!
I literally said nothing
and she found me fascinating.
- I would have thought you
were doing that for years.
- Should I have asked her out?
No, that's the key.
You wait for her to grow
into a plant
and then you fuck
the plant.
Okay.
This is easy.
All right.
Hello, Trish.
How you doing?
What's going on?
( laughs )
Good joke.
Oh, this is a fun
conversation.
Just grow a backbone
and call her.
She asked you to call her.
She wants you to call her.
- ( line ringing )
- ( breathes deep )
- ( phone ringing )
- Hello.
Hey, how you doing?
- Um, how you doing?
- I'm well.
Who is this?
This is James.
- James?
Do I know you, James?
- ( groans )
I was wondering whether
you had a few minutes
to talk about, uh,
laundry detergent.
Are you
a telemarketer, James?
- Yeah.
- Are you at the top
of a tall building?
Can you get
to a roof quickly?
Jump off!
I mean, you people are sick.
Get a real fucking job
why don't you?
Go shoot yourself
in the fucking head!
Hey, why don't you
just get a knife
and run into it?
- Why don't you do that?
- Okay.
- I'll see you later, James.
- Nice to talk to you.
Fuck your mother, okay?
Bye-bye.
- ( groans )
- ( doorbell rings )
Hey man, got a big
box of porn for you.
Oh.
- Can I come in?
- Uh, yeah yeah.
( sighs )
Sweet video game chair.
So, um...
so what's in the box?
It's my personal collection
of erotica.
- Oh.
- I want to
give it to you.
I think there may be
a few tapes in there
that just might
open up Pandora's
box of love.
- Oh, okay.
- Amy and I,
we used to watch
"Harry Twatter."
And we'd put it on
the television then act
it out as it was going on.
And it was--
it was all right.
( chuckling )
She was adorable.
Fucking bitch.
Well, you know, this is
really gracious and kind
generous and everything,
but I just don't want
a big box of porn
in my apartment.
There's some really
great stuff in here.
Really great great
movies in here, man.
- Did you ever see
"School of Rock"?
- Yeah.
Well this is--
it's called "School of--"
- you know.
- Oh, that's nice.
But it stars
Jack Blackcock.
Oh, that makes sense.
Dude, here it is.
"Boner Jams '03."
It's a mix tape I made.
All these great scenes
that I was really into
in the summer of 2003.
I think you'd really dig it.
Yeah, I can see that.
This is...
"Everybody Loves Raymond."
That's probably not supposed--
that's just a good show.
I tape it sometimes.
I don't think you
understand something, Dave.
I don't want this stuff, okay?
Because I don't do
that that much.
- What, masturbate?
- Yeah.
Are you-- dude,
I've jacked it twice
since I've been here.
- Are you kidding me?
Why not?
- It's not a hobby of mine.
Well, then that's the only
hobby you don't have.
Ha-ha-ha.
No, seriously, I just don't
feel comfortable talking--
You need to.
You're wound up.
You're like action figures,
hermetically sealed
in your box.
- You got to play with--
- Don't! Don't!
Don't! Don't take it out!
I'm sorry.
You know what?
It's just...
it loses it's value if you
take it out of it's packaging.
I'm just saying let it out.
Give it some air, man.
- Play with it.
- Take your porn with you.
- I'm not taking it.
- Take your box of porn!
- That is my gift to you.
- No, I don't want it.
- David, it's not--
- ( yelling ) Andy,
for the last time,
I don't want your giant
box of pornography!
No no, shh!
Come on, man.
That is so uncool.
Uncool?!
Uncool is trying
to give an honest man
a big box of porn, Andy!
Dave:
For the last time
I don't want to watch
"School of Cock" with you.
♪ I've been alone
with you ♪
♪ Inside my mind ♪
♪ And in my dreams
I've kissed your lips ♪
♪ 1,000 times ♪
♪ I sometimes see you ♪
♪ Pass outside my door ♪
♪ Hello ♪
♪ Is it me
you're looking for? ♪
♪ I can see it
in your eyes ♪
in your smile ♪
♪ And I want to tell
you so much ♪
♪ I love you. ♪
( dramatic music playing )
( sighs )
It's nothing official.
Just a little token
of my appreciation.
Eww! Okay.
Okay, new tape.
( laughing on TV )
Nothing is ever good enough
and it's always our fault!
You can't speak to your
mother like that!
- You do.
- She's not my mother!
This right here,
you're looking at the Bentley
of big-screen TVs.
This is the Rolls-Royce
of big-screen-- oh Jeez!
- Dude.
- Sometimes I think these
butterflies are in here.
Hey, Andy, what are you
doing for lunch?
Um, I don't know.
I have a turkey sandwich.
We're gonna go around
the corner. I think you
should come with us.
There's this great place.
Lot of cute girls.
I don't know.
Okay.
We brought you a shirt.
This place
is pretty fancy.
Is something going on?
- Hey, who's ready
to have some fun?
- ( crowd cheers )
Hey, guys.
Hey! No, don't ignore me.
I know what this is.
Within one hour,
you'll each have 20 dates.
Would you just quit
whining like a bitch?
- I'm not whining
like a bitch.
- You are.
Man, you're about
to cram like 10 years
of pimpage into one day.
- I don't want
to cram pimpage.
- Partner, after that...
you on my level.
Come on.
- Cal: Just ask questions.
- This is a bad idea.
( buzzer sounding )
- Hi.
- Hi, how are you?
I'm fine.
Are you fine?
- Yeah.
- You're fine then?
Are you fucking retarded?
What the hell's
the matter with you?
- Do you want me
to be fucking retarded?
- ( buzzer sounds )
When I look into the eyes
of the children
and the parents
and they're smiling and saying
"Thank you, Dr. Montalban,
you saved my child."
- Oh, it's worth it.
- ( buzzer sounds )
Amy.
- What are you doing here?
- David.
And you are Gina?
"Jy-na."
Man, what's up?
- Nothing.
- Look, I'm gonna be
real honest with you.
It's been a long time
since I've been with a man.
Spent a lot of time
with the ladies.
Looking to get back up
on that pogo stick.
- You know what
I'm saying?
- Excuse me?
Remember that time
when we made love and you
cried in my arms?
Please don't reminisce about
the times we fucked. Please!
- It's so creepy.
- Let's go to Paris.
I want to take you
underneath the Eiffel
Tower and make love to you.
- Cut it out!
- Cut what out?
This. "Go to Paris."
We've been broken up
for two years, man.
- I don't want
to date you anymore.
- You're a whore.
I am not a whore.
I just didn't like you.
- This is so us.
- ( both laugh )
- Psycho talk.
- What?!
- You're a good-looking man.
- Thank you.
Very pretty.
Real soft delicate features.
They're real feminine,
which is good for me,
because that would be
a simple sort of transition,
you know what I'm saying?
Maybe throw
a little rouge on you,
tuck your sack back.
You game?
- No.
- ( buzzer sounds )
You need to stop fucking
around with my friend, okay?
Because you're
giving him hope and it's
driving the man crazy.
I moved, I changed
my email address,
my phone number.
- He's practically stalking me.
- Well, I didn't know all that,
- so I am sorry.
- ( buzzer sounds )
Oh, I love Minnesota.
Woman:
I grew up in a town
outside of Minneapolis
with like a population
of like 500 people.
( chuckles )
- Really small.
- Yeah, it's like the land
of a thousand lakes.
What about you?
You're used to
a really big city.
Really-- God, yes.
The town that
I grew up in
was really small.
I mean,
- it was just so safe.
There was no crime.
- Boob. Come on.
I mean, a girl could
just walk from one end
of town to the other
- and just, you know...
- Mmm.
- ...feel completely safe.
- ( fakes coughs ) Nipple.
- ( buzzer sounds )
- Shorty's heading out.
The spank bank has
once again been filled.
( chuckles )
I'll tell you
who was the hottest.
You're going to think
I'm crazy, but I'm
going to tell you.
Gina, man.
I can't get Gina
out of my head.
- Gonna think
of Gina all week.
- I think that--
( gears clicking )
- You know what's
a fun game?
- Huh?
You take three
Excedrin P.M.s
and you see
if you can whack off
before you fall asleep.
- ( sighs ) Oh.
- ( phone rings )
You always win
is the best part
about the game.
- Are you Andy?
- Yeah.
Is this yours?
Did you write this stuff?
My girlfriend Jill found
your speed dating card.
Oh, yeah, right.
God, I've been looking
for that speed dating card.
Thank you so much
for bringing it to me.
So you actually wrote that
one girl looked like she was
"hurting for a squirting"?
Mm-hmm. Yeah, "hurting
for a squirting."
I wrote that.
Oh, so you wrote,
"Ho for sho"?
Yeah, I remember that girl.
She was a ho...
for sho.
Let me show you
how this device works.
- I'm just looking
for a cordless phone.
- Yep, it's great.
You can do anything--
make a video diary.
It's like, "Hey, Amy,
how's it going?
How you feeling?
I'm great!
I feel fantastic
since we broke up.
( shouts )
I feel awesome!"
Can you just show me
the department where
there would be phones?
"How have you been?
What's been going on?
I bet-- hey, have you
been doing a lot of this?"
- ( gags )
- Sir, please, sir.
You are never going to
meet anybody with that kind
of mentality about women,
- you sick son of a bitch!
- Who the fuck are you
to put me on trial?
I've never even met you.
So why don't you back
the shit off
and stop
with the inquisition?
- That's how you talk?
- You know what?
I don't have to
answer to you.
You ain't my bitch.
( imitates hood accent )
Know what I'm saying?
So shit, man.
Fuck it.
You shouldn't
even be hanging out
with this pervert.
I don't hang out with him.
I work with him and that's it.
I tried to introduce
him to a few nice people,
he made a fool of himself.
I don't mess with him.
That's not me.
You should keep
your ho on a leash.
- Hold, bro,
I can't let you--
- Hey hey hey.
- I can't let you be talking
to my woman like that, dawg.
- Hey, bitch is running wild.
You miss that ass?
That's the ass
of a free man.
That ass is going out
tonight, maybe to a club,
maybe to a nightclub.
- Hey, Andy!
- David: I'll give it
to her for free!
- Take a look at your pal.
- Oh my God.
- Yeah, he's performing
a public colonoscopy.
- Shit.
Isn't that sweet?
I'm going to send David
home for the day,
- and you're going
to fill in for him.
- What? Selling things?
- You got that right.
- I don't think that's
a good idea.
You're going to
have to talk to people,
and I know that's
a frightening concept,
but I think you can handle it.
So get out there
and start selling.
- I was making
a thing for Amy!
- Stop, man.
- Pull these-- ugh.
- Check it out.
I miss her.
( rock music playing )
Dude, the floor's
the ultimate aphrodisiac.
All you got to do is
go make your pick now.
Come on, man.
( whispers )
Okay.
- And you could act a little
enthused about it.
- Yeah.
Jay:
That's right, that's right.
Gazelle in the pink top.
- Oh shit.
- Oh, hey. It looks like
- you're checking out
digital cameras.
- You know what?
He ain't going
to do it willingly.
Now we need to facilitate
things a bit more.
- Yo, Andy.
- Yeah.
- Hey, what's up, dude?
This is Jay, man.
- Oh hey, Jay.
I am throwing a party tonight.
It's going to be real mellow,
just chilled out.
Now you really need
to be there. It's going to
be really really colorful.
- Are you free?
- I think so.
That was a joke, man.
I know you're free.
- ( chuckles )
- I'm okay.
- Got to go, man.
- All right, bye.
So tell me, Montel.
Why weren't we invited
to the party?
What are we, Al Qaeda?
- No, hold up. It's not
that kind of party!
- No no no!
You're not coming to our
fucking party either,
okay? Fuck you!
- Yeah.
- First of all, it ain't
that kind of party.
- Go fuck a goat!
- Yeah!
- Why are you always telling me
to fuck a goat, man?!
- Mooj: Fuck a goat!
( disco music playing )
( elevator dings )
( knocks )
Hello?
- ♪ I'm every woman... ♪
- Hello.
- Oh, hello.
- ♪ It's all in me... ♪
Hi. Are you here
for Jay's party?
Yes. I am Jay's party.
Hiring a transvestite prostitute
isn't helping me, man!
What? Ain't nobody hiring
no damn transvestite!
She was really nice,
incidentally.
If that sister
was a transvestite,
that was the Mona Lisa
of transvestites.
You got a hummer
from the tranny,
didn't you?
Aren't we owed one now?
'Cause technically we paid her.
- She had a dick, man!
- Do you guys even like me,
or is this
some sort of cruel joke
that you're all in on?
Because I'm not a freak!
I'm a good person.
I always thought
that Matt Damon
was a Streisand,
but I think that he's
rocking the shit in this one.
( shouts )
Shut up, Dave!
Hold up!
Let's just chill
on the aggression
for a minute.
- Beth: Look at him.
- ( woman laughs )
He is such a bad-ass.
- He looks just like
Luke Wilson.
- Mm-hmm.
- So you're saying
she was definitely a man?
- Yes.
How do you know
that she was a man?
Because her hands were
as big as Andre the Giant's
and she had an Adam's apple
as big as her balls.
So you have no proof?
You know what?
Just leave me alone.
Just stay away from me
or I'm going to tell Paula
that you're all stealing
the recordable CDs.
- Whoa! Come on!
- Whoa whoa whoa!
Come on, man.
We did this
'cause we're you're friends,
and we didn't think
you had the balls
to do it yourself.
- Oh really?
- Dave: Yeah.
Okay, watch this.
Yo, Andy!
It's just CDs, man!
That's a third strike
for me, dawg!
- ( tires screech )
- ( man yells )
( sighs deeply )
( bells jingle )
Hi.
- Andy, hi.
- Right. Yep.
You remember my name.
- I did. How you doing?
- I'm great.
I like your store.
That's good.
If you have time,
look around, it's--
Okay.
How's business been?
You know,
it's coming along.
- It takes a while.
- Do you want to go out
sometime?
Yes. Yes,
I would like that.
- Okay.
- That'd be great.
I think
I'm maybe free
this weekend if you, um--
if that's okay.
Or you could call
me tomorrow
- and we can just
firm it up.
- Okay.
- Both: Great.
- Okay, so I'll call you
and yeah, that'll be good.
That'll be good.
- How you doing?
- Congratulations.
Okay, so I'll-- yeah.
- Can I help you?
- Uh, yeah,
these are wonderful.
- I'll take these.
- Thanks, they are.
They're great
and the goldfish
just crack me up.
- Funny.
- ( Trish laughs ) Yeah.
Yeah, they are.
They're cute.
I actually don't sell
anything here.
I just sell them
on eBay.
Oh, I don't get it.
- I know.
- Okay.
- Can you help me?
- No, you're on your own here.
Good luck to you
and to you.
- I'll give you a call.
- Great.
- Great. Nice to see you.
- Thanks for coming in.
- Bye.
- ( bell jingles )
So, I guess I'll
give you some money
and you can give me
these shoes.
You know, I know
it seems so strange.
Yeah, so I'd just
rather buy them from you,
straight up.
Yeah, I know.
I wish it could be
that easy, but--
I wish too, but you're
making it extremely
difficult for me.
I'm just trying to get
these shoes back to my house
so I can wear them.
- David: I got a corpse
in my way.
- Cal: Just kill it.
That's so not fair that
you have blades in your--
- Ha!
- I'm telling you, man.
I feel great.
I'm so-- it's like
a weight has been lifted.
Celibacy is
the way to go, man.
Andy had it right.
Look at him.
He looks younger
than all of us,
but he's 10 years older.
Why? It's because he's
never had a relationship.
No she-devil sucked
his life force out yet.
( phone beeping )
( phone ringing )
- Hello?
- Hey hey, hi, hello.
- Um, is this Trish?
- Who's calling, please?
- This is Andy.
- Oh, hi, Andy!
- Hi, how are you doing?
- I'm good, how are you doing?
I'm doing great,
I'm doing great.
- So you're gay now?
- No, I'm not gay,
I'm just celibate.
I think--
I mean that sounds g--
I just want you
to know that this is
the first conversation
of three conversations
that leads to you being gay.
There's this,
and then in a year
it's like, "Oh, you know,
I kinda want to get
back out there,
but I think I like guys."
And then there's the big,
"Oh, I'm a gay guy now."
- You're gay
for saying that.
- I'm gay for saying that?
- You know how
I know you're gay?
- How do you know I'm gay?
'Cause you macraméd yourself
a pair of jean shorts.
Know how I know you're gay?
You just told me you're not
sleeping with women anymore.
- You know how
I know you're gay?
- How, 'cause you're gay
and you can tell
who other gay people are?
- You know how
I know you're gay?
- How?
You like Coldplay.
- Oh, you're dead.
You're dead. Oh!
- Oh! Come on.
Leave my torso alone
at least.
I also wanted
to call and--
and see what night
you might want to go out.
I'm actually free tonight.
Well, oh-- okay.
Well, I was thinking
maybe this weekend,
but that's good.
- Okay.
- Oh, great. What time do
you want to pick me up?
Uh...
let's see.
That's actually
kind of a problem,
because I ride a bike.
That's cool,
are you kidding me?
I love getting on
the back of a motorcycle.
My boyfriend in college
- drove a motorcycle so...
- Yeah. Yeah.
- ...I'm cool.
- Yeah, I bet
that was cool.
- I ride a bike-- bikes--
bike-cycle-- bicycle.
- Oh.
You know how I know
that you're gay?
- How?
- You like the movie
"Maid in Manhattan."
- You know how
I know you're gay?
- How?
I saw you make
spinach dip in a loaf
of sourdough bread once.
- You know I know
that you're gay?
- How?
You have a rainbow
bumper sticker on your car
- that says "I love it
when balls are in my face."
- That's gay?
- God damn it!
- I'm ripping your
head off right now.
It's off,
and now I'm throwing
it at your body.
- ( game character grunts )
- Fuck you!
You guys...
she's picking me
up in an hour.
Oh, drag, dude.
Wait, she's--
picking you up from here?
- Yeah.
- That's fucked up, man.
- Why?
- Why?! Seriously!
I mean, look at
this place, man.
You-- you gotta see this
through the eyes of a woman.
What is she gonna think
when she comes in here?
- "Look, he's got
a billion toys."
- So what?
And more video games
than a teenaged Asian kid.
Well, s-- all right.
Is that the Six Million
Dollar Man's boss?
- It's Oscar Goldman.
- Why do you have that?
That's worth a lot of money.
- That's much more valuable
than Steve Austin.
- That may be the case,
but none of this shit
is sexy, okay?
I'm not trying
to be sexy, man!
I mean-- Asia?
You framed an Asia poster?
How hard did the people
at the frame store laugh
when you brought this in?
- They did not laugh at me!
- Know why you're gay?
'Cause you like Asia.
Cool it with the gay!
She's on her way
over here, okay?
First you relax, okay?
Just stop calming me down
and tell me what I should do.
We take everything
that's embarrassing,
and we move it out of here
so it doesn't look like
you live in Neverland Ranch.
- Hi.
- Hi, how are you?
- Good.
- So, you want to head out?
Did you just
move in or something?
Oh, no. No, actually,
I'm getting new carpet in--
I'm having carpet
put in tomorrow.
- Oh.
- So...
- Oh, well.
- Yep, okay.
- It looks good
with the floors. All right.
- Yeah.
I should tear up
the hardwood and see if
there's carpet underneath.
- ( laughing )
- That's never the case.
- This is gonna be fun.
- ( women singing
in Japanese )
- Yes, this is.
- I drive by this place
every day, I've never been in.
I'm glad you came.
I never really go out
with nice guys like you.
I think I've avoided
nice guys like you
my whole life
at my own peril.
( laughs )
My last boyfriend
drank a lot.
- Mm-hmm.
- And so--
This is just punch.
- It's okay,
a little bit's fine.
- Buddha punch.
I need some Buddha.
- ( laughing )
- Man: Excuse me, Miss!
Could you gather your team
and sing "Happy Birthday"
for my daughter please?
( singing "If You're
Happy and You Know It"
in Japanese )
Yay!
- That was so good. What?
- That was great,
happy birthday.
- It's your birthday, too?
- No.
- Hey, it's his birthday too!
- No no no.
Could you sing for him
and bring him a cake?
Man:
Happy birthday!
( singing "If You're
Happy and You Know It"
in Japanese )
( silent )
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- Happy birthday!
- Thanks a lot.
- Happy birthday, Andy.
Wow.
You--
You really like
kissing, don't you?
- Yes!
- ( laughing )
- I really do-- what?
- Take off your-- take off
your pants, okay?
Oh, okay.
Okay?
- Wow, this is
really gonna happen.
- Oh, yeah.
Thank God.
Okay. I'm taking
off my pants.
Yeah. Do you
need some help?
I think almost got 'em.
It's hooked on my ankle.
( grunts )
Wow, that's--
Hey, wait, do you
have protection?
I don't like guns.
( laughing )
- That's-- funny.
- Thanks.
I have condoms
right here, okay?
- Okay.
- There's, you know--
check the expiration
date because they were
from when I was married.
We didn't have sex
that often, that's why
there are so many, okay?
Okay.
- So--
- ( dish rattling )
Oh, got 'em.
( whispers )
How does this go?
Okay.
"Roll over the tip
and down onto the base."
Over the balls?
It doesn't say.
- ( snaps )
- Ow.
Do you mind if
I use your-- Magnum?
( giggles )
Yeah.
Ho-ho-- wow.
You gotta be kidding.
I am Aquaman.
What is that?
( gags )
( coughs )
- ( pops )
- Ah!
Mom? Whoa!
What's going on here?
Who the hell are you?
- It's Andy!
- Hi, I'm Andy.
- God! What are you doing?!
- Marla, get the fuck
out of my room!
- Andy: You know what--
- I cannot believe
- you're allowed to have sex but
I'm not! That is so unfair!
- I'm gonna head out.
- Trish: You should go.
- Oh, Jesus, how many times
did you just do it?!
- Oh my God.
I'm so sorry.
- ( door slams )
- Shit.
God.
Dude...
teach me.
( sighs deeply )
Oh!
Ah, sh--
( trickling )
Oof! My goodness, Andy,
you are a terrific salesman.
- Oh, thank you.
- Gosh, you really
got it down.
- Thanks.
- Yeah, your
numbers are good.
- Thanks.
- I'm gonna put you out
on the floor full-time.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Wow, okay.
- Good, we're gonna get you
a blue shirt and the tie.
- Great, thanks.
- You know, Andy, I've been
thinking about your problem.
I think I might have
a solution for you.
- Hmm.
- You ever heard
of the term...
"fuck buddy"?
S-- wha--?
It's a special friend
who you fuck.
No, I haven't
heard that term.
When I was
a little girl,
I developed early.
By the time I was 14, I had
this body you're looking at.
- Can you imagine that?
- I don't want to, no.
Well, needless to say,
a lot of male attention.
I bet, yes.
Especially from our
Guatemalan gardener, Javier.
- Okay.
- You know, Javier...
before he made
passionate yet gentle
love to me for
the first time...
( sighs deeply )
he serenaded me
with a beautiful old
Guatemalan love song.
Really? That's--
that's-- sounds nice.
( singing in Spanish )
Okay.
Ooh! My goodness.
I think we better
get back to work.
Yeah-- yeah.
I better go back to work.
- Yeah.
- So, okay.
- All right. You mull it over
and I'll talk to you soon.
- All right, I will.
- Okay.
- Woman over P.A.:
Please come to the in-dash
- car stereos to assist...
- ( grunts )
- Hey.
- What's up, dawg?
What happened?
How was the date
with Trish?
- It was a disaster.
- Really?
Yes, I've never been more
embarrassed in my life.
I couldn't get
the condoms to work,
one of them
exploded on my balls
and then her kid
walked in the room.
- Wait, hold up. She was hiding
the kid from you, dawg?
- You know what?
It doesn't matter, because
it was going downhill
straight from there.
Listen, you don't want
no baby-daddy drama.
Trust me on
this one, a'ight?
For all you know,
he in prison right now.
Let's say
y'all living together,
next thing you know,
you the one going on the
1st and the 15th to pick
up the government check.
What if he got boys
that's on the outside
and they stalking you?
You see what I'm saying?
You got to think, partner--
What the fuck are
you talking about?
Here's what you do.
You tell her you're a virgin.
You test her
with this shit, okay?
Tell me, this is how
it's gonna go. Tell me.
- I'm a virgin.
- Sweet!
I like that
because you don't
have Chlamydia.
And I know that.
And that shit is everywhere.
What if she laughs
at me, though?
Then you punch her
in the fucking head
if she laughs.
I'm not gonna
punch her in the head,
she's really sweet.
No, I mean, you punch her
in the head emotionally.
She's different,
she's someone I felt like
I had a connection with.
All you trying
to do right now is
bust off this first nut.
- You got a whole lot
of semen back up in you.
- I am going to tell her.
- You should
totally tell her.
- I'm going to.
'Cause I watched this
movie called "Liar, Liar,"
and the message
was "Don't lie."
- And that was a smart movie.
- Yeah, that's the right thing.
Really?
All your girlfriends
wanted to have sex
with virgins too?
That's funny,
I didn't even know you--
girls talked like that.
I think
my first time might be
your best time, too.
Well, I knew it.
You know what?
I knew that
you'd react that way
and I knew that you would
want to lead me
through my first
sexual encounter
with all the compassion
and care
that someone would give
to their soulmate.
Oh my God,
I am in trouble.
( crickets chirping )
Hey, Andy!
- You watching
"Survivor" tonight?
- Oh, no.
- Actually, I'm going out
to dinner with somebody.
- Oh.
- Hi.
- Oh, and this is her.
- Um, Trish, this is
Joe and Sara.
- Hi.
- Hi, Trish.
- Hey.
- Tape it for me, okay?
- Will do.
- Thanks, all right.
- So long.
- See you later.
Have a good night.
- Sara: Bye-bye.
Yeah, my man's gonna
get it on tonight!
Yes, sir!
Mm-hmm, and you better
get on me, too. Mm-hmm.
What is wrong
with this woman?
Mercy mercy mercy.
( jazz music playing )
Thanks.
- I'm so sorry that happened
the other night.
- No, I'm sorry.
- Oh my God.
- I'm sorry.
That was me.
No. What?
( laughs )
Let me--
I have something
I wanna tell you.
Kinda hard
to talk about.
But there-- you know,
there's certain--
certain things
about who I am
that, um--
I'm sorry, I have to--
I just have to get this
off my chest.
I am so sorry
I didn't tell you
I had kids.
Yeah, what was
that about?
Gosh, you know,
that really surprised me.
( both laughing )
- Sorry.
- No. You should have
told me, probably...
- I know!
- ...but what do I care
if you have a kid?
Well, I have two kids.
Uh, wow! Okay.
- How old are they?
- Uh, six...
16.
21.
- 42.
- ( laughs )
56-- How many kids
do you have?
- I have three.
- Okay, three.
- Yeah. Oh, and one
of them has a kid.
- Oh.
- A one-year-old.
- That's cool
That's great.
I'm really glad
we're doing this.
Me too.
Um...
Listen, Andy,
I don't want to send you
running for the hills
or anything,
but I really feel
like if we decide
to do this again
then, um...
maybe we should hold off
on the physical part
for a while.
That is a fantastic idea.
Why didn't I think
of that?
- Really?
- Totally.
- No sex?
- No!
Why do that?!
Because-- here's the thing--
from personal experience
I found
that sex can really
complicate things,
and what we should be
doing right now is just
getting to know each other.
Yeah!
( laughs )
I never thought
you'd go for it.
I'm going for it.
That just is
a great great notion.
- ( laughs )
- Are you serious?
Look at my face.
Look at how serious I am.
Can you see my nostrils?
- ( laughs ) Yes.
- That's serious.
Well, that's more angry--
( laughs )
Yeah. You know what?
Most guys would be
saying "Yeah,"
right now,
but, like,
by the third date
it'd be,
"Hey, baby, I really need
to physically express
how I feel,"
all that stuff.
( laughing )
Well, hey, baby,
you know, three dates?
Make it 10.
10 dates.
How about 15?
- 15?!
- ( laughing )
Screw your 15!
20 dates!
- Okay, 20 dates.
- 20 dates.
- Okay.
- This is genius.
It's gonna hurt.
( laughing )
Not as much
as you think.
- ( moaning )
- We can really get to know
each other this way.
Yeah.
This is one, right?
Uh-huh--
no, next one.
( door opens )
Ahem.
Is it safe to come in,
or are you guys doing it?
- Honey, it's safe.
- Ahem.
Great.
- Well, good timing.
( chuckles )
- Yeah.
- You remember Marla.
- Hi, we met.
And this is my little
bunny rabbit Julia.
- Hey.
- This is Andy.
Julia, how're you doing?
You know what?
Do you by any chance
like magic?
- Yeah.
- I thought
that you might...
- ( Trish chuckling )
- because I noticed
on the way in
that you had
something shiny
behind your ear.
Marla, did you see that?
Something behind her ear?
I think you do.
Can I check?
Do you mind if I check
behind your ear?
( pops lips, yells )
Big money!
- Whoa!
- ( Trish laughing )
- That's amazing!
- Wow, it is amazing!
There's something else, too,
behind your ear, I think.
No, actually it's not
behind your ear.
It is your ear.
( yells )
Crrrip! It is your ear.
- ( Trish laughing )
- There is your ear!
I ripped it off.
- Gross!
- Yeah, that's sick.
( laughing )
All right, wait,
okay, but that means
that you walk around
with a rubber ear in your
pocket all day?
Um, yeah, like,
half the time.
You know, I can come
to your high school
and do it for
your friends if you want.
You know what?
I should head out.
- Oh really?
- Yeah.
Oh, well, I have
to give you a ride home.
- Right, yes, you do.
- Right.
- Yeah, 'cause you
don't have a car, right?
- Right, I don't have a car.
That's good,
'cause he doesn't have
a car and he does magic.
Awesome. Wow.
And sarcasm is like
a second language to me,
so I'm right there
with you.
( both giggling )
- ( jazz music playing )
- ( phone rings )
Yello!
- Hey hey hey, Cal.
- Hey!
I just got back
from the date.
Did you tell her
you're a virgin?
Uh, no.
I haven't gotten
to that yet.
Really?
Are you having sex
right now?
No! She was incredible.
She was amazing.
She didn't pressure me.
Hey, oh, and-- and--
and she has three kids!
And one of her kids
has a kid.
You all right?
Did you just say that
she has three kids,
one of whom has a kid?
- Yeah!
- So she's a grandma?
- No.
- I'm not a doctor
or anything like that,
but she's
a fucking grandma.
( laughing )
Yeah, well, whatever,
you know.
- She's the hottest
grandma I ever saw.
- Yeah, she is.
- She's a hot grandma.
- That's a good-looking
grandma.
My grandma looks
like Jack Palance.
- Well, she's
no Jack Palance.
- No, if Jack Palance looked
like that lady,
I would want to fuck
Jack Palance right now.
( laughs )
Yeah, me too.
She's a hot grandma.
Hey, yeah.
No, do a grandma, man.
You should fuck her on her
plastic-covered couch.
Fuck her while she watches
"Murder She Wrote."
She would probably
- find that very erotic.
- Yeah, well, whatever,
you know.
Fuck her and then
have her send you a check
for $12 on your birthday.
I'm the dude
with the hot granny!
- Do her.
- ( laughs )
Andy:
What did you want
to talk to me about?
Well, Andy, the numbers
just came in,
and you are by far
our best salesman.
- Cool.
- So I am promoting you
to floor manager.
This is the bullshit
of all bullshits,
you scumbag ass kisser!
Thank you.
That's great.
I understand
you have a girlfriend.
Yeah, I'm kinda
seeing somebody.
- I'm very happy for you.
- Thanks. She's great.
- Are you still a virgin?
- Oh, you know...
- I don't really talk
about my personal life--
- You're a virgin.
- Yes, I am.
- Yeah.
My door is always open...
- so to speak.
- Great.
Great.
Thank you.
I'm very discreet...
but I'll haunt
your dreams.
- Okay.
( inhales deeply )
( quietly )
Wow.
So who's gonna take
my job?
Cal will be
taking over your job,
and he's interviewing
people right now
for his old job.
So, have you ever worked
with electronics before?
- No.
But I have electronics
in my home.
Perfect!
That's the job, pretty much.
You're very well qualified.
- More than
these other losers.
- ( both giggle )
- I could do that--
- Wait wait wait wait,
last thing, last thing.
I'm also gonna need
that extended warranty on it
for the price of...
on the house, hmm?
That I can't do.
Hey, don't be a Negro,
be my nigga, all right?
Help me out.
Wait, hold on, hold on.
I ain't nobody's nigga.
Well, I mean,
you're somebody's nigga,
wearing this nigga tie.
- Now you're being
condescending, see?
- Mm-hmm.
You've been warned, a'ight?
Let's move forward amicably.
Okay, check this out, though.
First of all, you're throwing
too many big words at me, okay?
Now, because I don't
understand them, I'm gonna
take 'em as disrespect.
- Mmm.
- Watch your mouth
and help me with the sale.
Okay, see--
see, now you found
yourself a nigga.
- You were lookin' for
a nigga? Nigga here now.
- Okay.
Today's forecast--
dark and cloudy,
and chance of drive-by.
Jay, what's going on?
( sobbing )
Jill broke up with me.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
What happened?
I came home
a little tipsy,
and I had one
of my condoms on still.
I woke up
the next morning
and jumped
in the shower with her.
I don't know
what I was thinking!
Why did you cheat on her?
Because I'm insecure!
You can't tell?
I know,
I know, I know, man.
It's gonna be okay.
- I'm cold.
- It's gonna be
all right, man.
I'm-- seriously, man,
I'm sorry.
I apologize to you.
I know. If you want to have
a meaningful relationship,
you gotta leave
the sex out of it,
man, you're right.
- It's all right.
You're good. Okay.
- I'm sorry.
- Come here.
I love you, man.
- Oh, man, I love you too.
( crying )
- You're a good guy.
- ( exhales )
Do you know how I know
you guys are gay, hmm?
You're holding each other
ever so gently.
- ( Andy sighs )
- Cabrón.
- Whoo! Whoo-hoo!
- ( chuckles )
- Abbondanza!
- Trish: Bravo!
- Yay!
- At least
he can cook, Mom.
- ( growls )
- Ugh!
♪ Look at what's
happened to me... ♪
It's, uh, Spiderman.
- ♪ I can't
believe it myself... ♪
- ( Julia roars )
- Whee!
- ( yelling )
♪ Suddenly I'm
up on top of the world ♪
♪ It should have been
somebody else... ♪
Pull out slowly
and go straight ahead.
- ( both scream )
- ♪ Believe it or not ♪
♪ I'm walking on air ♪
♪ I never thought
I could feel so free ♪
♪ Flying away ♪
♪ On a wing and a prayer ♪
♪ Who could it be? ♪
( laughs )
♪ Believe it or not,
it's just me. ♪
( vocalizes music )
( screams, grunts )
I'm all right!
Nobody's there.
Trish:
I want to know
everything about you.
- I wanna tell you.
- You do?
- Yeah.
- Like what do you
want to do?
- What are your dreams?
- Uh...
You don't want
to work at Smart Tech
for the rest of your life.
- I-- I've been working there
for a long time...
- Yeah.
...and I've been thinking
lately that maybe I should
open my own store.
- ( gasps )
Really?
- Yeah.
- What kind of store?
- Well, like a stereo store.
Oh my God, that is--
so why don't you do that?!
I don't have
enough money
to do that.
What about those collectibles?
I bet if you sold those,
you could make
a lot of money.
I just sold
a guy's G.I. Joe
for 1,000 bucks!
- Really?
- Do you have
any of those?
- Yeah.
- You do?
- I have 47 of 'em.
- ( laughs ) No, you don't!
- Yeah, in the original boxes.
- You don't!
I could help you
sell them on eBay,
and I-- I mean,
I would not take
a commission, I swear to God!
You could do it.
You could totally
pull it off.
- Yeah, let's do it.
- Let's do it.
Aquaman, get your
gloves on...
send you off to...
a farm
with lots of land,
so you and other Aquamen
can run around,
play in the Aqua-fields.
Godspeed,
Colonel Steve Austin.
You don't wanna go, do you?
Okay, you can stay.
Steve Austin can stay.
Yeah, right.
( Marla screaming )
I have done everything
but sex!
I'm a woman, okay?
Deal with it!
I'm gonna start
taking you back to church!
- We are gonna start
going to church!
- ( door opens )
- Hello? Hello?
- Marla: You know what?!
What the hell are you
talking about? Oh my God,
I cannot believe this.
- Thank God you're here.
Oh Jesus Christ.
- Hi.
- Marla locked herself
in the bathroom.
- What happened?
She wants to go
to the family health clinic.
She wants birth control,
- but she's too young!
- ( screaming ) I want
to have sex
with my boyfriend,
but I can't, Mom!
So you want me
to take her?
- No, I don't
want you to take her!
- Okay, all right.
I want her
to keep it in her pants
until she gets to college!
Whoa whoa whoa!
Keep it in my pants?!
Okay, you didn't
keep it in your pants, Mom!
- Hey, Marla.
- I know!
I don't want you to make
the same mistakes as me!
Oh, mistakes?
Okay, so I was
a mistake then?!
No, you're not
a mistake!
Your sister
was the mistake.
( screeches )
Oh my God!
Her older sister--
I mean, she wasn't planned.
You know what I mean?
Because I was such a--
Oh God, you wanna
run away, don't you?
- Nope.
- You and your boyfriend...
have sex all the time!
Oh my God!
Are you kidding?!
- We never have sex.
Do we ever have sex?
- No, we don't.
What?!
Yes, you do!
You're such a liar!
Why are you lying
to me? Why?
( slams door,
babbling )
I didn't hear anything
after "liar."
- What did she
say after "liar"?
- She sounds like a teakettle.
Fuck you!
- What sh--
- Maybe I should take her.
- No, I don't think so.
- A little information
never hurt anybody.
( whispering )
Cool.
Wow.
Where-- where do
you put the penis?
( clatters )
Now, you're all here
because you're interested
in obtaining birth
control. Any questions?
( clears throat )
Here's a cute story.
I came home the other day
and he is with his girlfriend
in my marital bed
doing things that are
illegal in Alabama.
Sex acts, right?
Things that my wife
won't do, okay?
- Did you have a question?
- How do I get my
wife to do that?
Does anybody else
have a question?
My daughter is--
for lack of
a better word-- dumb.
How do I stop her
menstrual cycle?
You want her to stop
having a menstrual cycle?
I want to stop it--
maybe just for a few years.
Yeah, I don't think
that's a good idea.
- Does anybody else
have a question?
- I have a question.
I think some
of the people here
might be sexually
inexperienced.
Is it true that
if you don't use it,
you lose it?
Is that a serious question?
No, it wasn't.
Now, there are
a lot of activities
you can engage in
without having sex that
are both fun and safe.
What sort
of activities?
I think...
everybody wants to know
about the activities.
Well, instead of
having intercourse,
you could have
outercourse.
"Outercourse"?
Ew, what's that?
Yeah, what is that?
Outercourse is
anything that isn't
vaginal intercourse.
I prefer vaginal
intercourse.
( chuckles )
He really does.
Now, there are ways
of having sex
without intercourse.
Let's see, there are
things like body rubbing
- or dry humping.
- You could dry hump.
- There's masturbation,
- Masturbation, play
with yourself.
- Mutual masturbation,
- Play with a friend.
Deep kissing.
There's erotic massage.
Oh, that sounds
like it would be nice.
- Oral sex play.
- Sounds like
my Friday night.
Shut up, Seth,
we went to temple.
Okay, are there
any virgins here
who are thinking
about having sex
for the first time?
- Oh.
- ( laughing )
Wait, so you're a virgin?
( laughs )
I'd tap that.
Oh, yeah, you'd
"tap that." Seth, what?
You think you're cool
with your little Jew-fro?
We don't say "tap that."
What-- what are you
talking about, Seth?
You know what?
I'm a virgin, too.
- ( men laughing )
- Hey, that's--
- We're virgins too.
- Yeah.
( laughing )
No, you know what?
It's a personal choice,
and-- and I don't
think it's weird at all.
You know what your
problem is? You're putting
the pussy on a pedestal.
That's the second
time I've heard that.
What is the pussy
on a pedestal thing?
Okay, I can't listen
to any more of this,
'cause it's making
me sick, so bye.
- You can get this information
on your website, right?
- Oh, yes.
- Thanks, nice
meeting everybody.
- Any other questions?
Do you have any
extra-large condoms?
Seth, you've got
a tiny penis.
So, I made that all
up to help you out.
No, you didn't.
But, um, thank you
for doing that.
How can you tell?
Well, you know,
I go to school
with like 400 guys
- who are all trying
to have sex.
- Wow.
- Yeah, so I can
tell who's done it.
- Of course.
- And you really haven't.
- No, I really haven't.
Please don't tell
your mom, okay?
- Yeah, I won't.
- Thanks.
But-- when are you
gonna tell her?
Believe me,
I'm working on it.
I am working on it.
( pop music playing )
Cal. David.
I think she
likes you, man.
Hmm, I know. Too bad
I retired my cock.
Y'all wanna see something
beautiful? Come here!
You want to see the most
beautiful thing in the
world? Check this out!
This is my baby
right here. That's my
baby's dick right there.
Looks like a poltergeist.
That is his foot.
Look at his dick.
That's not even four months.
Extrapolate that.
By the time he's 30,
what's going to happen?
Hey, yo, Andy!
Yo, come check
this out, dawg.
Oh, is this the movie about
babies that are geniuses?
- No, no. This is my child,
dude. Jill is pregnant.
- That's yours?
Yeah! That's why
she broke up with me
in the first place
'cause she just
thought I wouldn't
be a really good father
in light of the fact
that I be cheating on her all
the time, but she got over that.
Congratulations,
man, that is great!
We having a party
tonight, Andy, and I
really want you to be there.
We celebrating and I really,
It looks like
the doppler radar.
Can you believe that?
This child ain't even
four months old.
He ain't even
four months old yet,
look at what he's packing.
Everybody dick
looks big on 60" TV.
My sister's dick
looks big on TV, okay?
- ( crickets chirping )
- Trish: Oh my God, this guy
Eric Gilliland?
- Uh-huh.
- He has bought
like 15 of these.
- Really?
- Yeah, I think he likes action
figures even more than you.
- That is impossible.
- I think so.
Andy, the way these things
are flying off your shelf,
you know, I think you
could actually make like--
- maybe like $100,000.
- Really?
Yeah, you could
open your store.
- Wow.
- I mean--
- That's a lot of money.
- I know.
That's incredible.
I wouldn't have done it
without you.
Thanks.
And that's not
the only good news.
- What?
- You know what tonight is?
"Survivor" is on?
- No.
- No? Is it...
"The Apprentice"?
- No.
- Hmm, what?
It's our...
20th date.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
- Really?
- Uh-huh.
- Seriously? I think--
I think we're at 18.
- Nuh-uh.
There were a couple
dates there that don't
count as dates.
No. I'll give you a free
pass on those other ones.
- Thank you.
- Listen.
- What? Mm-hmm.
I really like you.
I-- I--
( sighs )
I think I'm
falling for you.
I don't know.
I kinda see this...
- going somewhere.
- I do too.
I just think we should
just go crazy on each other.
- Okay.
- Okay?
Oh, thank God.
Oh!
Okay, I should--
I gotta pick those up.
Wait, no,
pick them up later.
- No, I have to pick
those up right now.
- Wait, we'll get 'em later.
Listen, it's really
important because
once the integrity of
the box gets compromised--
this is original packaging
and that's why these
things are so valuable.
So you don't-- you
don't screw with that.
- You really don't
screw with that.
- All right.
Well, we can wrap 'em
again later, you know?
Yeah, but you
know what? This is very
important that we don't--
- we don't lose the value
or compromise the integrity--
- Andy, I'm...
throwing myself at you
- and all you can think
about is fucking toys!
- They're not fucking toys!
This is Iron Man, okay?
I got this when
I was in 2nd grade!
- Do you know how hard it is
for a kid to not open that?
- Uh-huh.
This is important,
these are my things
and you are trying
to make me sell them
and I don't want to.
- No.
- And you're making me.
- I-- I'm not making--
- You're encouraging me
to quit my job.
- I'm not! I'm not trying--
- You want me to open a store!
You want me to sell
everything. You know what?
I'm gonna tell you something.
I don't just change like that.
I can't just change for you.
I don't-- I'm not
trying to change you.
I like you!
- I'm trying to help
you grow up, Andy.
- Well, thanks a lot.
I mean, my God,
you ride a bicycle to
work in a stockroom--
You know what? I'm not
in the stockroom anymore,
- I'm a floor manager.
- Okay.
I ride a bike
because I like to.
Einstein rode a bike.
He had a wife,
who he fucked, by the way.
What do I have to do
for you to have sex with me?
Do you want me to
dress up like Thor?
I'll dress up like Thor.
I'll dress up like Iron Man.
What do they do? I'll do it!
Why-- everything's
always about sex.
Why don't you want to
have sex with me? Why not?
You tell me the truth.
Is it because I have a kid
who has a kid? Is that why?
No, it's cool!
I love the fact that
you're a grandmother.
- Oh God!
- You are! You're
a hot grandma!
Oh my God!
You are so mean!
- Get out!
- Okay, fine, good!
- Good, fine, you're gonna go.
- I didn't ask for any of this.
- You asked for
all of it, Andy!
- Okay, great.
Hey, if that's
the way you want it,
that's the way
homie's gonna play it.
Yeah, truth be told.
( horns blaring )
♪ Hot this year ♪
♪ Say what?
Uh uh uh... ♪
Ooh, baby, you better
enjoy yourself tonight,
'cause once
this baby's born,
- you ain't going out again
till that baby's in college.
- Me?
- Yeah.
- You the club rat. I'm
not the one that be going out.
I'm not a club rat.
Now you're gonna get up,
you're gonna march over there
and I want you to hit
on Bernadette... now!
Dude, I'm not gonna
hit on Bernadette.
Yes, you are, man!
'Cause your depression
is boring me for one thing
and it's actually making
me a little depressed.
Which is then in turn making me
more depressed that you're
actually affecting my mood.
Look, I'm not in
any kind of place
to talk to a woman,
all right?
I'm just--
I'm fragile.
I hired her for you.
I hired a 90-lb. girl
to work in the stock room
at Smart Tech
for you, okay?
I should've hired
a 300-lb. guy
who could lift
a 60" wide screen,
but instead
I hired a hot girl
who can't lift
an iPod to bring you
out of your funk.
- You hired her for me?
- Yes!
- So will you
go talk to her?
- Yeah, I'm meeting somebody.
No.
- Did you just flick me
in the nuts?
- No.
I flicked you in
the fleshy patch where
your nuts used to be.
Ow! Quit flickin'
my balls, man!
Okay, I'll stop
flickin' your balls.
But I'll start
punching your nuts!
Oh! Okay.
- Well played, sir.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- No problem, man.
Go get 'em.
Mooj, you done seen my son.
You know his foot gonna
be bigger than this.
That baby looks Pakistani.
Don't fucking look at me, okay?
I wouldn't mind,
you got good genes.
- How old are you? What, 138?
- When your son is born,
is he already on parole?
- ( sighs )
- ♪ Sexy how you
move that body ♪
♪ Got me like whoa
whoa whoa ♪
♪ Welcome to
the after party... ♪
I need some poon.
You guys were so right,
right from the beginning.
I need genital
to genital connection,
and that's all I need.
You know the thing about
relationships is that
they make one person go...
( babbles )
...and the other person go,
"What are you talking about?"
And then one person goes...
( babbles )
How much have
you had to drink, man?
Oh, how much have I had
to drink? Hey! How many
pots have you smoken?
- What are you talking about?
- How many times have you gone
to the bathroom in your life?
Let me ask you that! You
know what?! You don't have
an answer for that, do you?!
- ( stammers )
- Fuck you, man!
I'm sorry. No no no no.
You're such a good guy,
and I appreciate you.
What's up, baby? I didn't
know you came already!
Hey hey hey hey,
mothafucka.
Oh, man, you know what?
Tonight is the night.
And you know what?
You were totally right,
and I was wrong.
You were right all along.
You cannot have
a relationship
with somebody
until you have sex
and that's the long--
that's the long and
short of it, so thank you.
- No, whoa whoa whoa!
That's good. I got it.
- You're the best.
And now I have to
go hunt for some hos.
( laughs )
- Is he gonna be all right?
- No, I don't think he is.
♪ In my hot tub
swimming like that ♪
♪ Here comes my... ♪
Cal said you
were celibate.
- No, I just said that so he
wouldn't hit on me anymore.
- Oh.
♪ Ah-ha! Welcome
to my after party... ♪
Hey, you!
( giggles )
- H-h-h-hey!
- Hey.
How you doing?
Oh, I'm much better now
that I'm talking to you.
Hey, looky,
I can see
through your shirt.
Nice!
So, you think we should
take this party
to my apartment or what?
I am RSVPing yes.
Hope you have
a big trunk,
'cause I'm putting
my bike in it.
Oh ho-ho-ho!
Yeah! Let's go!
Mom! I left my phone
somewhere and-- oh, thank you.
What's the matter?
- Where's Andy?
- We had a big fight.
- He just--
- Oh, Mom.
- He just stormed
out of here.
- What happened?
Well, I just-- wait a minute,
I thought you hated him.
I don't hate him.
I mean, he does
do magic, but you know.
He's a big dork, and I
like seeing you happy.
I do.
That's sweet,
that's really sweet.
Mom.
Why don't you just
go talk to him?
Work it out. Nothing's
that important that you
can't just talk to him.
- ( pop music playing )
- Bow, chick-uh, bow,
chick-uh, bang-bow, bow!
Yeah! Ha ha!
- ( gasps )
- Yeah!
Oh, right! Okay!
Yeah. That was
a fun day.
- ( laughs )
- You--
you are so... kinky.
- ( gasping )
- Yeah, I'm so kinky.
- That's why I did
this because--
- ( laughing excitedly )
- because I thought it looked--
- You like to shave,
don't you?
- Yeah.
- Let's shave each other.
- I don't think
you have any hair.
- You know where to shave me.
- Yeah!
- 'Cause I want
to shave you.
I want to shave
your head.
I wanna give
you a buzz cut.
- Let's get in the bath.
- ♪ I'll taste just
like candy... ♪
- In the bath tub?
- Yes.
We're gonna get dirty
dirty dirty, sudsy.
- You know, it's just about
time I got really dirty.
- Yeah!
Hmm-hmm-hmm!
Wow, that came out fast.
Okay.
- ( smacks )
- Ow! Wow!
Holy shit!
Wow, that-- this is just
the right thing to happen.
Yeah yeah yeah! Wow!
Almost on my peter!
Come to mama.
I am gonna really take
care of you tonight.
- Okay.
- You're never
gonna forget Beth.
Yeah.
♪ I'll let you touch... ♪
Mmm!
( laughs )
I just want
to please you.
What do you like?
I don't--
I don't know.
What do you like?
Can I show you
what I like?
- Okay.
- ♪ You've got
let your body... ♪
Hey, hi, it's--
it's me and, uh,
I'm on my way to
your house. I want to do
whatever you want to do, okay?
50 dates, 100.
I hope not,
but-- whatever.
I'm gonna see
you soon, okay?
Bye.
Mm-hmm.
( moans )
Oh, it's so hot in here.
I want to introduce
you to my friend.
- ♪ Come through my door,
take off my clothes... ♪
- Your friend is so shiny.
This guy knows
exactly what I like.
( giggles )
Where's your
friend going?
- ( moaning )
- Whew.
This is how I'm gonna
warm up for you.
That's always good,
to warm up.
You don't want
to pull something.
- ( moaning )
- ♪ Tell me your secrets ♪
♪ And I--
I'll tell you mine ♪
♪ I'm feeling
quite sexy ♪
♪ And I want
you for tonight ♪
♪ If I move too fast,
just let me know... ♪
Wow.
This is graphic.
( laughing pleasurably )
♪ And I like
a man that goes ♪
♪ Baby, it's yours,
all yours ♪
- ♪ If you want it tonight... ♪
- I can't do it.
♪ I'll give you... ♪
( whispers )
God! What are
you doing here?!
We came here
'cause we were concerned
about you and Trish,
and now I could
not give a fuck.
How did you even
know where she lives?
I hit it,
like eight months back.
- What?!
- Never gave
her back the key.
Man, you-- you have no
idea where this is going.
That girl is a freak.
Beth:
Oh, it's happening!
It's happening!
Andy!
( screaming )
- Oh, you think?
- We've been talking,
and-- look.
If you love Trish,
you can't do this.
Look, you guys,
I don't know what
I'm doing anymore,
I don't even
know who I am.
All I know is
that woman
scares the shit
out of me
and I just want
to go home, okay?
- Let's go.
- Yeah, we should all
get out of here.
- Okay.
- Cal: We should all go.
- It wasn't that good for me.
- We should totally
get out of here.
- We should run
away from here.
- ( Beth squealing )
- Hey.
- ( Beth laughs )
Cal.
( horn blaring )
Go around!
Come on,
just go around me!
Can't you hear me?!
Hey, there.
Hi, Trish.
( exhales )
Oh, man, I'm really
sorry about tonight.
What's this?
Oh, those are David's.
I think
he has a problem.
These are David's?
- He's into that.
- David's...
"Boner Jams '03"?
Yeah, God, it was--
it's so sad.
He compiled all the best
boner scenes I guess.
- ( slams tapes )
- This isn't what
it looks like, okay?
What does
this look like?
A vagina.
- And what do you
with this vagina?
- To learn.
- It's for medicinal purposes.
- ( groans )
- Hey, I'm sorry. God--
- What's this?
This your--
your date drug?
- Your roofie?
- It's a Mentos.
- They're the Freshmaker.
- Yeah, right.
What are you some kind
of sex pervert, a deviant--
- No, I'm not a sexual deviant.
- Well, what is all this?
I haven't even tried
to have sex with you, so--
What are you trying
to do? What are you
buttering me up for?
- Aw, come on.
- You're not gonna try
and kill me, are you?
- Look, Trish--
- You didn't get
a new carpet...
I am not trying
to kill you.
I love you.
- I love you!
- Oh God! Oh!
Trish.
( car door slams )
Trish! No no!
No! No, Trish, stop!
( tires squealing )
♪ I never meant
to be so bad to you... ♪
- Come on, Trish!
- ♪ One thing I said
that I would never do... ♪
I need to talk to you!
- No!
- ♪ A look from you and I
would fall from grace... ♪
Damn it!
♪ And that would wipe the
smile right from my face ♪
♪ It was the heat
of the moment ♪
♪ Telling me what
your heart meant ♪
♪ The heat of the moment ♪
♪ Shone in your eyes ♪
♪ It was the heat
of the moment ♪
- ♪ The heat of the moment... ♪
- Andy: Whoa whoa whoa whoa!
- ( grunts )
- ( bicycle bell rings )
- Ah!
- Oh! Oh my God!
( tires squealing,
horns blaring )
- Wow.
- Oh, Andy.
Andy, oh my God!
Call 911!
- Oh my-- Andy!
- Wow wow.
- Oh my God.
- Yep, just--
I'm gonna need a minute.
- Oh my--
- I'm in a lot
of pain right now.
Oh my God,
are you okay?
( groans )
There were two sides
to that billboard,
and they both
hurt equally.
Oh, Andy! Andy.
( exhales )
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
No, I'm not okay.
I'm a virgin.
A what?
I always have been.
- Shoot.
- Andy, is that what
all this was about?
I'm sorry.
You're just
a virgin, that's all?
- Yeah.
- That's good.
That's a good thing.
I feel stupid.
It's okay, I thought you
were trying to kill me.
( laughs )
No.
Oh my God.
No, I'm not trying
to kill you.
( grunts )
That's why I never tried
to have sex with you.
I was scared.
Okay, I just--
'cause I didn't know
what I was doing,
I just didn't think
it would be good.
Of course it'll be good,
we love each other.
Really?
I love you.
Yeah.
( horn blaring )
Get the fuck out
of the road, virgin!
Shut up,
you fuckin' jerk!
No, that's okay.
That's all right! Sorry!
You know what?
For so long,
I've thought that there
was something wrong with me,
because it had
never happened.
But...
I realize now that
it was just because
I was waiting for you.
This is some wedding.
How did they pay
for all of it?
Dude sells his toys and makes
like a half a million dollars.
- That's crazy, right?
- That's fuckin' crazy.
We gonna get
some fuckin' toys.
We are all so
happy for you,
and I am delighted
to say these words:
Andy, you may
kiss the bride.
( guests applauding )
Yeah!
Woo!
And for God's sake,
consummate the thing!
No no no, stop it!
I have the key,
I have the key.
- Ah!
- ( machine whirring )
- ( whirring stops )
- Hey. I'm not
gonna be done
buffing the marble
for about a half an hour,
but you can come in
and sit down if you want.
Or wait in the
lobby, it's okay.
It's up to you.
( machine whirring )
( singing in Spanish)
Dude, get the
fuck out of here!
( whirring stops )
( moaning )
Ah.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
Yeah?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
Whoa.
You're officially
not a virgin.
Cool.
- ( sighs )
- Wow.
Ooh.
Wanna do it again?
- Yeah, sure.
- Good, okay.
That was--
that was good.
That was okay.
- Okay.
- Okay, you ready?
- Are you ready?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
( panting )
So how was
that for you?
♪ When the moon ♪
♪ Is in the
seventh house ♪
♪ And Jupiter
aligns with Mars ♪
♪ Then peace will
guide the planets ♪
♪ And love will steer
the stars ♪
♪ This is the dawning
of the age of Aquarius ♪
♪ The age of Aquarius ♪
♪ Aquarius ♪
♪ Harmony
and understanding ♪
♪ Sympathy
and trust abounding ♪
♪ No more falsehoods
or derisions ♪
♪ Golden living
dreams of visions ♪
♪ Mystic crystal
revelations ♪
♪ And the mind's
true liberation ♪
♪ Aquarius ♪
♪ Aquarius. ♪
♪ Let the sun shine ♪
♪ Let the sun shine in ♪
♪ The sun shine in ♪
- ♪ Let the sun shine ♪
- ( singing scat )
♪ Let the sun shine in ♪
♪ The sun shine in ♪
♪ Let the sun shine ♪
- ♪ Whoa let it shine ♪
- ♪ Let the sun shine in ♪
- ♪ Oh, let it shine ♪
- ♪ The sun shine in ♪
- ♪ Let the sun shine ♪
- ♪ Whoa, let it shine ♪
- ♪ Let the sun shine in ♪
- ♪ Let it shine, yeah ♪
♪ The sun shine in ♪
- ♪ Let the sun shine ♪
- ♪ Let it go, yeah yeah ♪
♪ Let the sun shine in ♪
♪ The sun shine in ♪
- ♪ Let the sun shine ♪
- ♪ Let it shine,
let it shine ♪
♪ Let the sun shine in ♪
♪ The sun shine in ♪
♪ Let the sun shine ♪
♪ Let the sun shine in ♪
♪ The sun shine in. ♪
( pop rock music playing )
♪ Your technique,
it leaves me weak ♪
♪ My heart knows
it's the beat I seek
and I found it ♪
- ♪ Just got lucky ♪
- ♪ Oh, yes, I found it ♪
♪ Just got lucky ♪
♪ I never worry that
your love is fake ♪
♪ I'm feeling easy,
and I'm feeling jake ♪
- ♪ 'Cause I found it ♪
- ♪ Just got lucky ♪
- ♪ Oh, boy, I found it ♪
♪ 'Cause I never
felt this way before ♪
♪ Like a dog always
begging for more ♪
♪ Whoa, yeah! ♪
♪ I've been fooled
by love so many times ♪
♪ I gave up on all
the silly rhymes ♪
♪ Kept my feelings
all inside my heart ♪
♪ A locked door, no key
was cut that was to fit ♪
♪ Now I'm such
a very lucky guy ♪
♪ Gang way, one side now,
come on hear me say ♪
♪ We found the answer
and it's plain to see ♪
- ♪ Come on hear me say ♪
- ♪ That I'm for you
and you're for me ♪
- ♪ 'Cause I found it ♪
- ♪ Just got lucky ♪
- ♪ Together we found it ♪
♪ I feel a quiver
every time we kiss ♪
♪ The sky's the limit
with a love like this ♪
- ♪ 'Cause I found it ♪
- ♪ Just got lucky ♪
- ♪ Together we found it ♪
♪ 'Cause I never
felt this way before. ♪