Fair is
foul, and foul is fair.
Hover through the
fog and filthy air.
When shall we
three meet again?
In thunder,
lightning, or in rain?
When the hurly-burly's done,
when the battle's lost and won.
That would be ere
the set of sun.
- Where the place?
- Upon the heath.
There to meet with Macbeth.
What bloody man is that?
Hail, brave friend!
Say to the king thy knowledge of
the broil as thou didst leave it.
Doubtful it stood.
The merciless Macdonwald led his
rebellion from the western isles.
And fortune on his
damned quarrel smiled.
- But brave Macbeth - -
Well he deserves that name!
Carved out a passage
till he faced the slave…
and ne'er shook hands,
nor bade farewell to him…
till he unseamed him
from the nave to the chops.
Valiant cousin.
Worthy gentleman!
Upon this chance
did the Norwegian king…
with furbished arms
and new supplies of men…
begin a fresh assault.
Dismayed not this, our
captains Macbeth and Banquo?
Yes, as sparrows eagles,
or the hare the lion.
So well thy words become thee
as thy wounds!
They smack of honor both.
Go get him surgeons.
- God save the king!
- What news, my worthy thane?
Norway himself,
with terrible numbers…
assisted by this most disloyal
traitor, the thane of Cawdor…
began a dismal conflict…
till Bellona's bridegroom,
bold Macbeth…
confronts the king,
rebellious arm 'gainst arm…
curbing his lavish spirit.
And to conclude,
the victory fell on us.
Great happiness!
No more that thane of Cawdor shall
deceive our bosom interest.
Go pronounce his
present death.
And with his former title…
greet Macbeth.
Mercy! Mercy!
So foul and fair
a day I have not seen.
♪
What are these…
so withered
and so wild in their attire…
that look not like the inhabitants
of the earth, and yet are on it?
♪ Speak if you can.
What are you?
All hail Macbeth.
Hail to thee, thane of Glamis.
Hail to thee, thane of Cawdor.
All hail Macbeth…
that shall be king hereafter.
In the name of truth, are ye fantastical,
or that indeed which outwardly ye show?
My noble partner you greet with
present grace and great prediction…
that he seems rapt withal.
To me you speak not.
If you can look into
the seeds of time…
and say which grain will grow
and which will not…
speak then to me…
who neither beg nor fear
your favors nor your hate.
- Hail!
Hail.
Lesser than
Macbeth, and greater.
Not so
happy, yet much happier.
Thou shalt beget kings…
though thou be none.
So all hail
Macbeth and Banquo!
Banquo and Macbeth, all hail!
Stay, you imperfect speakers.
Tell me more.
By Sinel's death
I know I am thane of Glamis.
But how of Cawdor?
Say from whence you owe
this strange intelligence…
or why upon this blasted heath
you stop our way…
with such prophetic greeting.
Whither are they vanished?
Into the air.
And what seemed
corporal melted…
as breath into the wind.
Were such things here
as we do speak about?
Or have we eaten of the insane root
that takes the reason prisoner?
Your children shall be kings.
- You shall be king.
- And thane of Cawdor too!
- Went it not so?
- To the selfsame tune and words.
The thane of Cawdor lives.
And to be king.
Stands not within the
prospect of belief.
No more than to be Cawdor.
The king has happily received,
Macbeth, the news of thy success.
As thick as hail
came post with post…
and everyone did bear thy praises
in his kingdom's great defense.
We are sent to give thee
from our royal master thanks…
only to herald thee into
his sight, not pay thee.
And for an earnest of a greater honor,
he bade me, from him, call thee…
thane of Cawdor.
What?
Can the devil speak true?
The thane of Cawdor lives.
Why do you dress me
in borrowed robes?
Who was the thane lives yet.
But under heavy judgment bears that
life which he deserves to lose.
Treasons capital, confessed and
proved, have overthrown him.
Glamis…
and thane of Cawdor?
The greatest is behind.
Thanks for your pains.
Do you not hope your children
shall be kings…
when those that gave the thane of
Cawdor to me promised no less to them?
That trusted home…
might yet enkindle
you unto the crown…
besides the thane of Cawdor.
Oftentimes, to win us to our harm, the
instruments of darkness tell us truths…
win us with honest trifles…
to betray us in
deepest consequence.
This supernatural
soliciting cannot be ill…
cannot be good.
If ill, why hath it given me
earnest of success…
commencing in a truth?
I am thane of Cawdor.
If good…
why do I yield to
that suggestion…
whose horrid image
doth unfix my hair…
and make my seated heart knock at
my ribs against the use of nature?
Present fears are less
than horrible imaginings.
My thought…
whose murder yet
is but fantastical…
shakes so my single
state of man…
that function is
smothered in surmise…
and nothing is
but what is not.
I thank you, gentlemen.
Look how our partner's rapt.
If chance will have me king…
why, chance may crown me,
without my stir.
Worthy Macbeth.
We stay upon your leisure.
Give me your favor.
My dull brain was wrought
with things forgotten.
Let us to the king.
Long live the king.
Nothing in his life became
him like the leaving it.
He died as one that had been
studied in his death…
to throw away the dearest thing he
owed as 'twere a careless trifle.
There's no art to find the
mind's construction in the face.
He was a gentleman on whom
I built an absolute trust.
"'Hail, king that shall be!'
This have I thought good
to deliver thee…
my dearest partner
of greatness…
that thou mightst not be ignorant
of what greatness is promised thee.
Lay it to thy heart,
and farewell."
Glamis thou art, and Cawdor…
and shalt be what
thou art promised.
Yet I do fear thy nature.
It is too full of the milk of human
kindness to catch the nearest way.
Thou wouldst be great.
Art not without ambition, but without
the illness should attend it.
What thou wouldst highly,
that wouldst thou holily.
Wouldst not play false,
and yet wouldst wrongly win.
Hie thee hither…
that I may pour my
spirits in thine ear.
Hail, Macbeth!
Hail, thane of Cawdor!
O worthiest cousin!
The sin of my ingratitude
even now was heavy on me.
Only I have left to say, more is thy
due than more than all can pay.
The service and the loyalty I
owe, in doing it, pays itself.
Your Highness' part
is to receive our duties.
Welcome hither.
I have begun to plant thee and will
labor to make thee full of growing.
Noble Banquo,
that has no less deserved…
let me enfold thee
and hold thee to my heart.
There if I grow,
the harvest is your own.
Sons, kinsmen, thanes…
and you whose places
are the nearest…
know we will
establish our estate…
upon our eldest, Malcolm…
whom we name hereafter…
the prince of Cumberland.
Hail, prince of Cumberland!
From hence to Inverness…
and bind us further to you.
I'll be myself the messenger…
and make joyful the hearing
of my wife with your approach.
So humbly take my leave.
My worthy Cawdor.
It is a peerless kinsman.
The prince of Cumberland!
That is a step
on which I must fall down…
or else o'erleap…
for in my way it lies.
Macbeth!
Stars, hide your fires.
Let not light see
my black and deep desires.
Great Glamis!
Worthy Cawdor!
Oh, greater than both,
by the all-hail hereafter.
Thy letter has transported me
beyond this ignorant present…
and I feel now
the future in the instant.
My dearest love…
Duncan comes here tonight.
And when goes hence?
Tomorrow, as he purposes.
Never shall sun
that morrow see.
Your face, my thane, is as a book
where men may read strange matters.
He that's coming
must be provided for.
And you shall put this night's
great business into my dispatch.
We will speak further.
Look like the innocent flower,
but be the serpent under it.
Leave all the rest to me.
♪
The raven himself is hoarse…
that croaks the fatal entrance
of Duncan under my battlements.
Come, you spirits
that tend on mortal thoughts.
Unsex me here…
and fill me from the crown to the
toe top full of direst cruelty.
Make thick my blood.
Stop up the access
and passage to remorse…
that no compunctious visitings
of nature shake my fell purpose.
This castle has
a pleasant seat.
The air nimbly and sweetly recommends
itself unto our gentle senses.
Come, thick night…
and pall thee
in the dunnest smoke of hell…
that my keen knife
see not the wound it makes…
nor heaven peep through the blanket
of the dark to cry, "Hold! Hold!"
Fair and noble hostess,
we are your guests tonight.
Your servant ever.
Give me your hand.
Conduct me to mine host.
We love him highly and shall
continue our graces towards him.
If it 'twere
done when 'tis done…
then 'twere well it
were done quickly.
If the assassination could
trammel up the consequence…
and catch with his
surcease, success.
That but this blow might be the
be-all and the end-all here.
- Health to this household!
- But here…
upon this bank
and shoal of time…
we'd jump the life to come.
Health to this household!
But in these cases…
we still have judgment here…
that we but teach
bloody instructions…
which, being taught,
return to plague the inventor.
♪
♪ Oh, your two eyes ♪
♪ Will slay me certainly ♪
♪ I made the beauty of them ♪
♪ Not to stay ♪
♪ So peace hath it
throughout my heart be ♪
♪ Unless your words
will heal me hastily ♪
He's here in double trust.
First, as I am his kinsman
and his subject…
strong both against the deed.
Then as his host…
who should against his
murderer shut the door…
not bear the knife myself.
Besides… this Duncan…
hath borne
his faculties so meek…
hath been so clear
in his great office…
that his virtues will
plead like angels…
trumpet-tongued…
against the deep damnation
of his taking off.
And pity…
like a naked, newborn babe,
striding the blast…
or heaven's cherubim horsed upon
the sightless couriers of the air…
shall blow the horrid
deed in every eye…
that tears shall
drown the wind.
I have no spur to prick
the sides of my intent…
but only vaulting ambition…
which o'erleaps itself
and falls on the other side.
Why have you left the chamber?
Hath he asked for me?
Know you not he has?
We will proceed no further
in this business.
He hath honored me of late…
and I have bought golden opinions
from all sorts of people…
which would be worn now
in their newest gloss…
not cast aside so soon.
Was the hope drunk
wherein you dressed yourself?
♪ Hath it slept since?
And wakes it now to
look so green and pale…
at what it did so freely?
♪
From this time such
I account thy love.
Art thou afeard to be the same in thine
own act and valor as thou art in desire?
Prithee, peace.
Wouldst live a coward
in thine own esteem…
letting "I dare not"
wait upon "I would"…
like the poor
cat in the adage?
I dare do all that
may become a man.
Who dares do more is none.
What beast wast then that made
you break this enterprise to me?
When you durst do it,
then you were a man.
And to be more than what you were,
you would be so much more the man.
Hail, thane of Cawdor.
If we should fail?
We fail.
But screw your courage to the
sticking place and we'll not fail.
♪
Duncan's two chamberlains…
will I, with wine and wassail,
so convince…
that memory, the warder of
the brain, shall be a fume.
I'll drug their possets.
When in swinish sleep their
drenched natures lie as in a death…
what cannot you and I perform
upon the unguarded Duncan?
♪
Bring forth men-children only…
for thy undaunted mettle should
compose nothing but males.
How goes the night, boy?
The moon is down.
I have not heard the clock.
And she goes down at 12:00.
- I take 'tis later, sir.
- Hold.
Take my sword.
There's husbandry in heaven.
Their candles are all out.
Take thee that too.
A heavy summons
lies like lead upon me…
and yet I would not sleep.
Merciful powers, restrain
in me the cursed thoughts…
that nature gives
way to in repose.
Who's there?
A friend.
What, sir? Not yet at rest?
The king's abed.
He hath been in
unusual pleasure…
and sent forth great largess
to your offices.
Being unprepared, our will
became the servant to defect.
All's well.
I dreamt last night
of the three weird sisters.
To you they have
showed some truth.
I think not of them.
Yet when we can entreat
an hour to serve…
we would spend it in some
words upon that business…
if you would grant the time.
At your kindest leisure.
It shall make honor for you.
So I lose none in
seeking to augment it.
I shall be counseled.
Good repose the while.
Thanks, sir.
The like to you.
Is this a dagger
which I see before me…
the handle toward my hand?
Come.
Let me clutch thee.
I have thee not…
and yet I see thee still.
Art thou not, fatal vision…
sensible to feeling
as to sight?
Or art thou but a
dagger of the mind…
a false creation proceeding
from a heat-oppressed brain?
I see thee yet…
in form as palpable as this…
which now I draw.
Thou marshall'st me
the way that I was going…
and such an instrument
I was to use.
Mine eyes are made the fools
of the other senses…
or else worth all the rest.
I see thee still.
And on thy blade and dudgeon…
gouts of blood…
which was not so before.
There's no such thing.
It is the bloody business which
informs thus to mine eyes.
Now, o'er the one-half world…
nature seems dead…
and withered murder…
alarmed by his
sentinel, the wolf…
whose howl's his watch.
Thus with his stealthy pace…
with Tarquin's
ravishing strides…
towards his design
moves like a ghost.
Thou sure and firm-set earth…
hear not my steps,
which way they walk…
for fear the very stones
prate of my whereabouts.
Hear it not, Duncan…
for it is a knell
that summons thee to heaven…
or to hell.
Macbeth?
Murde -
Hark, I am afraid they
have awaked and 'tis not done.
The attempt and not the deed
confounds us.
Peace.
It was the owl that shrieked…
the fatal bellman which gives
the sternest good night.
My husband?
I have done the deed.
Didst thou not hear a noise?
I heard the owl scream
and the crickets cry.
Did not you speak?
- When?
- Now.
- As I descended?
- Aye.
Hark!
- Who lies in the second chamber?
- Donalbain.
This is a sorry sight.
A foolish thought to
say a sorry sight.
Me thought I
heard a voice cry…
"Sleep no more.
Macbeth does murder sleep."
The innocent sleep…
sleep that knits up
the ravelled sleave of care.
The death of each day's life…
sore labor's bath,
balm of hurt minds.
Great Nature's second course,
chief nourisher in life's feast.
What do you mean?
Still it cried
to all the house…
"Glamis hath murdered sleep…
and therefore Cawdor
shall sleep no more.
Macbeth shall sleep no more."
Who was it that thus cried?
These deeds must not be
thought after these ways so.
It will make us mad.
Come.
Get some water and wash this
filthy witness from your hands.
Come.
Why did you bring these
daggers from the place?
They must lie there.
I'll go no more.
I'm afraid to think what I have
done. Look on it again I dare not.
Infirm of purpose!
Give me the daggers.
If he do bleed…
I'll gild the faces
of the grooms withal…
for it must seem their guilt.
Whence is that knocking?
How is it with me,
when every noise appalls me?
What hands are here?
They pluck out mine eyes.
Will great Neptune's ocean wash
this blood clean from my hand?
No.
This my hand will rather the
multitudinous seas incarnadine…
making the green one red.
My hands are of your color.
But I scorn to wear
a heart so white.
A little water clears
us of this deed.
How easy is it then.
Retire we to our chamber.
Get on your nightgown, lest occasion
call us and show us to be watchers.
Be not lost so poorly
in your thoughts.
To know my deed…
'twere best not know myself.
- Wake Duncan with thy knocking!
- Shh!
I would thou couldst.
Here's a knocking indeed!
If a man were porter of hell gate,
he'd have less turning the key.
Who's there, in the
name of Beelzebub?
Knock, knock!
Who's there, in the
other devil's name?
Knock, knock. Never at quiet.
Well, what are you?
One that goes the primrose way
to the everlasting bonfire?
Oh, I'll devil-porter
it no further.
This place is too
cold for hell.
Anon, anon!
Was it so late, friend, ere you
went to bed that you lie so late?
Faith, sir, we were carousing
till the second cock.
And drink, sir…
is a great provoker
of three things.
- What three things?
- Marry, sir.
Nose-painting,
sleep and urine.
Lechery, sir,
it provokes and it unprovokes.
It provokes the desire…
but takes away
the performance.
It makes you, it mars you.
It sets you on
and takes you off.
It persuades you.
It disheartens you.
It makes you stand
to and not stand to.
- I believe drink gave thee the lie last night.
- That it did, sir, in the very throat.
- Is thy master stirring?
- Good morrow.
- Good morrow!
- Good morrow, noble sir.
Is the king stirring,
worthy thane?
- Not yet.
- He did command me to call timely on him.
I have almost
slipped the hour.
I'll bring you to him.
This is the door.
I'll make so bold to call,
for 'tis my appointed service.
Goes the king hence today?
He does. He did appoint so.
The night has been unruly.
Where we lay,
our chimneys were blown down.
And, as they say,
lamenting is heard in the air.
Strange screams of death.
Some say the earth was
feverous and did shake.
- 'Twas a rough night.
- Oh, horror!
Horror! Horror!
- Confusion now has made his masterpiece.
- What's the matter?
Murder hath broke open
the Lord's anointed temple…
and stole thence
the life of the building!
The life? What is it you say?
Mean you His Majesty?
Do not bid me speak.
See…
and then speak yourselves.
Awake!
Ring the alarm bell!
Murder and treason!
Malcolm and Donalbain!
Banquo! Awake!
Shake off this downy sleep,
death's counterfeit…
and look on death itself!
Up! Up!
And see the great
doom's image!
Fleance! Banquo!
Rise up as from your graves…
and walk like spirits
to countenance this horror.
Ring the bell!
What's the business,
that a hideous trumpet calls…
to parley the
sleepers of the house?
Speak! Speak!
Gentle lady, 'tis not for you
to hear what I can speak.
O Banquo. Banquo.
Our royal master's murdered.
Woe, alas.
What, in our house?
Too cruel anywhere.
Macduff, I prithee contradict
thyself and say it is not so.
Had I but died before this chance,
I had lived a blessed time.
For from this instant there is
nothing serious in mortality.
All is but toys.
Renown and grace is dead.
What is amiss?
You are, and do not know it.
Your royal father's murdered.
Who?
By whom?
Those of his chambers,
it seemed, had done it.
Their hands and faces
were all badged with blood.
So were their daggers.
O, yet I do repent me of my
fury that I did kill them.
Wherefore did you do so?
Who can be wise, amazed,
temperate and furious…
loyal and neutral in a moment?
No man!
Here lay Duncan, his silver skin
laced with his golden blood.
There the murderers, steeped
in the colors of their trade.
Who could refrain,
that had a heart to love?
And, in that heart, courage
to make his love known?
What sight is this?
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
Let's briefly put
on manly readiness…
and meet in the hall together…
to question this most bloody piece
of work and know it further.
Fears and scruples shake us.
In the great hand
of God I stand…
and thence against the undivulged
pretense I fight… of treasonous malice.
- So do I.
- So all.
So all.
What will you do?
Let's not consort with them.
I'll to England.
To Ireland, I.
Our separated fortune
shall keep us both the safer.
Where we are, there's
daggers in men's smiles.
This murderous
shaft that's shot…
hath not yet lighted.
Therefore to horse.
And let us not be dainty
of leave-taking.
Shift away.
How goes the world, Macduff?
Why? See you not?
It's known who did
this more than bloody deed?
Those that Macbeth hath slain.
Alas, the day.
What good could they expect?
They were suborned.
Malcolm and Donalbain, the king's two
sons, have stolen away and fled…
which puts upon them
suspicion of the deed.
Then 'tis most like the sovereignty
will fall upon Macbeth.
He's already named…
and gone to Scone
to be invested.
- Will you to Scone?
- No, cousin, I'll home to Fife.
Well, I will thither.
Oh. May you see things
well done there.
Adieu.
Thou hast it now.
King, Cawdor, Glamis.
All as the weird
women promised.
And I fear thou play'dst
most foully for it.
Yet it was said it should
not stand in thy posterity…
but that myself should be the
root and father of many kings.
If there comes
truth from them…
may they not be my
oracles as well…
and set me up in hope?
Hail, Macbeth!
Hail, king of Scotland!
Here's our chief guest.
If he had been forgotten, it'd have
been as a gap in our great feast.
Tonight we hold a solemn supper,
sir, and I'll request your presence.
Let Your Highness
command upon me…
to the which my duties are with a
most indissoluble tie forever knit.
Ride you this afternoon?
Aye, my good lord.
Is it far you ride?
As far, my lord, as will fill up
the time twixt this and supper.
- Fail not our feast.
- My lord, I will not.
We hear our bloody cousins are
bestowed in England and in Ireland…
not confessing their
cruel parricide.
But of that tomorrow. Hie you to
horse. Adieu till you return at night.
- Goes Fleance with you?
- Aye, my good lord.
I wish your horses
swift and sure of foot.
Farewell.
- Attend those men our leisure?
- They do, my lord.
Bring them before us.
To be thus is nothing…
but to be safely thus.
Our fears in
Banquo stick deep.
And in his royalty of nature
he hath the wisdom…
that doth guide his
valor to act in safety.
There is none but he
whose being I do fear.
And under him my
genius is rebuked.
We'll keep ourself
till suppertime alone.
Till then, God be with you.
He chid the sisters…
when first they put
the name of king upon me…
and bade them speak to him.
Then, prophet-like
they hailed him…
father to a line of kings.
Upon my head,
they placed a fruitless crown…
and put a barren
scepter in my grip…
thence to be wrenched
with an unlineal hand…
no son of mine succeeding.
If it be so…
for Banquo's sons
have I defiled my mind.
For them the gracious Duncan
have I murdered.
To make them kings.
The seeds of Banquo, kings.
Stay within call.
- Was it not yesterday we spoke together?
- It was, so please Your Highness.
Well, then now…
have you considered
of my speeches?
Know that it was he in the times past
which held you so under fortune…
which you thought
had been our innocent self.
You made this known to us.
Do you find your patience so predominant
in your nature that you can let this go?
Are you so gospelled to pray
for this good man…
and for his issue…
whose heavy hand
has bowed you to the grave…
and beggared yours forever?
We are men, my liege.
Aye, in the catalog
ye go for men.
As hounds and greyhounds…
mongrels, spaniels, curs, shoughs,
water-rugs and demi-wolves are clept…
all by the name of dogs.
And so of men.
Now, if you have a
station in the file…
not in the worst
rank of manhood…
say it…
and I will put that business
in your bosoms…
whose execution
takes your enemy off…
grapples you to the
heart and love of us…
who wear our health
but sickly in his life…
which in his death
were perfect.
I am one, my liege…
whom the vile blows and buffets
of the world have so incensed…
that I - I am reckless
what I do to spite the world.
And I another.
Both of you know
Banquo was your enemy.
- Aye, my lord.
- Aye, my lord, but -
So is he mine.
And though I could with barefaced
power sweep him from my sight…
and bid my will avouch it…
yet I must not…
for certain friends
that are both his and mine…
whose loves I may not drop.
And thence it is…
that I to your assistance
do make love…
masking the business from the common
eye for sundry weighty reasons.
We shall, my lord, perform
what you command us.
- Though our lives may - - Your
spirits shine through you.
It must be done tonight…
and some way from the palace.
And with him, to leave no
rubs nor botches in the work…
Fleance, his son,
that keeps him company…
whose absence is no less material
to me than is his father's…
must embrace the fate
of that dark hour.
- Resolve yourselves apart.
- We are resolved, my lord.
Advise them where
to plant themselves.
How now, my lord?
Why do you keep alone…
of sorriest fancies
your companions making?
Things without all remedy
should be without regard.
What's done is done.
We have scotch'd the
snake, not killed it.
But let the frame
of things disjoint…
ere we will eat
our meal in fear…
and sleep in the affliction of these
terrible dreams that shake us nightly.
Better be with the dead…
than on the torture of the mind
to lie in restless ecstasy.
Duncan is in his grave.
After life's fitful fever,
he sleeps well.
Treason has done his worst.
Not steel, nor poison…
malice domestic, foreign levy…
nothing can touch him further.
Come on. Gentle, my lord.
Sleek o'er your rugged looks.
Be bright and jovial
among your guests tonight.
So shall I, love.
And so, I pray, be you.
Full of scorpions is my mind,
dear wife.
Thou know'st that Banquo
and his Fleance live.
But in them
nature's copy is not eterne.
There's comfort yet.
They are assailable.
Then be thou jocund.
Ere the bat hath flown
his cloistered flight.
Ere to black Hecate's summons…
the shard-borne beetle
with his drowsy hums…
hath rung night's
yawning peal.
There shall be done
a deed of dreadful note.
What's to be done?
Be innocent of the knowledge,
dearest chuck…
till thou applaud the deed.
Come, seeling night.
Scarf up the tender
eye of pitiful day.
And with thy bloody
and invisible hand…
cancel and tear to pieces…
that great bond
which keeps me pale.
Light thickens…
and the crow makes wing
to the rooky wood.
Good things of day begin
to droop and drowse -
while night's black agents
to their prey do rouse.
Who did bid thee join with us?
Macbeth.
He needs not our mistrust…
since he delivers our offices and what
we have to do to the direction just.
Well, stand with us.
The west yet glimmers
with some streaks of day.
And near approaches
the subject of our watch.
By the clock 'tis day…
and yet dark night
strangles the traveling lamp.
Is it night's predominance…
or the day's shame…
that darkness does the face of earth
entomb when living light should kiss it?
It will be rain tonight.
Let it come down!
Treachery!
Fly, good Fleance, fly!
Fly!
There's blood upon thy face.
'Tis Banquo's then.
- Is he dispatched?
- My Lord, his throat is cut.
That I did for him.
Thou art the best
of the cutthroats.
Yet he's good
that did the like for Fleance.
If thou didst that,
thou art the nonpareil.
Most royal sir,
Fleance is escaped.
Then comes my fit again.
I had else been perfect…
whole as the marble,
founded as the rock.
But now I am cabined,
cribbed, confined…
bound in to saucy
doubts and fears.
- But Banquo's safe?
- Aye, my good lord.
Safe in that ditch he bides, with
20 trenched gashes on his head.
There the grown serpent lies.
The worm that's fled…
hath nature that in time
will venom breed.
No teeth for the present.
Get thee gone.
Tomorrow we'll hear
ourselves again.
You know your own degrees.
Sit down. At first and last,
a hearty welcome.
Thanks to Your Majesty.
Our hostess keeps her state.
Ourself will mingle with society
and play the humble host.
My royal lord,
you do not give the cheer.
Sweet remembrancer.
I drink to the general joy
of the whole table.
And to our dear friend Banquo,
whom we miss.
Would he were here.
Banquo!
Now good digestion wait on
appetite, and health on both.
May it please Your
Highness, sit.
Please it Your Highness to grace
us with your royal company?
- The table's full.
- Here is a place reserved, sir.
- Where?
- Here, my good lord.
Wh-Which of you
have done this?
- What, my good lord?
- Thou canst not say I did it.
Never shake thy
gory locks at me.
Gentlemen, rise.
His Highness is not well.
Sit, worthy friends.
My lord is often thus
and hath been from his youth.
Pray, you keep seat.
The fit is momentary.
Upon a thought, he
will again be well.
Are you a man?
Aye, and a bold one that dare look on
that which might appall the devil.
O, proper stuff!
This is the very
painting of your fear.
This is the air-drawn dagger which
you said led you to Duncan.
Shame itself!
Why do you make such faces?
When all's done,
you look but on a stool.
Prithee, see there!
Behold, look!
How say you! Avaunt and quit my
sight! Let the earth hide thee!
Thy bones are marrowless,
thy blood is cold.
Thou hast no speculation in those
eyes which thou dost glare with.
What man dare, I dare.
Take any shape but that, and my
firm nerves shall never tremble.
Oh, hence, horrible shadow!
Unreal mockery, hence!
What?
Quite unmanned in folly.
If I stand here, I saw him.
Fie, for shame.
Blood hath been shed ere now,
in the olden time.
Aye, and since too, murders have been
performed too terrible for the ear.
Time has been
that when the brains were out…
the man would die,
and there an end.
But now they rise again…
with 20 mortal gashes
on their crowns…
and push us from our stools.
You've displaced the mirth,
broke the good meeting…
with most admired disorder.
Can such things be…
and overwhelm us like a summer's
cloud without our special wonder?
You make me strange…
even to the
disposition that I owe.
When now I think
you can behold such sights…
and keep the natural ruby
of your cheeks…
when mine is
blanched with fear.
What sights, my lord?
I pray you, speak not.
He grows worse and worse.
Question enrages him.
At once, good night.
Stand not upon the order of
your going, but go at once.
Good night, and better
health attend His Majesty.
Kind good night to all.
It will have blood. They
say blood will have blood.
Stones have been known to move
and trees to speak.
What is the night?
Almost at odds with morning…
which is which.
How say'st thou that Macduff denies
his person at our great bidding?
How know you this, my lord?
I hear it by the way.
There's not a one of them, but in
his house I keep a servant paid.
You lack the season
of all natures, sleep.
Come. We'll to sleep.
I must again
to the weird sisters.
More shall they speak.
For now I am bent to know,
by the worst means, the worst.
For mine own good,
all causes shall give way.
I'm in blood,
stepped in so far…
that should I wade no more returning
were as tedious as go o'er.
Strange things I have in head
that will to hand…
which must be acted
ere they may be scanned.
We are yet but young in deed.
By the pricking of my thumbs…
something wicked
this way comes.
How now, you secret,
black and midnight hags?
- What is it you do?
- A deed without a name.
Double,
double, toil and trouble.
Fire burn and cauldron bubble.
Toad that under cold stone,
days and nights has 31.
Swelted venom sleeping got, boil
thou first in the charmed pot.
Eye of newt and toe of frog,
wool of bat and tongue of dog.
Adder's fork and
blind-worm's sting…
lizard's leg and
howlet's wing.
Nose of Turk and
Tartar's lips…
severed in the moon's eclipse.
Fillet of a fenny snake,
in the cauldron boil and bake.
Liver of blaspheming Jew,
gall of goat and slips of yew.
I conjure you, by that which you
profess, howe'er you come to know it.
Answer me to what I ask you.
- Speak!
- Demand!
We'll answer.
Say if thou'dst hear it from our
mouths, or from our masters.
Call them. Let me see them.
Cool it with a baboon's blood…
then the charm
is firm and good.
Tell me, thou unknown power.
He knows thy thought.
Macbeth, Macbeth, Macbeth.
Beware Macduff.
Beware the thane of Fife.
Thou hast harped my fear
aright. But one word more!
He will not be commanded.
Be bloody, bold and resolute.
Laugh to scorn
the power of man.
For none of woman born
shall harm Macbeth.
None of woman born
None of woman born -
Then live Macduff.
What need I fear of thee?
But I'll make assurance double
sure and take a bond of fate.
Thou shalt not live!
Macbeth shall never
vanquished be.
Never, never.
Until great Birnam
Wood to high Dunsinane Hill…
shall come against him.
Oh!
That will never be!
Who can recruit the forest?
Bid the tree, unfix
his earth-bound root?
Sweet bodements, good!
Yet my heart throbs
to know one thing:
Shall Banquo's issue
ever reign in this kingdom?
Seek to know no more!
I will be satisfied! Deny me this
and an eternal curse fall on you!
Thou art too like
the spirit of Banquo.
Thy crown does
sear mine eyeballs.
What, will the line stretch
out to the crack of doom?
Now I see 'tis true.
For the blood-bolter'd Banquo
smiles upon me…
and points at them for his!
Where are they?
Gone!
Infected be the air
whereon they ride…
and damned all those
that trust them!
Macduff is fled.
Can you tell
where he bestows himself?
In the English court…
where lives the son of Duncan.
Thither Macduff is gone…
to pray the holy
king upon his aid…
to wake Northumberland
and warlike Seyward.
By the help of these, we may
again give to our tables meat…
sleep to our nights…
our feasts and banquets free
from bloody knives.
Some holy angel
fly to the court of England…
that a swift blessing may soon return
to this, our suffering country.
Gentle lady.
Gracious Duncan's dead.
The gracious Duncan
was pitied of Macbeth.
Marry, he was dead.
The right valiant Banquo
walked too late.
Whom, you may say, if it please you,
Fleance killed, for Fleance fled.
Man must not walk too late.
How monstrous it was for Malcolm and for
Donalbain to kill their gracious father.
Damned, indeed.
How it did grieve Macbeth.
I do think that had he
Duncan's sons under his key -
As, an't please
heaven he shall not.
They should find what it were
to kill a father.
So should Fleance.
Peace.
What news?
Macduff is fled to England.
- Fled to England?
- Aye, my good lord.
Time, thou anticipatest
my dread exploits.
The castle of
Macduff I will surprise.
Seize upon Fife.
Give to the edge of the sword
his wife, his babes…
and all unfortunate souls
that trace him in his line.
No boasting like a fool.
This deed I'll do
before the purpose cool.
You must have patience, madam.
He had none.
His flight is madness.
When our actions do not,
our fears do make us traitors.
You know not whether it was
his wisdom or his fear.
Wisdom? To leave his wife,
to leave his babes…
his mansion and his titles in a
place from whence himself does fly?
He loves us not.
He wants a natural touch.
For the poor wren,
the most diminutive of birds…
will fight, her young ones
in the nest, against the owl.
All is the fear,
and nothing is the love.
My dearest coz,
I pray you, school yourself.
But for your husband,
he is noble, wise, judicious…
and best knows the
fits of the seasons.
I take my leave of you.
I shall not be long
but I'll be here again.
Things at their
worst will cease…
or else climb upward
to what they were before.
My pretty cousin.
Blessing upon you.
Fathered he is,
and yet he's fatherless.
I take my leave at once.
How wilt thou do for a father?
Nay, how will you
do for a husband?
Why, I can buy me
20 at any market!
Was my father a traitor?
Aye, that he was.
What is a traitor?
Why, one that swears and lies.
Are they all
traitors that do so?
Everyone that does so is a
traitor and must be hanged.
- Who must hang them?
- Why, the honest men.
Then the liars and
swearers are fools…
for there are enough of them
to beat the honest men…
and hang them up.
Oh, God help
thee, poor monkey.
If he were dead,
you would weep for him.
Oh, God! No!
Where's your husband?
I hope, in no place so unsanctified,
where such as thou mayst find him.
He's a traitor.
Thou liest, thou
shag-haired villain!
What, you egg?
Young fry of treachery!
He has killed me, Mother.
Besides her walking
and other actual performances…
what, at any time,
have you heard her say?
That, sir, which I will
not report after her.
You may to a doctor.
'Tis most meet you should.
Neither to you, nor anyone…
having no witness
to confirm my speech.
- Her eyes are open.
- Aye, but their sense is shut.
What is it she does now?
It is an accustomed action with her
- to seem thus washing her hands.
Yet here's a spot.
Out, damned spot.
Out, I say.
One.
Two.
Why, then 'tis time to do it.
Hell is murky.
Fie, my lord, fie!
A soldier and afeard?
What need we fear who knows it, when
none can call our power to account?
Yet who'd have thought the old man
to have so much blood in him?
Well, well, well.
The thane of Fife had a wife.
Where is she now?
What, will these
hands ne'er be clean?
No more of that, my lord.
No more of that.
Your mar all with
this starting.
Go to. Go to. You have
known what you should not.
She has spoke what she should
not, I am sure of that.
Here's the smell
of blood still.
All the perfumes of Arabia will
not sweeten this little hand.
Oh!
What a sigh is there.
The heart is solely charged.
Wash your hands.
Put on your nightgown.
Look not so pale.
I tell you yet again, Banquo's buried.
He cannot come out of his grave.
Even so?
To bed.
Come. Come, come.
Come, give me your hand.
What's done cannot be undone.
To bed, to bed.
To bed.
More needs she the divine
than the physician.
God.
God forgive us all.
Look after her.
Remove from her
the means of all annoyance…
and still keep eyes upon her.
- So good night.
- Good night, good doctor.
How does your patient, Doctor?
Not so sick, my lord,
as she's troubled…
with thick-coming fancies
that keep her from her sleep.
Cure her of that.
Canst thou not minister
to a mind diseased?
Pluck from the memory
a rooted sorrow?
Raze out the written troubles
of the brain?
And with some sweet,
oblivious antidote…
cleanse the charged bosom
of that perilous stuff…
which weighs upon the heart?
Therein the patient
must minister to himself.
Throw physic to the dogs.
I'll none of it.
Bring me no more reports.
Let them fly. All!
Till Birnam Wood remove to
Dunsinane, I cannot taint with fear.
What's the boy, Malcolm?
Was he not born of woman?
The spirits that know all mortal
consequence have pronounced me thus:
"Fear not, Macbeth.
No man that's born of woman…
shall e'er have
power upon thee."
Then fly, false thanes…
and mingle with the
English epicures!
Our country
sinks beneath the yoke.
It weeps, it bleeds.
And each new day
a gash is added to her wounds.
Each new morn new widows howl,
new orphans cry.
New sorrows strike heaven on the face that
it resounds as if it felt with Scotland.
Who comes here?
A countryman
who seems a stranger to us.
My ever gentle cousin.
Welcome hither.
Stands Scotland where it did?
Alas, poor country.
Almost afraid to know itself.
It cannot be called our
mother, but our grave.
What's the newest grief?
Each minute teems a new one.
How does my wife?
Why, well.
- And all my children?
- Well too.
The tyrant has not battered
at their peace?
No. They were well at peace
when I did leave them.
Heave! Heave!
Be not a niggard of your
speech. How goes it?
Your eye in Scotland
will create soldiers…
make our women fight
to doff their dire distresses.
We are coming thither.
Gracious England hath lent us
good Seyward and 10,000 men.
Oh!
An older and a better soldier
none that Christendom gives out.
Oh!
♪
Would I could answer this
comfort with the like.
But I have words that will be
howled out in the desert air…
where hearing should
not catch them.
What concern they?
The main part
pertains to you alone.
If it be mine, keep
it not from me.
Quickly, let me have it.
Your castle is surprised, your wife
and babes savagely slaughtered.
Merciful heaven.
What, man!
Ne'er put your hat
upon your brows.
Give sorrow words.
My children too?
Wife, children, servants.
All that could be found.
And I must be from thence.
- My wife killed too?
- I have said.
Be comforted.
Let's make us medicines
of our great revenge…
to cure this deadly grief.
He has no children.
All my pretty ones!
Did you say all?
Hell-kite!
What, all my pretty chickens and
their dam at one fell swoop?
Dispute it like a man.
I shall do so.
But I must also
feel it as a man.
I cannot but remember
such things were…
that were most precious to me.
Did the heaven look on
and would not take their part?
Sinful Macduff,
they were all struck for thee.
Not for their own demerits, but for
mine, fell slaughter on their souls.
Heaven rest them now.
Be this the
whetstone of your sword.
Let grief convert to anger.
Blunt not the heart.
Enrage it!
Gentle heavens…
cut short all intermission.
Front to front bring thou this
fiend of Scotland and myself.
Our power is ready.
Macbeth is ripe for shaking.
Within my sword's
length set him.
If he escape,
heaven forgive him too.
What does the tyrant?
Great Dunsinane
he strongly fortifies.
Some say he's mad.
Others that lesser hate him
do call it valiant fury.
Those he commands
move only in command.
Nothing in love.
Now does he feel his title
hang loose about him…
like a giant's robe
upon a dwarfish thief.
All that is within him does
condemn itself for being there.
The English power is near, led on by Malcolm,
his Uncle Seyward and the good Macduff.
Near Birnam Wood
shall we well meet them.
That way are they coming.
The devil damn thee
black, thou cream-faced loon!
Where got'st thou
that goose look?
There is 10,000 s -
Geese, villain?
Soldiers, sir.
Thou lily-livered boy.
What s-s-soldiers, patch?
Death to thy soul. Those linen cheeks
of thine are counselors to fear.
What soldiers, whey-face?
The English force,
s-so please you.
Seyton!
Take thy face hence.
I am sick at heart,
when I behold -
Seyton, I say!
Seyton.
- Seyton! Sir! Seyton!
- Seyton!
I have lived long enough.
My may of life is fallen into
the sear, the yellow leaf.
And that which should
accompany old age…
as honor, love, obedience…
troops of friends…
I must not look to have.
But in their stead, curses…
not loud, but deep.
Mouth-honor…
breath which the poor heart
would fain deny and dare not.
Seyton!
- What's your gracious pleasure?
- What news more?
All is confirmed, my lord,
which was reported.
I'll fight till from my bones
my flesh be hacked.
- Give me my armor.
- 'Tis not needed yet.
I'll put it on.
Send out more horses,
skirr the country round.
Hang those that talk of fear.
Come, put mine armor on,
give me my sword.
Doctor, the thanes
fly from me.
Come, sir, dispatch.
If thou couldst, Doctor…
cast the water of my land,
find her disease…
and purge it to a sound
and pristine health…
I would applaud thee to the very
echo that should applaud again.
Pull it off, I say!
What rhubarb, senna…
or what purgative drug would
scour these English hence?
- Hear'st thou of them?
- Aye, my good lord.
Your royal preparation
makes us hear something.
I will not be afraid
of death or bane…
till Birnam Forest
come to Dunsinane.
Were I from Dunsinane
away and clear…
profit again
should hardly draw me here.
♪
- What wood is this before us?
- The wood of Birnam.
"They met me
in the day of success.
And I have learnt
by the perfectest report…
they have more in them
than mortal knowledge.
Wh-While I stood rapt
in the wonder of it…
came…
missives from the king,
who all-hailed me…
thane of Cawdor…
by which title, before, these
weird sisters saluted me…
and referred me
to the coming on of time with:
'Hail, king that shall be!'
This have I thought good to deliver
thee, my dearest partner of greatness…
that thou mightst not be -
ignorant of what… greatness
is promised thee.
Lay it to thy heart, and…
farewell."
Hang out our banners
on the outward walls.
The cry is still, "They come!"
Our castle's strength
will laugh a siege to scorn.
Here let them lie till famine
and the ague eat them up.
Were they not stuffed with
those that should be ours…
we might have met them
dareful, beard to beard…
and beat them backward home.
What is that noise?
I've almost forgot
the taste of fear.
The time has been, my senses would
have cooled to hear a night-shriek.
My fell of hair…
would at a dismal treatise rouse
and stir as life were in't.
I have supped
full with horrors.
Wherefore was that cry?
The queen, my lord, is dead.
She should have
died hereafter.
There would have been a time
for such a word.
Tomorrow
and tomorrow and tomorrow…
creeps in this petty pace
from day to day…
to the last syllable
of recorded time.
And all our yesterdays
have lighted fools…
the way to dusty death.
Out, out, brief candle.
Life's but a walking shadow…
a poor player…
struts and frets his hour
upon the stage…
and then is heard no more.
It is a tale told by an idiot…
full of sound and fury…
signifying nothing.
Gracious, my lord!
Thy story, quickly.
I should report that which I say I
saw, but know not how to do it.
Well? Say, sir!
As I did stand my watch,
I looked toward Birnam.
And anon, me thought,
the wood began to move.
Liar and slave!
Within a mile may
you see it coming.
A moving grove.
♪
If thou speak'st false…
upon the next tree shalt thou hang
alive till famine cling thee.
Fear not till Birnam
Wood do come to Dunsinane.
And now a wood
comes towards Dunsinane.
Every soldier hath hewed and downed
a bough and bears it before him.
Thereby do they shadow
the number of their host…
and make discovery
err in report of them.
I 'gin to
be aweary of the sun…
and wish the estate of
the world were now undone.
Ring the alarum bell!
Blow, wind! Come, wrack! At least
we'll die with harness on our back!
Make all our trumpets speak.
♪
Worthy Macduff, you, with young
Seyward, lead our first assault.
♪
Tyrant! Show thy face!
Let me find him, Fortune.
For more I beg not.
If thou be slain
and with no sword of mine…
my wife and children's ghosts
will haunt me still.
What is thy name?
Thou'lt be afraid to hear it.
No. Though thou call'st thyself a
hotter name than any is in hell.
My name's Macbeth!
The devil himself could not pronounce
a title more hateful to mine ear.
No, nor more fearful.
Thou liest, abhorrent tyrant!
With my sword I'll prove
the lie thou speak'st.
Thou wast born of woman.
They have tied
me to the stake.
I cannot fly.
But bear-like I must
fight the course!
Why should I play the Roman
fool and die on mine own sword…
while I see lives
that gashes do better on them?
What's he that was
not born of woman?
Such a one am I
to fear, or none.
Turn, hell-hound!
Turn!
Of all men else,
I have avoided thee.
I have no words.
My voice is in my sword.
Thou bloodier villain
than terms can give thee out!
My soul is too much charged
with blood of thine already.
Let fall thy blade
on vulnerable crests.
I bear a charmed life…
which must not yield
to one of woman born!
Despair thy charm…
and let the angel whom
thou hast served tell thee…
Macduff was from his mother's
womb untimely ripped!
Accursed be that
tongue that tells me so…
for it hath cowed my
better part of man.
And be these juggling fiends
no more believed…
that palter with us
in a double sense.
That keep the word of promise to
our ear and break it to our hope.
I will not yield…
to kiss the ground
before young Malcolm's feet…
and to be baited with
the rabble's curse!
Though Birnam Wood
be come to Dunsinane…
and thou opposed
being of no woman born…
yet I will try the last.
Lay on, Macduff.
And damned be him that
first cries, "Hold, enough!"
So great a day as this
is cheaply bought.
Hail, king, for so thou art.
Behold where lies
the usurper's cursed head.
The time is free.
Hail!
Hail, king of Scotland!