(lion roars)
(gentle synth music)
(gentle synth music continues)
(lively percussive music)
(children chatter)
(horn honks)
- Be careful.
Tommy!
(chatter in foreign language)
Don't do that.
Oh, look! There's daddy.
- [Tommy] Where?
- [Heather] I see him!
- [Tommy] Where, Daddy?
- [Heather] This thing is getting heavy.
- My office.
Right there.
There.
- I can watch you from here when you work.
- Yeah.
But most of the time, I'm
gonna be way out there.
(gentle synth music)
;' Gently down the stream [
J Merrily, merrily, merrily, merrily J
J Life is but a dream J
- Daddy, when do we get there?
- She said it again, Mom.
- What?
I told you, if you say that one more time,
I was gonna strangle you!
(Heather giggles)
- I spy with my little eye!
Look.
- Hurray!
- All right!
- Yay!
- Great!
- [Jean] Hallelujah!
- [Tommy] Are all these
guys working for you, Daddy?
(Bill laughs)
(brakes squeal)
- Hi, Pavio. How's it going?
- Good to see you.
- Ah, you see it's going pretty well.
By the way, I would like
you to take a look at
some plans I heard about, no?
- Pavio, this is my wife Jean.
- How do you do?
- Hi, how are you?
- This is Pavio.
(chatter drowned out by engines)
- Tommy!
(engines roar)
We have to clear 10 square
kilometers and level right down.
Going to be some time before your husband
can start pouring concrete.
(tree thumps)
- See, the roots on the
trees are not very deep,
so the bulldozer can
just push 'em right down.
- I'm scared.
- I'm not.
(tree crashes)
- One of these days, when
you get a little bigger,
I'll show you how to drive one of those.
- Great!
(engines roar)
- [Bill] Come on. Let's
get something to eat, huh?
(engines roar)
(birds chirp)
(food crunches)
- Where's everything going to be?
- Well, there's a lot
more work to be done.
We gotta clear all these trees here,
all this, all the way down to the river,
before we even can start
construction on the dam.
Over here, we'll put the
town and the airstrip.
(Jean giggles)
- It's really gonna be
something, isn't it?
- Mommy, is Tommy allowed?
- [Jean] Tommy?
- It's okay, Daddy. Isn't it?
- Is it safe?
- [Bill] You just stay
where I can see you, okay?
- Are there any snakes here, Daddy?
- No.
(suspenseful music)
(tribe member chuckles)
- Daddy! Daddy!
Daddy!
There's people in there!
- People? What kind of people?
- Smiling people.
- He just wants you to play with him.
(Heather giggles)
- Okay, big boy. Let's go have a look!
All right, come on, come on.
- There, I'll show you!
(Tommy giggles)
- Where are they?
Smiling people, huh?
(Tommy laughs)
Come on!
I don't see anybody.
- They were here.
- All right, come on. Let's go.
Tell you what I'd like to do?
Let's go down to the river
and have a swim, all right?
Tommy, come on! Quit
fooling around, let's go!
(suspenseful music)
Tommy!
Get yourself down here!
Come on, Tommy.
I'm not playing around now.
I'm gonna bust your behind
when I get you, son.
(arrow thuds)
(suspenseful music continues)
Tommy?
Tommy!
(Bill grunts)
Jean!
Jean! Get some help!
They've taken Tommy!
- What?
- They've taken Tommy!
Just get some help!
- [Jean] Help!
Help!
Somebody help me, please!
(Jean speaks foreign language)
(leaves rustle)
(Bill grunts and pants)
(workers speak foreign language)
(workers yell in foreign language)
- It's okay.
(Heather whimpers)
(leaves rustle)
(Bill grunts)
- [Worker] Tommy!
(birds chirp)
(leaves rustle)
(Bill grunts)
(Bill grunts and pants)
- Tommy!
(workers speak foreign language)
- Tommy?
Baby, answer me.
Bill!
(Bill grunts)
- [Jean] Tommy!
- [Worker] Tommy!
- Tommy!
(ominous music)
- [Jean] Tommy!
(chatter drowned out by engines)
(Bill speaks foreign language)
(worker speaks foreign language)
(helicopter roars)
(Bill speaks foreign language)
(helicopter blades whir)
(pilot speaks foreign language)
(Bill speaks foreign language)
(distant children chatter)
- It's a big problem here,
yes? These abandoned children.
More than two million,
roaming the streets.
Et cetera, et cetera.
I will cover it, but it's
been done so many times.
- Jean's searched all
these places for Tommy.
When she saw what was going
on, she kinda got involved.
- Oh. I see.
She looks after lost children,
and maybe someone, somewhere,
looks after her lost boy.
(distant chatter)
- So, we gradually built up
this map of Amazonian tribes
and their hunting grounds,
their numbers, cosmologies,
and so on.
Your editor was so helpful early on,
by publishing our problem.
A lot of people came
forward with information.
- Yeah. He is very sentimental.
He likes, uh, human stories.
It makes him feel noble.
- This area that, um,
you and Bill are going to be going to.
We know for a fact there are at least
two tribes
that have had no contact
with the outside world.
- Are you taking fireworks this time, Dad?
- Sure.
- [Jean] Somewhere in this region here.
- And, uh...
You think
the poor little boy...
- No. It's not knowing
that's so hard, you know?
There are times when I...
- You almost wish he were dead?
Oh, so you can stop all the searching and
at least you would have
some peace of mind.
I can understand that!
- You don't understand at all.
(boat engine chugs)
- Can you smell it?
The oxygen?
40% of the world's oxygen is
produced here, in the Amazon.
- Come on, Uwe.
You know oxygen doesn't
smell. It's the rot.
The decay.
- Also the blossoms.
(chatter in foreign language)
(camera shutter clicks)
(birds chirp)
(chatter in foreign language)
- Look!
- You would miss these trips
if you found your boy, huh?
- Listen, Uwe, I'm letting you tag along
because I owe your magazine a favor.
But I am running out of
gratitude, real fast!
- No,. Please.
Just making fun!
(chatter in foreign language)
(boat engine chugs)
(Leduc speaks foreign language)
(bell rings)
Ah!
(children chatter in foreign language)
- Padre Leduc.
- Hello.
- Good to see you.
This is Uwe Werner.
- Confirmed atheist, I'm afraid.
- Oh. They confirm atheists now.
It's hard to keep up
with new ideas out here.
- There you go.
You got my message?
- I did, indeed.
Would this craft be suitable?
- Just the ticket.
- [Leduc] You talk with
the Indians before you go?
(Bill speaks foreign language)
- He's saying something
about being not seen.
- Yes. They say it's
an arrow of the, um...
The Invisible People.
(Bill speaks foreign language)
- Did he say, "They hunt
on this side of the river"?
- Yes.
(camera shutter clicks)
- You ever had contact with this tribe?
- Nobody has.
Even these people here
have only heard about them,
from others.
(chatter in foreign language)
(gentle synth music)
(birds chirp)
(animals chatter)
(dart whooshes)
I killed him!
One dart!
- Tomme.
No.
He's old and slow, like me.
(Wanadi chuckles)
(birds chirp)
(water splashes)
Beware, it's a very hungry jaguar
that hunts fish.
(water splashes)
Allow for the water
bending the arrow.
(birds chirp)
One more day and we are home.
(bird squawks)
When you hear the toucan,
danger is near.
(distant tribe chants)
The Fierce People.
(tribe chants)
(percussive music)
(distant boat engine hums)
(boat engine revs)
(birds chirp)
(water splashes)
(chatter in foreign language)
(tribe members howl)
- Tomme!
- Wanadi!
Wanadi.
(tribe members howl)
I killed a monkey.
By yourself?
My father let me.
We saw the Fierce People.
A war party of the Fierce People
is very close.
We must be prepared.
I will watch.
Mother, it's for you.
Honey.
My new son!
- Mapi!
- Tomme!
(children chatter in foreign language)
(waterfall roars)
(both grunt)
- Woo!
(water splashes)
(distant percussive music)
Girls from Paranita.
(bow string thuds)
Who's she?
That's Kachiri.
Little Kachiri?
You like her?
(Mapi pants)
(Mapi chuckles)
(tribe members chatter and giggle)
(Mapi laughs)
You will scare the fish.
You won't spear a fish.
But a fish is going to spear you.
(suspenseful music)
(Kachiri yelps)
(percussive music)
Tomme, you think you are a man...
but I only see a stupid boy.
Your time has come to die.
Must he die?
Yes.
I will never see my boy again.
(ritualistic percussive music)
(tribe members chant in foreign language)
(Tomme grunts and pants)
(Tomme pants)
(tribe members chant in foreign language)
(Tomme yells in foreign language)
(water swashes)
The boy is dead...
and the man is born.
(wind music)
(waterfall roars)
- [Bill] Hold it!
- I was beginning to lose faith in you.
- We'll camp here.
(Uwe grunts)
(water splashes)
(pots clang)
(insects buzz)
- How do they get under the net?
How do they do it?
- You're not losing your
sense of humor, are you, Uwe?
- [Uwe] All this waiting. Is
that what you do for 10 years?
Wait?
- [Bill] Mostly.
(ritualistic percussive music)
(Tomme grunts)
(percussive music continues)
(suspenseful music)
(eagle screams)
(suspenseful music continues)
(Tomme breathes heavily)
I saw green stones in a waterfall.
You have seen the Sacred Stones.
It was the place we lived in
before the Fierce People came.
From these stones comes the paint
that makes us the Invisible People.
Just these are left.
I will go to that place
and find more stones.
(lively percussive music)
(birds chirp)
(gentle music)
I need you and you need me.
Now you are a man.
You say what other men say to me.
I will find
the Sacred Stones...
which is more
than other men can do.
The Fierce People
will catch you.
I will be Invisible.
They will cook you
and eat you...
even the grandfathers
without teeth.
I am invisible.
(percussive music continues)
(suspenseful percussive music)
(firework bangs)
(fuse hisses)
(fireworks whoosh)
(fireworks bang)
(ominous percussive music)
(firework whooshes)
(firework bangs)
- Astonishing.
(tribe members grunt)
(chatter in foreign language)
- [Bill] This is what
you came for, isn't it?
- [Uwe] You think they are lost tribe?
(Bill laughs)
- [Bill] If anybody's lost, it's us.
(chatter in foreign language)
(birds chirp)
(percussive music)
(tribe members chant in foreign language)
(tribe members yell in foreign language)
(camera shutter clicks)
(chanting and chatter in foreign language)
(Bill speaks foreign language)
(Jacareh chuckles)
(Jacareh yells in foreign language)
- What did he say?
- [Bill] He says the arrow
belongs to the Invisible People
who are good meat.
But maybe you and I are even sweeter.
(Jacareh yells in foreign language)
(tribe members yell)
(gun fires rapidly)
(Jacareh yells in foreign language)
(birds squawk)
(tribe members grunt)
(bullet clinks)
(tribe members murmur)
(Jacareh grunts)
(Jacareh speaks foreign language)
(Jacareh yells in foreign language)
- What's going on?
What did he say?
- He says
that I have the heart of
a hungry jaguar, like him.
Jacareh!
- He's giving me a chance.
- 1 go now.
- At dawn, they hunt me.
(tribe members chatter
in foreign language)
- What about me?
(Uwe groans)
(weapons thud)
(tribe members howl)
(tribe members grunt rhythmically
with percussive music)
(gun fires rapidly)
(tribe members howl)
(Bill pants)
(percussive music)
(tribe members grunt rhythmically)
(birds chirp)
(jaws snap)
(Bill gasps)
(birds chirp)
(distant waterfall roars)
(Tomme pants)
(Bill pants)
(tribe members barks)
(gun fires rapidly)
(birds squawk)
(tribe member barks)
(gun fires rapidly)
(tribe members howl)
(Bill pants)
(gun fires rapidly)
(waterfall roars)
(birds chirp)
(water splashes)
(arrow thuds)
(Bill groans)
(Jacareh yells in foreign language)
(tribe members grunt)
(bow string thuds)
(arrow thuds)
(Bill groans)
(tribe members howl)
(Bill grunts)
(gentle synth music)
(distant tribe members howl)
(Bill grunts)
(Bill groans)
(birds chirp)
(distant waterfall roars)
(waterfall roars)
(gun clatters)
(Bill groans)
(gun fires rapidly)
(bullets ricochet)
(waterfall roars)
(tribe members grunt)
(Jacareh yells in foreign language)
(bow string pings)
(tribe member groans)
(water splashes)
(arrow thuds)
(Bill groans)
(bow string twangs)
(body thuds)
(arrow snaps)
(Bill groans)
(Bill pants)
(tribe members howl)
(bow string twangs)
(gun fires rapidly)
(tribe members scream)
(tribe members speak foreign language)
(Bill groans)
(Bill grunts)
(bow string twangs)
(tribe member grunts)
(Tomme groans)
(gun thuds)
(water splashes)
(fist thuds)
(Bill pants)
(water splashes)
(tribe members yell in foreign language)
(Jacareh yells in foreign language)
(Bill speaks foreign language)
(waterfall roars)
(Jacareh yells in foreign language)
(Bill pants)
- Tommy.
Tommy.
- Tomme.
My name is Tomme.
Where do we go now?
(Bill coughs)
We go to my father.
He will help you.
I am your father.
No, you are Daddee.
You live in there, when I dream.
Now you are here.
Come.
(Bill grunts)
(Bill coughs)
(Tomme pants)
(Bill grunts)
Listen.
The frogs.
A big rain comes.
- Tommy?
Tomme.
your mother, Jean,
can you remember her?
Jean.
(thunder rumbles)
(thunder claps)
(tribe members grunt rhythmically)
(Jacareh screams)
(Tomme squawks)
- [Tribe Member] Wanadi!
The Stones.
The Sacred Stones.
I killed five fierce warriors.
Five!
He is Daddee.
I told you about him...
the one in my dreams.
Hey, Daddee.
Yes, we know you.
(Bill groans)
When a dream becomes flesh...
trouble is not far behind.
(Bill groans lightly)
He has a fever.
He is near death.
Father, surely you can cure him.
Even a great storm...
can not always quench
a forest fire.
- Wanad..
Wanadi, do it.
If it can be done...
I will do it.
(Bill grunts lightly)
Daddee. Can you hear me?
- Tommy! (grunts)
He will hear you.
I will suck out the evil fire.
(Wanadi yells in foreign language)
(Wanadi blows sharply)
The evil fire is gone.
You see...
he is a great healer.
Now, he must sleep.
(birds chirp)
(tribe members chatter
in foreign language)
I will show you a great secret.
(gentle wind music)
(Wanadi sucks sharply)
Watch the fire.
(Wanadi coughs)
(Tomme winces)
(Wanadi chuckles)
(both laugh)
(distant baby cries)
(Bill breathes heavily)
Why did you take my son?
One day, I was hunting
at the edge of the world...
when Tomme appeared...
and he smiled...
and even though you were
a Termite Child...
I had not the heart...
to send you back
to The Dead World.
Why are they called
The Termite People?
They come into the world...
and chew down all
the grandfather trees.
Just like termites.
(distant chatter in foreign language)
(Wanadi grunts aggressively)
(gentle percussive music)
(tribe member yells in foreign language)
(tribe members hoot and howl)
(suspenseful percussive music)
(tribe members squeal)
I want your daughter...
but I give you the Sacred Stones.
- Ah,
Oh.
(tribe members squeal)
(tribe members grunt)
- Kachari, you will tend the fire.
- No! I tend to my father's fire.
Do it right.
(tribe members grunt
with percussive music)
(stick thuds)
(tribe members squeal)
(tribe members grunt rhythmically)
(friends giggle)
(birds chirp)
(gun cocks)
(gun fires rapidly)
- No, no, no.
This.
No.
This. Huh?
(trader speaks foreign language)
(Jacareh speaks foreign language)
(chatter in foreign language)
(gentle music)
(gentle music continues)
(birds chirp)
(distant chatter in foreign language)
(Bill grunts)
You like it?
I made it for you.
- Tommy.
- Tomme?
Tomme Kachiri.
Tomme needs Kachari...
Kachiri Tomme.
and Kachari needs Tomme.
You need me?
You are well?
She is yours if you have need.
Need?
Yes.
Eat and be strong...
then you will have need.
Shall we go to the river and bathe?
(waterfall roars)
(tribe member yells)
(water splashes)
- Woo!
We have crushed
the sacred stones.
And once again they...
shine in our war paint.
You are well.
- Tommy.
Tomme.
I want you to come with me.
Momme wants you to come home.
He is finished with mothers.
I am his woman now.
You stole my son.
He took you from me, from Momme.
That was long ago.
I just want you to see the home
that you came from.
This is my home.
It will be the home of my
children.
Daddee, you must rest here...
and we must hunt.
For tonight is the feast
of Tomme and Kachari.
Stop.
You are the chief.
Tell him to come and visit.
He can choose.
If I tell a man...
to do what he does not
want to do...
I am no longer chief.
(tribe members cheer)
(Bill whimpers)
(distant chatter in foreign language)
Why are you so sad?
- Oh.
Ten years, Tomme...
looking for you...
all over.
Yes. It is good to hunt...
to track an animal.
You should be happy.
But no, you feel sad.
It will be a good feast tonight.
(lively percussive music)
(lively percussive music continues)
(tribe members chant)
(tribe members scream wildly)
(percussive music continues)
(tribe members grunt and snarl)
(tribe members hoot and howl)
- Tomme.
I must return.
Why go back
to that terrible place?
You can stay...
and become a great warrior
and hunter.
My family is there.
It is where I belong.
- Tomme.
Bring the pipe.
I swore to Tommy's mother...
I would bring him back.
your heart is torn.
If you take him,
you'll wish you had not.
If you don't take him
you will wish you had.
You are a man of courage.
You have traveled far...
and you have come
to the center of the world.
Now you can go farther
and see more.
But you can not enter
that place naked.
It is our way.
Accept our gift, Daddee...
You will meet your spirit animal
and he will show you.
(tribe member blows sharply)
(Bill groans)
(Bill screams)
(dark percussive music)
(leopard roars)
(dark music continues)
(glass shatters)
(Bill gasps)
(distant engines rev)
(distant chatter)
- Hey.
(worker speaks foreign language)
(chatter in foreign language)
When I was a boy...
the Edge of the World
was very far...
but every year it comes closer.
- Oh.
You're home.
Oh, my God. What's happened you?
Something's happened.
You know something, don't you?
- Yeah.
(birds chirp)
(ominous music)
(tribe members murmur)
(Wanadi yells in foreign language)
(ominous percussive music continues)
The Fierce Ones came before dawn.
Tomme, Tomme!
- [Tomme] Kachiri!
Kachiri!
Mother!
There was a terrible noise.
They had spears
that make lightning.
Kachiri.
Did you see Kachari?
I ran away.
Uluru. Father, they have killed Uiuru.
Kachiri.
I can not find Kachari.
(Tomme pants)
(suspenseful percussive music)
- Tomme!
(fire crackles)
(somber wind music)
(somber wind music continues)
The fire will set free
their souls to the stars.
(somber wind music continues)
(tools clack rhythmically)
And what is left of the dead
must be crushed.
Crushed into dust.
In here is the dust of those
who went before us...
even the First Man
and First Woman.
(ashes crash)
(somber music continues)
Now drink in memory
of what we have been...
and the lives of those
who went before us...
will live inside us.
Drink, boy. You come too.
(tribe members chatter
in foreign language)
(Tribe members grunt rhythmically)
(prisoners whine)
(prisoners scream)
(Jacareh yells in foreign language)
(prisoner grunts wildly)
(prisoner grunts)
(Jacareh yells in foreign language)
(birds chirp)
(distant engines hum)
They are taking
the Skin off The World.
How will she breathe?
There was a great river there once.
What is that?
It's like...a log jam.
This was the home
of the Fierce People.
Now we know why they came
to our part of The World.
Father, there!
Come back.
We are not invisible
in The Dead World.
But Father!
No. We go along
The Edge of The World.
(vehicle approaches)
(bow string twangs)
(arrow clinks)
(engine roars)
(birds chirp)
(tribe members yell)
(prisoners yelp)
(Jacareh yells in foreign language)
(trader yells in foreign language)
(prostitutes giggle and laugh)
(prostitutes chatter in foreign language)
- Hey.
(assistant speaks foreign language)
(trader speaks foreign language)
(distant laughter and chatter)
(muffled pop music)
(tribe member groans)
Look. Strange trees and vines.
We can climb up.
Go across the vine and down.
(Tomme grunts)
(distant laughter and chatter)
(muffled pop music)
(sparks crackle and pop)
(tribe member groans)
(tribe member grunts)
(tribe member screams)
(tribe member groans)
(tribe members murmur)
(distant yelling in foreign language)
- Tomme!
(trader speaks foreign language)
(tribe members chatter)
- Ah, hah-hah!
Oh! Hah-hah!
If we attack now we will all die.
But without our women
we will be a people no more.
(distant tribe chants rhythmically)
(gun fires rapidly)
(tribe member screams)
(bullets ricochet)
(gun fires rapidly)
(tribe member screams)
(body thumps)
(gun fires rapidly)
(bullets ricochet)
(tribe members grunt rhythmically)
(Jacareh yells in foreign language)
(gun fires rapidly)
(Jacareh yells)
(tribe member screams)
(gun fires rapidly)
(Jacareh yells)
(Wanadi groans)
(gun fires rapidly)
(bullets ricochet)
(arrow thuds)
(Jacareh groans)
Father...
(Wanadi groans)
(spear thuds)
(tribe member groans)
(Jacareh grunts)
(Jacareh yells in foreign language)
(gun fires rapidly)
(tribe members grunt rhythmically)
(gun fires)
(bleak music)
(Wanadi breathes heavily)
Put me down. I must die.
Brother, set my soul free with fire.
Add a few grains of my bones...
to the dust of those
that went before us.
Tomme,.
Son...
do what I could not do.
I will, Father.
Do as my father says.
Take his body back...
and wait for me there.
What? Where will you go?
I will go beyond
The Edge of The World.
To find my other father.
He knows about the Lightning Spears.
I will ask him to help us.
(Tomme and Mapi pant)
(lively percussive music)
How do you know this is the way?
He told me he lives at the end
of The-River-Without-Water.
(vehicle approaches)
(percussive music continues)
(fires crackle)
(Tomme and Mapi pant)
(distant boat horn blows)
The-River-Without-Water
ends here.
Daddee lives here?
He said his village...
has more people than ants
in an ant hill.
Could that be it?
(percussive music continues)
(dog barks)
(hushed chatter)
(water splashes)
(dog barks)
(villager yells in foreign language)
(water splashes)
(townspeople yell in foreign language)
(gun fires)
(dog barks)
(resident speaks foreign language)
(resident yells in foreign language)
Ah.
I know you.
You are The Invisible People.
Come. Hurry.
(door closes)
So there are still people like you.
(muffled footsteps stomp)
(muffled yelling)
(resident yells in foreign language)
Paulo.
(resident speaks foreign language)
(Paulo laughs)
We once lived out there,
not far from them.
You called us The Bat People.
Because you hunted at night.
My father told me many stories
about your tribe.
Why do you come here?
We seek what you call
A White Man.
Can you help us?
What's he called?
- Bill. Bill.
Bill. He said he was called Bill.
- Mm. (chuckles)
Bill. Senor Bill.
Senor Bill?
It's not enough.
The people here have many names.
You must know them all...
and each living place
has a number.
Did he tell you any numbers?
No.
We can not wait.
I must find him.
(suspenseful music)
I will look through the darkness
of what-has-been.
(Tomme grunts)
(lively percussive music)
(eagle screams)
(Tomme grunts)
(Tomme grunts and pants)
I have seen.
I remember.
(suspenseful music)
(leaves rustle)
(suspenseful music continues)
(Tomme pants)
(Tomme grunts)
(door creaks)
(window squeaks)
- Tommy.
(engine revs)
(distant laughter and chatter)
(distant chatter in foreign language)
(muffled pop music)
(motorcycle engine revs)
(smooth pop music)
(trader speaks foreign language)
(hand slaps)
(chatter in foreign language)
(prisoner speaks foreign language)
(assistant speaks foreign language)
(Bill speaks foreign language)
(muffled pop music)
(muffled chatter and laughter)
(object clacks)
(arrow thuds)
(guard groans)
(chain clinks)
(smooth pop music)
Wait for the war cry.
(patron speaks foreign language)
(patron yells in foreign language)
I have told them to wait
for the war cry.
Wait for the war cry.
(prisoner yells in foreign language)
(padlock clangs)
(Tomme pants)
(Kachiri whines)
(Tomme grunts)
(patron screams)
(Kachiri sobs)
(Tomme howls)
(patron screams)
(muffled screams)
(yelling in foreign language)
(patron groans)
(patron speaks foreign language)
(patron screams)
(patron grunts)
(patron yells in foreign language)
(gun fires)
(patrons scream)
(chatter in foreign language)
(foot thuds)
(trader groans)
(both grunt)
(fist thuds)
(gun fires)
(Bill yells in foreign language)
Go. This way.
(prisoners whimper)
Go. Go.
(prisoners speaks foreign language)
(gun fires)
(glass shatters)
(distant chatter in foreign language)
(prisoners pant)
(tribe members howl)
(muffled sobbing)
(gun fires)
(gun cocks)
(guns fire)
(tribe members howl)
(guns fire rapidly)
(tribe member groans)
(guns fire)
(tribe member screams)
(guns fire rapidly)
(tribe member groans)
(guns fire)
(bullets ricochet)
(gun fires)
(tribe member screams)
You are not Fierce.
(gun fires)
- Mapi!
(prisoners grunt)
(gentle music)
- [Tomme] Oh, Kachiri.
(gun thuds)
Father...
we will tell our children...
the story of what
you did for us.
You will always live
in our hearts...
and in our dreams.
Tommie, my son.
Do you see that?
Wanadi said...
it is a big log jam.
(Bill chuckles)
Yes. Lots of logs and the river...
can not flow.
Because of that log jam...
more white people
will come here...
and enter The World
and cut down more trees...
and take what is yours.
They will not find us.
We are The Invisible People.
They will, Tommie.
They will see you.
Father...
if that is a log jam...
water can break it.
- No.
No.
A great flood of water
can break it.
No.
Not this kind of log jam
you remember.
The frogs sing and it rains.
We will ask the frogs
to sing very loud.
(tribe members murmur)
(gentle music)
(Bill sighs)
(car door slams)
(car starts)
(engine revs)
(percussive music)
(tribe members chant in foreign language)
(Tomme grunts)
(eagle screams)
(ethereal percussive music)
(frogs croak)
(Tomme grunts)
(ethereal music continues)
(thunder claps)
(engine revs)
(rain splashes)
(thunder claps)
(engine roars)
(frog croaks)
(engines rev)
(thunder claps)
(frogs croak)
(engine revs)
(thunder claps)
(chatter in foreign language)
(phone rings)
- The water level rose ten
feet in the last 40 minutes.
- That's within your safety margin?
- I don't know.
- What?
- I could've made a
mistake in my calculations!
- A mistake!
You?
- You've got to evacuate the men!
- You want the men off?
(thunder claps)
(alarm blares)
(thunder roars)
(distant yelling)
(siren wails)
(distant yelling in foreign language)
(crowbar clangs)
(Bill grunts)
(door slides open)
(footsteps clack)
(muffled siren wails)
(muffled thunder claps)
(rain splashes)
(gentle percussive music)
The rain?
It has been raining for two days.
(thunder claps)
We have been to the river.
A big flood is coming.
(thunder claps)
(muffled siren wails)
(muffled thunder roars)
(muffled thunder claps)
(suspenseful music)
(muffled thunder roars)
(thunder claps)
(siren wails)
(rain splashes)
(thunder claps)
And every stream
has its spirit snake...
and all the spirit snakes
meet in the big river...
and twist around each other...
to become one,
the greatest one...
the greatest spirit
of all spirits...
The Great Anaconda...
and nothing can stop
the Great Anaconda...
not even a log jam...
Because it is angry, very...
very angry.
(tribe members giggle)
(water roars)
(thunder claps)
(siren wails)
(winch thumps)
(Bill groans)
(water rumbles)
(thunder claps)
(dam wall thumps)
(dam wall crashes)
(thunder claps)
(water gushes)
(dam wall crashes)
(thunder claps)
(gentle music)
(water splashes)
(tribe member yells)
See. Saman Po and Caya.
(tribe member giggles)
- Mapi?
And Mapi?
(Mapi screams)
- Mapi and Kaba.
Mapi and Kaba.
(tribe members laugh)
It is time to settle these matters.
And Jabuti?
It will be Pucu...
but they do not know it yet.
There will be some without men.
You should marry
one or two of them.
If you say so.
There is only you, Kachari.
(dark synth music)
(lively music)
(lively music continues)
(group sings in foreign language)
(vocalist speaks foreign language)
(lion roars)