An Israeli and a Palestinian
working together?
Let's be serious.
Even the big NGO's had
trouble making that happen.
Obviously, because of the boycott,
the integrated commerce between
Israel and Palestine
was almost non-existent,
but from the Palestinian side,
it was more than just a boycott
on Israeli commerce,
it was a moratorium on business
cooperation as well.
To be realistic,
even if Palestinian and
Israeli businessmen
want to cooperate,
the situation on the
ground made it impossible.
Yeah, I really thought
they were reckless.
We already had an ongoing
political process
happening at the same time.
When they took matters
into their own hands,
Of course, not everyone knew about the
political negotiations,
the secret peace talks,
but everybody knew about the boycott.
So what these two did was very risky.
Hi. Nizar speaking.
Hey, Nizar.
I was going to call you Sunday morning.
I didn't think it would
reach the media so fast.
You know I was abroad this week.
They spoke to my secretary.
I'm so sorry, Nizar.
Nizar?
So this is why I'm here.
To put out feelers. Everyone
says it's a crazy idea, but...
now I see that there are some
serious Palestinian businessmen,
and as you saw at the convention,
the Europeans
are willing to invest big-time
in green projects like this
in the future Palestinian state.
All we need is a pilot project
and see how things work out.
I don't imagine you're motivated by the
quality of life of the Palestinians.
I didn't say that, but...
if people can benefit
from business, why not?
What about your partner?
Have you talked to him about it?
Not yet.
I've been putting it off.
I don't think he'll cooperate.
What if he doesn't?
If he doesn't, I'll invest in it myself.
We'll find a way.
It's a field that interests me very much.
Green solar energy is the future...
especially in Palestine.
A free Palestinian state
that does not rely on Israel.
Is that a problem?
If you're going to work with
my company, I hope you know
that I'm Israeli as well.
We have to meet then.
-
- It's a good question.
Is there any way
you can come to Ramallah?
Let me see if I can get you a permit.
Nizar, Shaul.
I've been waiting for your call.
Thing is, Nizar...
I didn't get a permit for you.
Do you know about anything?
Well, we'll have to think
of something else.
<-It's true that you
never visit us.>
Welcome to the Promised Land.
What did the soldiers want?
Nothing really, just a spot
check. Happens all the time.
It's hard to believe it's this
difficult to meet someone
who lives only 45 minutes away.
Look at us, sneaking around like
two thieves. This is absurd.
Careful.
You okay?
This road leads
to the settlement over here,
and the Palestinian town of
Beit Jala over there.
They simply did not finish the wall yet.
Soon we'll be separated.
You are in a Palestinian land
fully controlled by Israel.
There's another matter, Shaul.
- Yeah?
Do you work with...
settlers?
No.
Not as a matter of principle,
I just don't.
I'll have a hard time working with you
if I know you do business
with the settlements.
Okay...
I usually don't like
when somebody is dictating to me
who I can or can't work with.
But in this case, I think it's worth it.
Any more conditions?
- No.
Actually, yes.
- Tell me.
Secrecy is the most
important thing at this point,
while we put it all together.
Okay.
- Going public, media,
that sort of thing
could cause lots of trouble.
Not to mention my family.
It would take me a hard
time to explain to them
why I'm doing this.
So how was the homecoming
with the family?
I'm sure they were very happy to see you.
My mom is so happy.
She's already looking for a wife for me.
It's okay, I've been there too.
Really? -Yes.
- Your mom also...?
Like this.
There is another thing
I have to tell you.
My sister, she lives in a settlement.
What can you do?
Sometimes there are different
opinions in one family.
Then it's your problem, not mine.
Okay.
Shaul, what's up?
Check this out.
Nice, huh?
Very impressive.
We'll need the pictures of the
village as soon as you can.
I think I can send you the
final map in a few days.
- Good. - Excellent.
Hey, Nizar.
Listen, we have to meet and talk.
What's there to talk about?
You screwed the whole thing.
I warned you.
Okay, so let's meet then.
We'll discuss the problems
and solve them.
Come to Ramallah, solve my problems.
Great, Nizar. You know
I can't come to Ramallah.
I haven't left my house
for a week, Shaul.
Forget it.
I'll talk to you later.
Listen, Nizar,
I came to apologize for what happened.
My secretary, she did not know better
when the reporter called
and I was abroad...
I warned you, this is serious.
- I know.
I got in trouble myself
with my own family.
I'm not trying to avoid responsibility,
and I know the pressure on you
is much greater, but...
I have to tell you, Nizar,
that when we met a year ago,
I was purely thinking business
and Palestine was just
another market to exploit.
But things have changed.
I feel invested in something
that is meaningful,
and it's because of you, Nizar.
And all this added pressure now
makes me realize
that what we're doing really matters.
It makes a difference in people's lives
and we must go on.
It's not just pressure.
It's a life threat I'm dealing with here.
Do you understand that?
I know.
Believe me...
I'm here in Ramallah, no?
Sorry you have to drink my coffee.
My mom's not here.
You know, last time I was in Ramallah
was when I was a soldier.
20 years ago.
But I have to admit that I feel
much safer now. -Really?
You're probably shaking
in your boots right now.
The truth is,
I'm touched you came.
Smells good.
Let's see how it tastes.
That's my brother, Tarek.
He was killed in the first Intifada.
He was only 14.
You never mentioned it.
Should I have said something?
You know what, Shaul?
We should not stop.
We cannot sit back anymore,
hoping that no one will notice us.
We should fight back,
make it clear what we stand for.
What do you mean?
- Facebook.
Facebook?
Yes, Facebook.
Look around you.
There are a lot of people like me and you
who believe that we should
find a way how to live together,
using our energy for a better future.
Many Israelis talk about wanting
to live together,
but their voices are silenced
by the minority who don't.
Exactly.
You have to realize that we
cannot work in a bubble.
If there's no political peace treaty,
any initiative like ours
is destined to fail.
Imagine if the pressure
comes from within.
Imagine if the Palestinians
and the Israelis
call their leaders to make peace.
That could be us.
I'm in.
This is a great name for the page.
Now it's your turn.
In Hebrew.
"Under the Same Sun"
I don't want to say it was unexpected.
But the wave of the political movement
caught everybody by surprise.
It was overwhelming.
The leaders had to respond
and meet the challenge.
What's different this time is
that for the first time
you can actually see masses of
Palestinian and Israeli ordinary people
working together, working
with one voice on the streets,
and you can see their activities
on the social network all around.
And after a while, politicians
couldn't just ignore these voices
but I think that this time
they were forced to.
The politicians all around the world
they were forced
to actually act and talk.
You see?
They'll be able to turn on
the light even tomorrow.
Bravo, bravo.
Nizar, I know what
your pretty face looks like.
Can you aim the phone
to the farm so I can see?
It looks good.