Venus, my Venus, Venus
Started out on the horizon
Then it grew to be a siren
I'm a fire and I'm coming undone
It's so beautiful now I'm crying
Thought that love was
made for someone else,
but you have changed me
My body and my mind agree
that you have rearranged me
Oh, Venus
Like a supernova, I can't stop
this overwhelming feeling
You got me falling in love and
everybody here can see us
My world is upside down
Oh, Venus
You turn my heart around
I couldn't love 'til you arrived
Now I'm living with
the bluer skies
I shouldn't laugh,
shouldn't be surprised
It's what you do,
and you do it right
Thought that love was
made for someone else,
but you have changed me
My body and my mind agree
that you have rearranged me
Oh, Venus
Like a supernova, I can't stop
this overwhelming feeling
You got me falling in love and
everybody here can see us
My world is upside down
Oh, Venus
You turn my heart around
Venus, my Venus, my
Venus, my Venus, Venus
Now I understand
what it is to fly
To dive in deep with someone
for more the just a night
Now I understand what
love songs really mean
Two bodies into one
Two minds into a dream
Oh, Venus
Like a supernova, I can't stop
this overwhelming feeling
You got me falling in love and
everybody here can see us
My world is upside down
Oh, Venus, mm-mm
You turn my heart around
Venus
Like a supernova, I can't stop
this overwhelming feeling
You got me falling in love and
everybody here can see us
My world is upside down
Oh, Venus, mm-mm
You turn my heart around
I didn't know that I
could want you so deep
Until I saw you with
someone who's not me
You've got me playing in
a game that ain't fair
But you're taking me there,
but you're taking me there
Oh, I can't help myself, it's
human nature, human nature
Who's to say what's
meant to be?
Oh, why can't we be on our worst
behavior, worst behavior
When it comes so naturally
'Cause I would like, to get what?
(to know you baby)
Like to get, under
your sexy body
I would like, to get,
to know you baby
Like to get, under
your sexy body
Woah, woah-oah-oah
(Under your sexy body)
I know what you're doing
when you hold her like that
You're looking at me to see
if I'm looking back
But me and you both know
where tonight is gon' lead
'Cause you're leaving with me
But you're leaving with
me, yeah
Oh, I can't help myself, it's
human nature, human nature
Who's to say what's meant to be?
Oh, why can't we be on our worst
behavior, worst behavior
When it comes so naturally
Cause I would like to get,
(to know you baby)
Like to get, under your sexy body
I would like to get,
to know you baby
(Like to get)
Under your sexy body
Woah-oah-oah
Let's dance!
(Na na na, na na, na, na)
Woah-oah-oah
(Under your sexy body)
I would like, to get,
to know you baby
Like to get, under
your sexy body
Come take me under now,
na na na, na na na
Oh, don't want to go
without, na na na, na na na
Come take me under now,
na na na, na na na
Oh, don't want to go
without, na na na, na na na
I would like, to get
to know you baby
Like to get, under
your sexy body
I would like, to get,
to know you baby
Like to get, under
your sexy body
Woah-oah-oah
(Under your sexy body)
Hey!
Come take me under now,
na na na, na na na
Oh, don't want to go
without, na na na, na na na
Come take me under now,
na na na, na na na
Oh, don't want to go
without, na na na, na na na
(Oah)
Thank you so much!
Amsterdam, how are we
feeling tonight?
What about you guys up there?
Are you feeling alright?
I am so happy to be here.
Welcome to the Venus tour
with me and my girls.
We're gonna have a
good night tonight.
Let's all just escape for
a second to planet Venus.
(Na, na, na,
yeah)
Let's put on our dancing shoes
and get a little hot and sweaty.
Everything's going like crazy
Yeah
Don't even got time
to breathe, oh yeah
Lately I'm needing my baby, mm-mm
To come and take care of
me, me, me, me
(Please) Could you pour
up my drink?
Could you rub my feet?
Would you roll with me?
Hey, baby, I'm (Weak)
In the knees, yeah
(Please) Could you pour
up my drink?
'Cause you know my kink
Would you roll with me?
Hey, baby, I'm weak
Come fly with me, yeah
Ooh, you got my heart goin', bae
I think we one and the same
Baby, be my escape
Maybe we could hop on a plane
Hear you calling my name
Baby, be my escape
Got me feeling like ooh,
na na na, yeah
Na na na, whoa-oh
Would you be my, be
my, be my escape?
See, it's a private flight
You can take me all the
way, anywhere you like
Just don't let me go
Leave all the finer things
When I'm lying next to
you, that's enough for me
Just don't let me go
Ooh, hey
Yeah
So maybe we could hop on a plane
Hear you calling my name
Baby, be my escape
Got me feeling like ooh,
na na na, yeah
Na na na, whoa-oh
Would you be my, be
my, be my escape?
Na na na, whoa-oh
Would you be my, be
my, be my escape?
Yeah
Alright, Amsterdam
Let's throw it back
to Poster Girl.
Now this is Look What
You've Done.
And now they're playing
our favorite song that
We used to dance to,
nights like tonight
The pain is fading,
feels so amazing
To know you hurt me
for the last time
So I ain't crying anymore
I'm stronger than I was before
You keep calling me again
But I keep dancing anyway
'Cause now that you're gone
I'm number one
Boy, I should thank
you for who I've become
Don't need no one
This girl's having fun
Watch me catch fire
Yeah, look what you've done
Look what you've done
(Look what you've done)
Baby, can't you see what
you've done to me?
Look what I've become
Look what you have done
'Cause now that you're gone
I'm number one
Boy, I should thank you for
who I've become
Who I've become
(Don't need no one)
This girl's having fun
This girl is having
so much fun.
Now, look what you've done
(Look what you've done)
Look what, look what
you've done
Look what you've done,
hey yeah
Baby, now look what
you've done.
Where's all my girls?
Hey!
(What do girls like?)
I know what boys like
I know what they want
They want that good thing
They wanna get some
I know what boys like
I know what they want
So go ahead and prove me right
Cause that's what girls like
Don't need me a guy who's a friend
He better pick me up in a Benz
I like cruisin' around the West End
No Netflix and chill, that's dead
(All the girls like)
I don't need your money for my rent
I'm not an eight or a nine, I'm a ten
(All the girls like)
What's the code to your Wi-Fi again?
(G-G-Girls like)
I know what boys like
I know what they want
They want that good thing
They wanna get some
I know what boys like
I know what they want
So go ahead and prove me right
Cause that's what girls like
(Go)
At your house again
Are we more than friends?
There's so much that I wanna say
But I gotta hold it back
So scared how you'll react
I just hide it all away
I could give you it
all in a minute
We'll fall any minute
But we go 'round and 'round
I don't wanna mention commitment
But I feel it slippin'
So please don't let
me down, me down
I got the words "I love you"
Sittin' on the tip of my tongue
Oh, I feel like
As soon as they leave my mouth
You're just gonna get up and run
You're gonna run away
You know we connect
More than just the sex
But are you gonna let me in?
Yeah, I can set your world on fire
But you're holdin' the lighter
Instead, you're puttin'
out our flame
I could give you it
all in a minute
We'll fall any minute
But we go 'round and 'round
I don't wanna mention commitment
But I feel it slippin'
So please don't let
me down
I got the words "I love you"
Sittin' on the tip of my tongue
Oh, I feel like
As soon as they leave my mouth
You're just gonna get up and run
You're gonna run away
(Run)
Run away (Run)
I got the words "I love you"
Sittin' on the tip of my tongue
Oh, I feel like
As soon as they leave my mouth
You're just gonna get up and run
You're gonna run away
If I say it now
Then one day, I'll wake up
and you walked out
You walked out,
you walked out
(So I just stay here with
The words "I love you")
Sittin' on the tip of my tongue
(I love you)
Run, run, run
Thank you.
I used to be so happy, but without
you here I feel so low
I watched you as you left, but
I can never seem to let you go
'Cause once upon a time
you were my everything
It's clear to see that time
hasn't changed a thing
No
It's buried deep inside me, but I feel
there's somethin' you should know
Hey
I will never
forget you, yeah
You will always be by my side
From the day that I met you
I knew that I would love
you 'til the day I die
And I will never want much more
And in my heart,
I will always be sure
I will never forget you
And you will always be
by my side 'til the day I die
'Til the day I die
Funny how we both end up here,
but everything seems so right
Right
I wonder what would happen
if we went back and put up a fight
'Cause once upon a time
you were my everything
It's clear to see that
time hasn't changed a thing
So, what in this world do you think
could ever take you off my mind?
(Take you off my mind)
I will never forget you, yeah
You will always be by my side
From the day that I met you
I knew that I would love
you 'til the day I die
And I will never want much more
And in my heart,
I will always be sure
I will never forget you
And you will always be
by my side 'til the day I die
Because I'm feelin' it, lovin' it,
everything that we do
And all along, I knew I had
somethin' special with you
But sometimes you just gotta know
that these things fall through
But I'm still tied and I can't hide
my connection with you
'Cause I am feelin' it, lovin' it,
everything that we do
And all along, I knew I had
something special with you
But sometimes you just gotta
know that these things fall through
I can't hide my connection with you
(I will never forget you, yeah)
(You will always be by my side)
(From the day that I met you)
(I knew that I would love
you 'til the day I die)
And I will never want much more
And in my heart,
I will always be sure
I will never forget you
Never forget you, no
And you will always be
by my side 'til the day I die
'Cause you will always
be by my side
(I will never forget you)
I will never, never, never, never
Never, never, never, never
I will never forget you
And you will always be by my side
'til the day I die
('til the day I die).
Thank you so much, guys.
Are you having a
good time so far?
What about you
guys on the sides?
I didn't check with you guys yet.
Are you having a good time?
I am so so happy to be
back here with you guys.
I love these signs.
Are you the number one zluts?
Is it?
I got you, I got you.
Could you give that vinyl, please?
Could you?
Thank you.
This is my new album, Venus.
Has anyone heard it yet?
Yeah?
What's your favorite song on it?
Ammunition?
Well, today is your luck day
'cause I'm gonna play that song.
I, I'm really really happy,
I really am that you all
are here tonight.
I mean, this is my favorite
spot on the whole entire earth.
And to just be here with
this many people.
And make beautiful memories
and just create together.
Honestly,
this is probably the best
nights of the tour so far.
Could you give this back?
So I will forgive you, guys
If don't know all the words
to all the new songs yet.
'Cause it didn't come
out that long ago.
I barely know them myself.
The one who knows know,
I struggle sometimes with lyrics,
but I think you guys know
this next song.
And if you do, please don't be shy.
If you wanna stand up,
stand up,
if you wanna dance, dance
and if you wanna sing along,
let's go.
I miss you pushing
me close to the edge
I miss you
I wish I knew what
I had when I left
I miss you
You set fire to my world,
couldn't handle the heat
Now I'm sleeping alone and
I'm starting to freeze
Baby, come bring me hell
Let it rain over me
Baby, come back to me
Woah yeah
I want you to ruin my life
You to ruin my life,
to ruin my life, yeah
I want you to fuck
up my nights, yeah
Fuck up my nights, yeah,
all of my nights, yeah
I want you to bring it all on
If you make it all wrong,
then I'll make it all right, yeah
I want you to ruin my life
Yeah, to ruin my life,
yeah, to ruin my life
I want you to ruin my life
You to ruin my life,
to ruin my life, yeah
I want you to fuck up my nights, yeah
Fuck up my nights, yeah,
all of my nights, yeah
I want you to bring it all on
If you make it all wrong,
then I'll make it all right, yeah
I want you to ruin my life
Yeah, to ruin my life,
yeah, to ruin my life
I miss you more than I
thought that I could
I miss you
Oh yeah, yeah
And I know you missin' me
too like you should
I miss you
You set fire to my world,
couldn't handle the heat
Now I'm sleeping alone and
I'm starting to freeze
Baby, come bring me hell
Let it rain over me
Baby, come back to me
Woah yeah
I want you to ruin my life
You to ruin my life,
to ruin my life, yeah
I want you to fuck
up my nights, yeah
Fuck up my nights, yeah,
all of my nights, yeah
I want you to bring it all on
If you make it all wrong,
then I'll make it all right, yeah
I want you to ruin my life
Yeah, to ruin my life,
yeah, to ruin my life
I want you to ruin my life
You to ruin my life,
to ruin my life, yeah
I want you to fuck
up my nights, yeah
Fuck up my nights, yeah,
all of my nights, yeah
I want you to bring it all on
If you make it all wrong,
then I'll make it all right, yeah
I want you to ruin my life
Yeah, to ruin my life,
yeah, to ruin my life
I miss you, I miss you, yeah
(You-ooh-ooh)
I wish you, I wish you, yeah
Would come back to,
come back to me
Come back to me,
I want you to ruin my life
You to ruin my life,
to ruin my life, yeah
I want you to fuck
up my nights, yeah
Fuck up my nights, yeah,
all of my nights, yeah
I want you to bring it all on
If you make it all wrong,
then I'll make it all right, yeah
I want you to ruin my life
Yeah, to ruin my life,
yeah, to ruin my life
I want you to fuck
up my nights, yeah
Fuck up my nights, yeah,
all of my nights, yeah
I want you to bring it all on
If you make it all wrong,
then I'll make it all right, yeah
I want you to ruin my life
My life, my life,
yeah
I miss you, I miss you,
I wish you, I wish you,
yeah
Well, come back,
come back
Come back,
come back to me
Come back to me
Well, come back,
come back to me
Come back to me,
please come back to me.
Alright, let's slow it
down for a second.
The one before you wasn't careful
The one before you took
my heart around the core
The one before you wasn't gentle
Nobody told me love
was a contact sport
So no, he's not your fault
That I can't love you yet
But can I be with you
after the healing
After the healing is done?
So can I be with you
after the hurting
After the monsters in my
head are finally gone?
So can I be with you
after the healing?
The one before you wasn't easy
The one before you pushed
me right over the edge
And now I got some
trouble sleeping
I'm kept awake by
knife left in my bed
So no, he's not your fault
That I can't love you yet
But can I be with you
after the healing
After the healing is done?
So can I be with you
after the hurting
After the monsters in my
head are finally gone?
So can I be with you
after the healing?
So give me just a little time
'Cause I just gotta let me cry
This isn't your responsibility
'Cause I wanna be with
you after the healing
After the healing is done
So can I be with you
after the hurting
After the monsters in my
head are finally gone?
So give me just a little time
'Cause I just gotta let me cry
This isn't your responsibility
Can I be with you
after the healing
After the healing is done?
So can I be with you
after the healing?
The beginning is a very
delicate time.
Amsterdam!
Do you wanna be part of
my symphony tonight?
You ready?
I've been hearin' symphonies
Before, all I heard was silence
Hey!
A rhapsody for you and me
And every melody is timeless
Life was stringin' me along
Then you came and
you cut me loose
Was solo, singin' on my own
Now I can't find the key without you
And now your song is on repeat
And I'm dancin' on
to your heartbeat
And when you're gone,
I feel incomplete
Are you ready?
(So, if you want the truth)
Woah-oh, I just wanna be
part of your symphony
Will you hold me tight
and not let go?
Symphony
Like a love song on the radio
Will you hold me tight
and not let go?
I'm sorry if it's all too much
Every day you're here, I'm healin'
And I was runnin' outta luck
I never thought I'd
find this feelin'
'Cause I've been hearin' symphonies
And before all I heard was silence
A rhapsody for you and me
(A rhapsody for you and me)
And every melody is timeless
And now your song is on repeat
And I'm dancin' on
to your heartbeat
And when you're gone,
I feel incomplete
So, if you want the truth
I just wanna be part
of your symphony
Will you hold me tight
and not let go?
Symphony
Like a love song on the radio
Will you hold me
tight and not let go?
Ah, ah, ah,
ah-ah-ah, ah, hey
Everybody put your hands up!
Ah-ah-ah, ah, ah, ah
And now your song is on repeat
And I'm dancin'
on to your heartbeat
And when you're gone,
I feel incomplete
So, if you want the truth
I just wanna be part
of your symphony
Will you hold me
tight and not let go?
Symphony
Like a love song
on the radio, hey
Symphony
(Will you hold me
tight and not let go?)
Symphony
Like a love song
on the radio
Will you hold me
tight and not let go?
Thank you!
That was amazing.
Alright, let's throw it back, like
really throw it back
to the very beginning
of my career, and
this song is so special to me,
and especially here 'cause it was
so well-recieved and
I feel like you guys
have been a part of my
journey for over a decade
and I just wanna sing this song
with you guys tonight
still one of my favorite songs,
you know what to do
if you know the words,
come on, Amsterdam,
are you with me?
Nobody sees, nobody knows
We are a secret, can't be exposed
That's how it is,
that's how it goes
Far from the others
Close to each other
In the daylight,
in the daylight
When the sun is shinin'
On a late night,
on a late night
When the moon is blindin'
In plain sight,
plain sight
Like stars in hidin'
You and I burn on, on
Put two and together, forever
We'll never change
Two and together
Nobody sees, nobody knows
We are a secret,
can't be exposed
That's how it is,
that's how it goes
Far from the others
Close to each other
That's when we uncover-cover-cover
My asylum, my asylum
Is in your arms
When the world gives
heavy burdens
I can bear a thousand tons
On your shoulder,
on your shoulder
I can reach an endless sky
Feels like paradise
Put two and together, forever
We'll never change
Two and together
We'll never change.
Sing!
Nobody sees, nobody knows
We are a secret, can't be exposed
And that's how it is,
that's how it goes
Far from the others
Close to each other
That's when we uncover-cover-cover
But we could build a
universe right here
All the world could disappear
I wouldn't notice, I wouldn't care
'Cause we could build
a universe right here
The world could disappear
I just need you near.
Sing!
Nobody sees, nobody knows
We are a secret, can't be exposed
That's how it is, that's how it goes
Far from the others
Close to each other
But that's when we
uncover-cover-cover
That's when we uncover-cover-cover
That's when we uncover.
Thank you so much.
That was beautiful.
Thank you, Amsterdam.
Make your jaw drop-drop
Say, "Oh my," drop-drop-drop
Make you say, "Oh my god"
My, drop-drop
Make your jaw drop
Make you say, "Oh my god"
And you never felt
this type of emotion
Make your jaw drop-drop
Say, "Oh my," drop-drop-drop
Make you say, "Oh my god"
My, drop-drop
Make your jaw drop
Make you say, "Oh my god"
And you never felt
this type of emotion
Baby, I'm not even in a gown
I'm just in a T-shirt on the couch
The way you want me
makes me want you now
The only thing you
have to say is (Wow)
And I feel this
way with no chemicals
In my system, babe, it's incredible
When you're touching me,
yeah, that says it all
You said it all (Yeah)
(Baby, I'm not even in a gown)
I'm not even in a gown
(I'm just in a T-shirt on the couch)
The way you want me
makes me want you now
Want me now
The only thing you
have to say is (Wow)
Make your jaw drop-drop
Say, "Oh my," drop-drop-drop
Make you say, "Oh my god"
My, drop-drop
Make your jaw drop
Make you say, "Oh my god"
And you never felt
this type of emotion
Make your jaw drop-drop
Say, "Oh my," drop-drop-drop
Make you say, "Oh my god"
My, drop-drop
Make your jaw drop
Make you say, "Oh my god"
(And you never felt this type of emotion)
Never, never, never
Never, never, never, oh
Never, eh
Make your jaw
make your jaw drop
Make you say, "Oh my god"
Make your jaw
make your jaw drop
And you never felt
this type of emotion.
(None of these guys;
Nothing on mine)
(None of these, none of these,
none of these, none of these)
None of these guys
got nothing on mine
They're either too short,
they're either too high
None of these guys
got nothing on mine
(Nothing on mine)
None of these guys
got nothing on mine
They don't have his cool,
they don't have his style
Yeah, none of these
guys got nothing on mine
(Nothing on mine)
Feelin' sweaty and crowded
Drippin' down to my knees
They woke up but I doubt they
Got the right energy
Hundred bodies touchin' all around
But I'm only lookin' at one
All these guys look alive but
They're just NPCs
None of these guys
got nothing on mine
They're either too short,
they're either too high
Yeah, none of these guys
got nothing on mine
(Nothing on mine, they got
nothing, they got nothing)
None of these guys
got nothing on mine
They don't have his cool,
they don't have his style
Yeah, none of these
guys got nothing on mine
(Nothing on mine)
Through the night
Nobody can read the signs
You stand out from all these guys
Way you make me feel so right
Babe, they might hate
but I can't lie-ie
None of these guys
got nothing on mine
They're either too short,
they're either too high
Yeah, none of these
guys got nothing on mine
(None of these guys
got nothing on mine)
None of these guys
got nothing on mine
They don't have his cool,
they don't have his style
Yeah, none of these
guys got nothing on mine
(mine, mine, mine)
Through the night
Nobody can read the signs
You stand out from all these guys
Way you make me feel so right
They might hate but I can't lie.
Alright, this next one.
This one's for my friend over there
and which also happens to be
one of my personal favorites off Venus.
You know my situation
Why you acting like
you can't be patient?
All I'm hearing from you lately.
What?
"Monogamy's so fucking dated"
Huh?
(Mm-mm) Boys like you
love fantasy
(Mm-mm) Anime, no,
that ain't me
(Mm-mm) They dream 'bout
controlling things
(Mm-mm) Sad you went so
cold on me, come hold on me
You've been distant
I wanna give us a shot, please
Give me, give me,
give me ammunition
Love me, love me,
kiss me, touch me
I wanna give us a shot, please
Give me, give me,
give me ammunition
You know my intuition
(Intuition, yoh)
Got me out here looking
at you different (Different)
You've been acting like
you on a mission (Yoh)
Tryna make this love we made
go missing, mm-mm yeah
Girls like me know what
we need (Mm-mm)
Fix yourself or watch
me leave (Mm-mm)
They dream 'bout
controlling me (Mm-mm)
Sad you went so cold on me,
come hold on me (Mm-mm)
You've been distant
I wanna give us a shot, please
(Shot)
Give me, give me,
give me ammunition
Love me, love me,
kiss me, touch me
I wanna give us a shot, please
Give me, give me,
give me ammunition
Can we just go back to when
I still believed in it?
'Cause if you got me way back,
then life could've been different
I'd probably be livin' with you
but after all I been through, I
I get nervous when
you're swerving me
Can't think about you hurting me
I need you to prove your worth
You've been distant
I wanna give us a shot, please
Give me ammunition
Love me, kiss me
I wanna give us a shot,
Whoa, whoa-oh
(You've been distant)
I wanna give us a shot, please
(Shot)
Give me, give me,
give me ammunition
Love me, love me,
kiss me, touch me
I wanna give us a shot, please
(Shot)
Give me, give me,
give me ammunition
Give me ammunition (Shot)
Gimme, gimme, gimme,
gimme, gimme, gimme,
Gimme, gimme
Gimme, gimme, gimme,
gimme, gimme
Love me, love me,
kiss me, touch me
Kiss me, touch me,
touch me, touch me
Love me, love me,
kiss me, touch me
Love me, love me, I wanna
give us a shot (Shot)
Love me, love me,
kiss me, touch me
Love me, love me, I wanna
give us a shot (Shot)
Love me, love me,
kiss me, touch me
This one, this one
goes out to that one friend
who would just not listen.
Ugh. You try to tell them,
You say they're not
good for you, you know.
You deserve
someone better.
And they just say:
"but I love them, you
don't get it, I love them".
You feel me, Amsterdam?
You're so in love with him, it's tragic
You just wanna have
him all to yourself (Ah)
And to your family,
he's perfect
But behind the curtains,
he's someone else (Ah)
When will you use your
common sense?
He drags you down instead
of compliments
You know he ain't Heaven-sent
No, he ain't Heaven-sent,
look at the evidence. Sing!
Girl, give him up
I'm tellin' you as a friend
What he's putting you
through is too much
I told you enough
But you don't wanna listen
You just tell me,
"You love who you love"
Won't be long,
it's a matter of time
Till you call me 'cause
he made you cry
Enough is enough
'Cause you don't wanna listen
You just tell me, "You
love who you love"
It's like we goin'
'round in circles
He does this on purpose
to keep you near (Ah)
This toxic love makin' you
feel like you're insane
He promised you he was
gonna change, but he's the same
When will you use your
common sense?
He drags you down instead
of compliments
You know he ain't Heaven-sent
No, he ain't Heaven-sent,
look at the evidence
Girl, give him up
I'm tellin' you as a friend
What he's putting you
through is too much
I told you enough
But you don't wanna listen
You just tell me, "You
love who you love"
Won't be long,
it's a matter of time
Till you call me 'cause
he made you cry
Enough is enough
'Cause you don't wanna listen
You just tell me, "You
love who you love"
Maybe one day, you will
finally understand
That if you're lookin' for
love, he isn't the man
I sound like a broken record
But you need to figure it out
Girl, give him up
I'm tellin' you as a friend
What he's putting you
through is too much
I told you enough
But you don't wanna listen
You just tell me, "You
love who you love"
Won't be long,
it's a matter of time
Till you call me
'cause he made you cry
Enough is enough
'Cause you don't wanna listen
You just tell me,
"You love who you love"
Oh my, oh my, oh my
oh my (Hahahahaha)
It ain't my fault you
keep turnin' me on
It ain't my fault you got,
got me so gone
It ain't my fault I'm
not leavin' alone
It ain't my fault you
keep turnin' me on
I can't talk right now
I'm lookin' and I like
what I'm seein',
got me feelin' kinda
shocked right now
Couldn't stop right now
Even if I wanted, gotta get it, get it,
get it when it's hot right now
Oh my God, what is this?
Want you all in my business
Baby, I insist
Please don't blame me for
whatever happens next
No, I-I-I-I can't be responsible
If I-I-I-I get you in trouble now
See, you're too irresistible
Yeah, that's for sure
So, if I put your hands
where my eyes can't see
Then you're the one
who's got a hold on me
No, I-I-I-I can't be responsible
Responsible
It ain't my fault
Nope, nope, nope, nope
Nope, nope, nope
It ain't my fault
Nope, nope, nope, nope
Nope, nope, nope
It ain't my fault
It ain't my fault you
came here lookin' like that
You just made me trip,
fall and land on your lap
Certain bad boy smooth,
body hotter than a summer
I don't mean to be rude, but
I'd look so damn good on ya
Ain't got time right now
Missed me with that "What's
your name, your sign" right now
It's light outside
I just called an Uber
and it's right outside
Oh my God, what is this?
Want you all in my business
Baby, I insist
Please don't blame me for
whatever happens next
No, I-I-I-I can't be responsible
If I-I-I-I get you in trouble now
See, you're too irresistible
Yeah, that's for sure
So, if I put your hands
where my eyes can't see
Then you're the one
who's got a hold on me
No, I-I-I-I can't be responsible
Responsible
It ain't my fault
Nope, nope, nope, nope
Nope, nope, nope
It ain't my fault
Nope, nope, nope, nope
Nope, nope, nope
Baby, one, two, three
Your body's callin' me
And I know wherever you're at
Is exactly where I wanna be
But don't blame me
It ain't my fault, no
No (Nope, nope, nope, nope
It ain't my fault)
Hey (Nope, nope, nope, nope
(Nope, nope, nope, it ain't my fault)
Well, that's too bad it ain't my fault.
Alright, let's slow it down,
get a little sexy here.
Feel, I feel myself fallin'
All the blood rushed
to my head, mm-mm
Knee-deep into emotion
And you make me want
to sink to oblivion
I want your love
to roll the dice
I put it all on you and I
Until the end of time
I want your love
to start a fire
And keep it burnin'
through the night
Baby, until the end of time
They will say that we're insane
Hey!
And in a way, baby,
we are, mm-mm
When you pull me close
underneath that light
From the moment I looked
into your eyes
Saw what I'd been searchin'
for all of this time
This time, oh
I want your love
(I want your love)
To roll the dice
(To roll the dice)
I put it all on you and I
Until the end of time
I want your love
(I want your love)
To start a fire
(To start a fire)
And keep it burnin'
through the night
Baby, until the end of time
I want your love
to redefine
The very meaning of my life
Undo the fabric of my mind
I want your love
To start a fire
And keep it burnin'
through the night
Until the end, the end, the
end of fucking time
La, la, la-la, la, la, la-la-la
La, la, la-la, la
Until the end, until the end,
until the end of time
I don't need the time to
make up my mind (Yeah, yeah)
That's on my love (Yeah)
That's on my love, yeah (Yeah)
Hear my pain, can you
hear my prayer?
Take my breath, can
you take me there?
That's on my love, yeah, yeah
Into the dark, into the
light, baby, I go
Whether it's wrong, whether
it's right, I will follow
I'll pay the price, I'll sacrifice
That's on my love, yeah
On my love, on my love
I put that on my, on
my love, on my love
I put that on my love
On my love, on my love
I put that on my, on
my love, on my love
I put that on my love
That's on my love
I still need you deep
in my heart (Yeah, yeah)
That's on my love (Yeah)
You're the one thing
I can't escape
You're the fire to my
warm embrace, yeah
That's on my love
Into the dark, into the
light, baby, I go
Whether it's wrong, whether
it's right, I will follow
I'll pay the price,
I'll sacrifice
That's on my love
On my love, on my love
I put that on my, on
my love, on my love
I put that on my love
On my love, on my love
I put that on my, on
my love, on my love
I put that on my love
On my love, on my love
I put that on my, on my
love, on my love
I put that on my love
It's party time!
I wanna see everybody
up on their feet.
Let's get moving, baby!
C'mon, Amsterdam,
sing this one with me.
I live my day as
if it was the last
Live my day as if
there was no past
Doin' it all night, all summer
Doin' it the way I wanna
Yeah, I'ma dance my heart
out 'til the dawn
But I won't be done
when mornin' comes
Doin' it all night, all summer
Gonna spend it like no other
It was a crush
But I couldn't,
couldn't get enough
It was a rush
But I gave it up
It was a crush
Now, I might've went
and said too much
But that's all it was
So I gave it up
I live my day as if
it was the last
Live my day as if
there was no past
Doin' it all night, all summer
Doin' it the way I wanna
Yeah, I'ma dance my
heart out 'til the dawn
But I won't be done
when mornin' comes
Doin' it all night, all summer
Gonna spend it like no other
It was a crush
I kept sayin',
"I'ma stay in touch"
But that thing went bust
So I gave it up, ooh
No tricks, no bluff
I'm just better off
without them cuffs
Yeah, the sun won't set on us
Ooh, ooh, ooh, yeah, yeah
Went low, went high
Still waters run dry
Gotta get back in the groove
I ain't ever worried
Went low, went high
What matters is now
Gettin' right back in the mood
I live my day as if
it was the last
Live my day as if
there was no past
Doin' it all night, all summer
Doin' it the way I wanna
Yeah, I'ma dance my
heart out 'til the dawn
But I won't be done
when mornin' comes
Doin' it all night, all summer
Gonna spend it like no other
Now I've found another crush
The lush life's given me a rush
Had one chance to make me blush
Second time is one too late
Now I've found another crush
The lush life's given me a rush
Had one chance to make me blush
Second time is one too late
Please, give it up for
my incredible band
and for my amazing dancers,
for the lightning and the sound.
Thank you so much for tonight.
You guys have been
absolutely incredible.
Are you with me on
the last chorus?
I live my day as if it was the last
Live my day as if there was no past
Doin' it all night, all summer
Doin' it the way I wanna
Yeah, I'ma dance my heart
out 'til the dawn
But I won't be done when mornin' comes
Doin' it all night, all summer
Gonna spend it like no other
Now I've found another crush
The lush life's given me a rush
Had one chance to make me blush
Second time is one too late
Now I've found another crush
The lush life's given me a rush
Had one chance to make me blush
Second time is one too late
Thank you so much, Amsterdam
I got one more song for you,
'cause I know you're wild and crazy
and I can't tame you.
You ready?
Don't need no one, she
can dance on her own
Club is closin', but she
ain't goin' home
Night is still young, where
the hell will she go?
Nobody knows, nobody knows
Ain't the first time 'cause
I've seen her before
Smell her perfume as she walks
through the door
I wanna know, where the
hell will she go?
Nobody knows, nobody,
nobody knows
No, you can't tame the girl
'Cause she runs her own world
So if she wanna party
all night (All night)
No, you can't tame her, no
And you can't tie her down
When the night comes around
Said she gonna party
all night (All night)
And you can't change
her, can't blame her
Can't tame her
No, no, no
Can't tame her magic energy
She's so magnetic, pulls you in
every time (Every time)
Every time (Every time)
But she don't care, she gonna
do what she wants (She wants)
Because she never needed
any reason (Reason)
Yeah, she a girl and she just
wanna have fun, ooh
No, you can't tame the girl
'Cause she runs her own world
So if she wanna party
all night (All night)
No, you can't tame her, no
And you can't tie her down
When the night comes around
Said she gonna party
all night (All night)
And you can't change
her, can't blame her
Can't tame her
And you can't change her,
can't blame her,
Don't need no one, she
can dance on her own
Club is closin', but she
ain't goin' home
Night is still young, where
the hell will she go?
Nobody, nobody, nobody knows
Ain't the first time
Smell her perfume
I wanna know,
What nobody knows, nobody,
nobody knows
No, you can't tame the girl
'Cause she runs her own world
So if she wanna party
all night (All night)
No, you can't tame her, no
And you can't tie her down
When the night comes around
Said she gonna party
all night (All night)
And you can't change
her, can't blame her
No, you can't tame the girl
'Cause she runs her own world
So if she wanna party
all night (All night)
No, you can't tame her, no
And you can't tie her down
When the night comes around
Said she gonna party
all night (All night)
And you can't change
her, can't blame her
Can't tame her
No, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no, no, no,
And you can't change
her, no, no, no
her, can't blame her
Can't tame her
Thank you so much.
I had the most amazing night.
Please give it up one more time,
I'll see you next time.
I love you, Amsterdam.
@felipevannucci